/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a84b30e99eeabcd4708"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-is-interior-design-important?-",
    "answer" : "Studio DigiArch, lived in Pune, Maharashtra, IndiaAnswered November 10, 2020Why is interior design important? Studio DigiArch Interior design plays a very important role in our life today, making our lifestyle more modern and stylish. Not only that it also introduces us to elegance and comfort and helps to raise the functionality in our life.  Interior design helps to uplift our spirits and also helps to effectively optimize the space in our home making the best use of the available space. Here are some of the top 10 reasons which make interior design an important part of our lives: Add functionality to space: Interior design not only beautifies the interior of your building but also makes sure that it adds functionality to your home. Functionality is one of the key aspects of interior design. This is important because a poorly designed large house can be lacking in space or even a tiny apartment can be one of the peContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:32:36.223Z"),
    "question" : "Why is interior design important? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a84b30e99eeabcd470a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-colleges-in-interior-designing-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "According to launchpadacademy , here are top 10 interior design colleges in India: 1. National Institute of Design (NID) Location: Delhi Courses Offered: 1. 4 year B.Des courses in Furniture, Textile, Ceramic & Glass Design 2. 2.5 year M.Des courses in Furniture, Textile, Ceramic & Glass and Lifestyle Accessory Design Why Join: India’s top most design school in terms of faculty, exposure and placements 2. Sai School of Interior Design Location: New Delhi Courses Offered: 1. Certificate in Furniture Samadhan 2. Certificate in Vastu Shastra 3. 1 year Professional course in Interior Design 4. 2 year Advanced Professional course in Interior Design Why Join: Known for its specialized certificate courses and placements 3. Sir JJ School of Art Location: Mumbai Courses Offered: 4 year B Continue Reading According to launchpadacademy , here are top 10 interior design colleges in India: 1. National Institute of Design (NID) Location: Delhi Courses Offered: 1. 4 year B.Des courses in Furniture, Textile, Ceramic & Glass Design 2. 2.5 year M.Des courses in Furniture, Textile, Ceramic & Glass and Lifestyle Accessory Design Why Join: India’s top most design school in terms of faculty, exposure and placements 2. Sai School of Interior Design Location: New Delhi Courses Offered: 1. Certificate in Furniture Samadhan 2. Certificate in Vastu Shastra 3. 1 year Professional course in Interior Design 4. 2 year Advanced Professional course in Interior Design Why Join: Known for its specialized certificate courses and placements 3. Sir JJ School of Art Location: Mumbai Courses Offered: 4 year B Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:32:36.367Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best colleges in interior designing in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8a84b30e99eeabcd470c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-kind-of-jobs-can-you-get-with-an-interior-design-degree?-",
    "answer" : "Who This Career is For? This career is for those people who are passionate about design and are artistic. Since this career involves designing homes/properties, and then executing those designs to create the environment that the client wants, the person should have excellent management and communication skills, as well as be creative with his/her work. Those people who are good at maintaining their spending according to a budget as well as people who have a good knowledge about various materials are people who should defiantly be looking at interior designing as a potential career path. Moreover, people who have an eye for detail and enjoys solving puzzles would be an ideal interior designer. Want to know more about it? Interior designer is not new to us, as all our lives we have been organizi Continue Reading Who This Career is For? This career is for those people who are passionate about design and are artistic. Since this career involves designing homes/properties, and then executing those designs to create the environment that the client wants, the person should have excellent management and communication skills, as well as be creative with his/her work. Those people who are good at maintaining their spending according to a budget as well as people who have a good knowledge about various materials are people who should defiantly be looking at interior designing as a potential career path. Moreover, people who have an eye for detail and enjoys solving puzzles would be an ideal interior designer. Want to know more about it? Interior designer is not new to us, as all our lives we have been organizi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:32:36.369Z"),
    "question" : "What kind of jobs can you get with an interior design degree? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8aacb30e99eeabcd4723"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-interiors?-",
    "answer" : "You can completely change the look of your room by making minor changes to your furniture and lighting. Whether you have a four-storey mansion or a tiny apartment, there is an interior design fix for each type of home. Check out these tips to get inspiration to decorate your home: 1) Rope Lighting Want your bedroom to give off a relaxed and cozy vibe? Well-placed rope lighting can help you create the right mood. You can place it on the top of the headboard or even under your bed. If you want the light to be spread across the room, you can also try adding rope lighting to your ceiling. Overall, it adds a soft and welcoming glow to the entire room.  Image via S3Production.Bobvilla 2) Get Creative With Blinds Ditch the boring plain blinds and get creative to add character to your room. For a bold l Continue Reading You can completely change the look of your room by making minor changes to your furniture and lighting. Whether you have a four-storey mansion or a tiny apartment, there is an interior design fix for each type of home. Check out these tips to get inspiration to decorate your home: 1) Rope Lighting Want your bedroom to give off a relaxed and cozy vibe? Well-placed rope lighting can help you create the right mood. You can place it on the top of the headboard or even under your bed. If you want the light to be spread across the room, you can also try adding rope lighting to your ceiling. Overall, it adds a soft and welcoming glow to the entire room.  Image via S3Production.Bobvilla 2) Get Creative With Blinds Ditch the boring plain blinds and get creative to add character to your room. For a bold l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:33:16.308Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best interiors? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8abeb30e99eeabcd472e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-creative-interior-design-websites?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Joyce Tranchida 25",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:33:34.107Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most creative interior design websites? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8afeb30e99eeabcd4750"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-Architecture-and-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "While it is true that architects can (and do) interior design work, it is not true that interior designers can do architecture. Architecture is a licensed profession. Every state in the US licenses architects, and by doing so, grants them responsibility for health and safety of the occupants. In most states, you cannot call yourself an architect unless you have been licensed as an architect. Each state — plus the American Institute of Architects — sets standards to ensure that architects meet a specific type of knowledge. In most states its a minimum of the professional degree, plus 3 years of internship, plus passing the seven parts of the licensing exam. To be simplistic — architects design things that can fall down and injure people; they are responsible for the safe exiting out of a bui Continue Reading While it is true that architects can (and do) interior design work, it is not true that interior designers can do architecture. Architecture is a licensed profession. Every state in the US licenses architects, and by doing so, grants them responsibility for health and safety of the occupants. In most states, you cannot call yourself an architect unless you have been licensed as an architect. Each state — plus the American Institute of Architects — sets standards to ensure that architects meet a specific type of knowledge. In most states its a minimum of the professional degree, plus 3 years of internship, plus passing the seven parts of the licensing exam. To be simplistic — architects design things that can fall down and injure people; they are responsible for the safe exiting out of a bui Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:34:38.042Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between Architecture and interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b11b30e99eeabcd475b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-hire-an-interior-designer-or-an-architect?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Adam Vogs",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:34:57.272Z"),
    "question" : "Should I hire an interior designer or an architect? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b26b30e99eeabcd4768"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-interior-design-blogs?-",
    "answer" : "No matter if you are a student or a fan of interior designing, there are some blogging websites in the niche that produce quality content and is suitable for all. I have purposefully kept my list short as too much content will do more harm than good. My advice would be to keep a shortlist of websites and follow them whole-heartedly as too many of them will only confuse you. Here are the websites I regularly refer to: Alcove Studio: A relatively new company, their blogs are of quality content and will inform you about the latest trends in the scene. The thing I liked the most about their blogs is their east-to-understand content. Even a beginner in the field will easily grasp it. Do check it out. I have read their blogs and definitely loved it. They post regularly.  Home lane: Awesome quality, div Continue Reading No matter if you are a student or a fan of interior designing, there are some blogging websites in the niche that produce quality content and is suitable for all. I have purposefully kept my list short as too much content will do more harm than good. My advice would be to keep a shortlist of websites and follow them whole-heartedly as too many of them will only confuse you. Here are the websites I regularly refer to: Alcove Studio: A relatively new company, their blogs are of quality content and will inform you about the latest trends in the scene. The thing I liked the most about their blogs is their east-to-understand content. Even a beginner in the field will easily grasp it. Do check it out. I have read their blogs and definitely loved it. They post regularly.  Home lane: Awesome quality, div Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:35:18.113Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best interior design blogs? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b37b30e99eeabcd4770"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-would-you-find-the-best-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Mufaddal Bharmal The best???? If you'll ask me, I'll definitely take my name. Asking for best is not an answer to your anxiety. I know you are very anxious about appointing a designer (may be for your new home from your hard earned money, or may be be for your first office, or your space). And, you do not want to throw away your space in any wrong or non-professional's hands. Hiring a good Designer is a very lengthy and tiresome work. You have to look for their past works. Their style of works. Their forte of works. Their signature element in the designs. All above should match your preferences. If you will look for top notch designers on Google, their fee amount will be more than your entire budget. Plus their travelling fares to the site, to the stores and vendors will be extra burden on your budget. They will  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:35:35.592Z"),
    "question" : "How would you find the best interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b59b30e99eeabcd478a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-to-be-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "As an interior design student that has been struggling for 3 years, I’d like to say yes it is. For me. At first, I thought interior design would be easy for me since I have so much passion in drawing and design, turned out it didn’t easy as I expected. I’ll tell you about what makes it hard; both for being the interior student and being the interior designer. Interior design is fun. We play with colors, shapes, fabric, textiles, etc everyday. It wouldn’t be as stressful as we learn math or physics (I personally hate counting and formulas). But what makes it hard, and a bit stressful, is because of its much of tasks and assignments. There could be assignment everyday in a row; made a layout (I hate the manual drawing, digital drawing is fine). And the paper size is made me crazy, it’s in an A1  Continue Reading As an interior design student that has been struggling for 3 years, I’d like to say yes it is. For me. At first, I thought interior design would be easy for me since I have so much passion in drawing and design, turned out it didn’t easy as I expected. I’ll tell you about what makes it hard; both for being the interior student and being the interior designer. Interior design is fun. We play with colors, shapes, fabric, textiles, etc everyday. It wouldn’t be as stressful as we learn math or physics (I personally hate counting and formulas). But what makes it hard, and a bit stressful, is because of its much of tasks and assignments. There could be assignment everyday in a row; made a layout (I hate the manual drawing, digital drawing is fine). And the paper size is made me crazy, it’s in an A1  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:36:09.699Z"),
    "question" : "What is it like to be an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8b6bb30e99eeabcd4793"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-common-interior-design-styles?-",
    "answer" : "Divya Sharma The pandemic has changed everything around the globe. People are now prioritising their health over everything else more than ever, with more focus on sustainable living, which I believe is something long overdue. Another thing that the pandemic has brought to the centre stage is our living spaces. With more people spending time indoors, the home interior has taken centre stage. Everyone wants their space to be chic but also sustainable and healthy at the same time. Architects and designers are now well aware that they must create spaces that would help the client’s overall wellbeing and create a positive, healthy environment. Here are some trends I have observed that are taking the centre stage: Biophilic Design This trend is a fun way of integrating nature into living spaces. Adding indoor p Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:36:27.664Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most common interior design styles? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8beab30e99eeabcd47d0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-interior-designers?-",
    "answer" : " Award Winning Interior Design We are pleased to introduce ourselves as Royal Home Interiors & Construction Pvt. Ltd. (RHID) earlier known as S.R. Creations founded in 2008.RHID is one of the pioneer Civil, Residential and interior contracting company in this profession / trade for more than the last 7 years. Since 2008, we have been setting standards when it comes to unique perception of available space, planning and execution of design. You are sure to find a mark that speak of our 5 years of master touch to every aspect. Be it 500 sqft. Or 5 lakhs sqft. Attention to detail cusom-built interior solution, furniture and architectural excellence is delivered on the agreed date, time and quality levels. Our Solutions are customized not only to suit the unique need and restricted budget but also  Continue Reading  Award Winning Interior Design We are pleased to introduce ourselves as Royal Home Interiors & Construction Pvt. Ltd. (RHID) earlier known as S.R. Creations founded in 2008.RHID is one of the pioneer Civil, Residential and interior contracting company in this profession / trade for more than the last 7 years. Since 2008, we have been setting standards when it comes to unique perception of available space, planning and execution of design. You are sure to find a mark that speak of our 5 years of master touch to every aspect. Be it 500 sqft. Or 5 lakhs sqft. Attention to detail cusom-built interior solution, furniture and architectural excellence is delivered on the agreed date, time and quality levels. Our Solutions are customized not only to suit the unique need and restricted budget but also  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:38:34.857Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best interior designers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8bfcb30e99eeabcd47d8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-into-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Amisha Sehgal The first step you must take towards starting your career is getting an education to back your professional choice. So if you are looking to get started in Interior Design, I suggest that you start looking at some institutes that offer related courses. In my experience, it is best if you find an institute where you can learn things more practically, beyond the classroom environment, because that is where the real learning happens. I was intrigued by interior design as a profession when we were renovating our home. I realised that I enjoyed sitting with the professionals while they discussed the design of our space. I often found myself looking at different interior styles online, wondering how to decorate and how to make my home more comfortable and functional in the chicest way possible. I Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:38:52.704Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get into interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c0eb30e99eeabcd47e5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-interior-designers-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Interior design is the art and science of enhancing the interior of a building to achieve a healthier and more aesthetically pleasing environment for the people using the space. An interior designer is someone who plans, researches, coordinates, and manages such enhancement projects. Interior design is a multifaceted profession that includes conceptual development, space planning, site inspections, programming, research, communicating with the stakeholders of a project, construction management, and execution of the design. People usually especially in Indian culture doesn’t understand the importance of interior design. But when you go abroad and see the western way of living. The people abroad don’t compromise in their interior design. We Indian currently are coming up better ways to underst Continue Reading Interior design is the art and science of enhancing the interior of a building to achieve a healthier and more aesthetically pleasing environment for the people using the space. An interior designer is someone who plans, researches, coordinates, and manages such enhancement projects. Interior design is a multifaceted profession that includes conceptual development, space planning, site inspections, programming, research, communicating with the stakeholders of a project, construction management, and execution of the design. People usually especially in Indian culture doesn’t understand the importance of interior design. But when you go abroad and see the western way of living. The people abroad don’t compromise in their interior design. We Indian currently are coming up better ways to underst Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:39:10.623Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best interior designers in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c1fb30e99eeabcd47ef"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-I-need-to-know-about-Interior-Design?-",
    "answer" : "Neeraj C V 7 Facts you never knew about interior designing Interior Design is a combination of art and science as it involves lot of creativity. From lighting to colour choices, everything can be of impact to how a home feels. Some facts were quite intriguing for us when we went through them. We thought it would be amazing if you guys knew these facts too. Lighting could affect an individual Lighting of a room can have an effect on your body and can even rattle the sleep cycle of your body. This might lead to stress and sleep deprivation which is very dangerous to your immune system. Lighting plays a major role in boosting your sleep, and that’s why it’s better to keep your home lighted in a balanced way. Inspired by things around us Many amazing interior designs are inspired by everyday things and nature Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:39:27.532Z"),
    "question" : "What do I need to know about Interior Design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c31b30e99eeabcd47f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-interior-designers-find-clients?-",
    "answer" : "Arkaneh Urairat, Live in Bangkok know Thailand and Thais well.Answered 1 year ago · Author has 1.1K answers and 16.5M answer viewsHow do interior designers find clients? Arkaneh Urairat Wait , are you just graduated ? ….,,,,Have you ever worked with somebody else as an interior designer ? There are usual steps to be taken for any professional work ,which is:- To work with professional firm for couple of years or more .To get yourself a licence to practiceTo learn as much as you can to get the experiences and get familiarised with the building ‘s code and by laws .To get to know fellow consultants and know available building materials .To get to know people especially your company ‘s clients and that will lead you to being your own boss ( I don’t mean you should steal your boss’s clients )Have you done all these ? If you have, whenever you are your own boss.. I don’t think there won’t be any problem getting FIRST CUSTOMER . But , if you are now working with some company and p Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:39:45.167Z"),
    "question" : "How do interior designers find clients? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c43b30e99eeabcd4803"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-college-is-suitable-to-be-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which college is suitable to be interior designer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:40:03.877Z"),
    "question" : "Which college is suitable to be interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c54b30e99eeabcd480d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-online-interior-design-courses?-",
    "answer" : "There are a bunch of different online interior design courses from different online interior design academy that you will find if you search for them. You can take anyone from any of them. Also, there are many different interior design institutes from where you can take an interior designing course online. I can suggest you Think Interior Design Academy as I know better. They will provide you with an opportunity to polish your skills and get aware of the design concepts so that you may be able to create your own interior designs. Here will be able to learn the art of analyzing a design problem and find out practical solutions of the problems. On the other hand, at both for-profit and non-profit schools, online coursework in interior design is available mainly through degree programs. The cl Continue Reading There are a bunch of different online interior design courses from different online interior design academy that you will find if you search for them. You can take anyone from any of them. Also, there are many different interior design institutes from where you can take an interior designing course online. I can suggest you Think Interior Design Academy as I know better. They will provide you with an opportunity to polish your skills and get aware of the design concepts so that you may be able to create your own interior designs. Here will be able to learn the art of analyzing a design problem and find out practical solutions of the problems. On the other hand, at both for-profit and non-profit schools, online coursework in interior design is available mainly through degree programs. The cl Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:40:20.202Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good online interior design courses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c6bb30e99eeabcd4818"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I become an interior designer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:40:43.168Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8c91b30e99eeabcd4831"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-classes-do-interior-designers-take?-",
    "answer" : "Step 1: Students are required to complete 10+2 in any subjects with an aggregate of 50 percent of marks or equivalent to it from a recognised board. Those who want to pursue B.Arch for interior design are required to complete 10+2 in physics, chemistry and maths. Step 2: Several universities and colleges conduct entrance examinations to provide admissions. The candidates are required to meet the eligibility to appear in the entrance examination. It is compulsory for students to appear in NATA (National Aptitude Test in Architecture) for opting B.Arch. We have mentioned below the popular entrance examinations for establishing a career as an Interior Designer. Entrance examinations for Interior designer CEED: Common Entrance Exam for Design NID-EE: National Institute of Design Entrance Examinati Continue Reading Step 1: Students are required to complete 10+2 in any subjects with an aggregate of 50 percent of marks or equivalent to it from a recognised board. Those who want to pursue B.Arch for interior design are required to complete 10+2 in physics, chemistry and maths. Step 2: Several universities and colleges conduct entrance examinations to provide admissions. The candidates are required to meet the eligibility to appear in the entrance examination. It is compulsory for students to appear in NATA (National Aptitude Test in Architecture) for opting B.Arch. We have mentioned below the popular entrance examinations for establishing a career as an Interior Designer. Entrance examinations for Interior designer CEED: Common Entrance Exam for Design NID-EE: National Institute of Design Entrance Examinati Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:41:21.922Z"),
    "question" : "What classes do interior designers take? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8cb8b30e99eeabcd4845"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-university-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Akhilesh Mehta Well, interior design is unquestionably a good option for a career. The growing demand is certainly making it a trend. So talking about which university, hasn't specified anything but for India, then you should definitely go for the Karnavati University-Ahmedabad. Unitedworld Institute of design. Among the private institutes, UID should be your first preference. We went through the same question last year for choosing a better design institute/ University for my niece. Their curriculum, workshops, and infrastructure with well-equipped digital labs, auditoriums are much acknowledgeable. Having such an excellent team of faculty personnel with hands-on training makes the actual difference. Adding to its scope for the internship with reputed organizations enhances the overall exposure of the stu Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:42:00.164Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best university for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8ccbb30e99eeabcd4851"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-start-a-interior-design-business?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, you might have a great eye for design but it's not called a BUSINESS for anything. There is a huge difference between being able to make your own home look great and then starting a successful interior design business. Want to know how to do it? Read on... 1. Build a super slick website No-one is going to take you seriously as a designer if you can't even create a website that is extra special. Clients are looking for you to prove to them that you are forward thinking with your design approach and this needs to be reflected across the board, from your website to your outfit and so on. It's worth investing in this area heavily as you start up your interior design business. Take time to find a great web designer or learn as much as you can about creating a great site yourself. If you're goi Continue Reading Yes, you might have a great eye for design but it's not called a BUSINESS for anything. There is a huge difference between being able to make your own home look great and then starting a successful interior design business. Want to know how to do it? Read on... 1. Build a super slick website No-one is going to take you seriously as a designer if you can't even create a website that is extra special. Clients are looking for you to prove to them that you are forward thinking with your design approach and this needs to be reflected across the board, from your website to your outfit and so on. It's worth investing in this area heavily as you start up your interior design business. Take time to find a great web designer or learn as much as you can about creating a great site yourself. If you're goi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:42:19.651Z"),
    "question" : "How do I start a interior design business? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8ce0b30e99eeabcd485b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-interior-design-and-interior-decorating?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between interior design and interior decorating?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:42:40.470Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between interior design and interior decorating? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8cf5b30e99eeabcd4867"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-interior-designers-charge-for-services?-",
    "answer" : "Interior designers are professionally trained to make your space functional, beautiful and safe. They help in optimizing the available space by choosing the right kind of layout, artwork, colour and decorative elements. They can be of great help in designing and decorating your new flat or office space, especially when you want to utilize the space to fullest. Flat Design Consulting Fees In this model, you as a client will have to pay a flat fee (they call it to design consulting fees) to the interior designers. They will charge you a flat fee and design consulting charges. The interior designers will send their team to take the measurement and layout of the property. Then based on your requirements, they will create sketches or the design elevation. Based on the elevation, they will create 2D Continue Reading Interior designers are professionally trained to make your space functional, beautiful and safe. They help in optimizing the available space by choosing the right kind of layout, artwork, colour and decorative elements. They can be of great help in designing and decorating your new flat or office space, especially when you want to utilize the space to fullest. Flat Design Consulting Fees In this model, you as a client will have to pay a flat fee (they call it to design consulting fees) to the interior designers. They will charge you a flat fee and design consulting charges. The interior designers will send their team to take the measurement and layout of the property. Then based on your requirements, they will create sketches or the design elevation. Based on the elevation, they will create 2D Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:43:01.433Z"),
    "question" : "How do interior designers charge for services? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8d50b30e99eeabcd4893"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-designing-company-in-India-to-work-with?-",
    "answer" : "Here is a curated list of the top interior designing tech companies in India, ranked by Tracxn score, a proprietary ranking algorithm that takes into account various factors impacting a company’s size, growth, and execution. HomeLane (2014, $67.7M): Online platform providing interior design solutionsLivSpace (2015, $200M): Online interior designing service providersHouzz India (2017): Content-driven discovery and commerce portal catering to Home ImprovementDesign Cafe (2015, $34.2M): Online booking platform for interior design servicesFoyr (2014, $9.66M): Provider of a VR platform for visualizing real estate spacesFurdo (2014, $400K): Interior designer platform offering end to end servicesHouseome (2015, $77.4K): Online Home Interior and e-commerce solution providerBuildofy (2014): Online mContinue Reading Here is a curated list of the top interior designing tech companies in India, ranked by Tracxn score, a proprietary ranking algorithm that takes into account various factors impacting a company’s size, growth, and execution. HomeLane (2014, $67.7M): Online platform providing interior design solutionsLivSpace (2015, $200M): Online interior designing service providersHouzz India (2017): Content-driven discovery and commerce portal catering to Home ImprovementDesign Cafe (2015, $34.2M): Online booking platform for interior design servicesFoyr (2014, $9.66M): Provider of a VR platform for visualizing real estate spacesFurdo (2014, $400K): Interior designer platform offering end to end servicesHouseome (2015, $77.4K): Online Home Interior and e-commerce solution providerBuildofy (2014): Online mContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:44:32.022Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior designing company in India to work with? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8d68b30e99eeabcd48a2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-know-best-interior-designer-in-Pune?-",
    "answer" : "There are many interior designers in Pune, we can select perfect and best interior designer from them with the help of following tips. But if you ask me I will surely recommend you decormyplace. Because they fulfill all our need. How to select the best interior designer How to select the best interior designer in the town is the first question in mind after getting possession of the apartment anywhere in the world. The question is really tricky to answer, as there are thousands of interior designing professionals and companies around, to evaluate all of them is impossible for anyone. We will mention here with few of the most important parameters which must be evaluated to get answers to your query ‘How to select the best Interior Designers’. Request you go through all these parameters thorou Continue Reading There are many interior designers in Pune, we can select perfect and best interior designer from them with the help of following tips. But if you ask me I will surely recommend you decormyplace. Because they fulfill all our need. How to select the best interior designer How to select the best interior designer in the town is the first question in mind after getting possession of the apartment anywhere in the world. The question is really tricky to answer, as there are thousands of interior designing professionals and companies around, to evaluate all of them is impossible for anyone. We will mention here with few of the most important parameters which must be evaluated to get answers to your query ‘How to select the best Interior Designers’. Request you go through all these parameters thorou Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:44:56.931Z"),
    "question" : "Do you know best interior designer in Pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8d8bb30e99eeabcd48b3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-main-fundamental-concepts-of-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Sapna Aggarwal Budget: It’s the most important for it governs what you can spend on and what not.Theme: Do you know what kind of designs don’t look good? The ones that are all over the place. There has to be a central theme in a space for it to look good.Interior Designer: What your house will look like depends on the interior designer you hire. Does that designer take time to understand your personality and vision? Does that designer discuss everything with you and give you a clear picture on what’s happening? Does that designer care about you as a homeowner more than their own creative drive? If yes, you’ll have a wonderful house design that everybody’s going to fall in love with. If no, you need to switch your designer!Elements in Interior Designing Below are some of the basic elements involved in inte Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:45:31.918Z"),
    "question" : "What are the main fundamental concepts of interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8da1b30e99eeabcd48c2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-residential-interior-designers-in-Pune?-",
    "answer" : "I wish this column was written by someone who have already experienced working with an interior designer rather than write-ups by designing companies trying their best to boost themselves to get listed on this particular platform. Why don’t you understand that general people like us are already confused to hire the right designer and after reading such columns it becomes more chaotic? So I thought I will share my experience working with interior designers from Areaplanz design. I thought of writing on this because I want to help people like me to make the right decision by hiring the right interior designer. And also because just few months back we shifted to our heaven created by Areaplanz Design team. We have been really blessed, after struggling and running around searching for the right  Continue Reading I wish this column was written by someone who have already experienced working with an interior designer rather than write-ups by designing companies trying their best to boost themselves to get listed on this particular platform. Why don’t you understand that general people like us are already confused to hire the right designer and after reading such columns it becomes more chaotic? So I thought I will share my experience working with interior designers from Areaplanz design. I thought of writing on this because I want to help people like me to make the right decision by hiring the right interior designer. And also because just few months back we shifted to our heaven created by Areaplanz Design team. We have been really blessed, after struggling and running around searching for the right  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:45:53.657Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best residential interior designers in Pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8dc7b30e99eeabcd48d6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-does-an-interior-decorator-charge?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What does an interior decorator charge?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:46:31.031Z"),
    "question" : "What does an interior decorator charge? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8dddb30e99eeabcd48dc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-3D-rendering-software-for-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "There are many 3d rendering software available in the market. But the V-ray comes first in the mind with it’s robust and intuitive features. V-Ray is smarter, faster, and more powerful than ever software for 3D Rendering. The app is designed to get you up and running in no time. It lets you create the highest quality renders possible – directly in SketchUp. It gives you the power to move anything and everything – from quick design models to your most detailed 3D scenes. It lets you spend more time being creative and less time waiting. Focus on design, with a full suite of creative tools for lighting, shading, and rendering services.  Streamline your workflow and keep track of your entire scene quickly and easily with the new and improved asset management tools in V-Ray Renderer. You can now s Continue Reading There are many 3d rendering software available in the market. But the V-ray comes first in the mind with it’s robust and intuitive features. V-Ray is smarter, faster, and more powerful than ever software for 3D Rendering. The app is designed to get you up and running in no time. It lets you create the highest quality renders possible – directly in SketchUp. It gives you the power to move anything and everything – from quick design models to your most detailed 3D scenes. It lets you spend more time being creative and less time waiting. Focus on design, with a full suite of creative tools for lighting, shading, and rendering services.  Streamline your workflow and keep track of your entire scene quickly and easily with the new and improved asset management tools in V-Ray Renderer. You can now s Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:46:53.565Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best 3D rendering software for an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8deeb30e99eeabcd48e6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-necessary-to-be-good-at-drawing-for-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Not at all This was one of the many things that I was worried about before I went to my Design School. In the first few weeks the instructors had this issue sorted out. They made us understand that, of course good drawing skills are useful, but it does not mean that someone who is not good at drawing can not be a good designer. You just need to be able to express your ideas to others efficiently, and Sketching is a medium, among various others, that will help you do this. For example, instead of drawing out a rough floor plan by hand, if you find making the same on a computer (Illustrator/Photoshop) easier, more efficient, more helpful, then that is your way and it is as good as other ways to do it. Or you might find 3d Modelling and rendering to be something that interests you more than sketc Continue Reading Not at all This was one of the many things that I was worried about before I went to my Design School. In the first few weeks the instructors had this issue sorted out. They made us understand that, of course good drawing skills are useful, but it does not mean that someone who is not good at drawing can not be a good designer. You just need to be able to express your ideas to others efficiently, and Sketching is a medium, among various others, that will help you do this. For example, instead of drawing out a rough floor plan by hand, if you find making the same on a computer (Illustrator/Photoshop) easier, more efficient, more helpful, then that is your way and it is as good as other ways to do it. Or you might find 3d Modelling and rendering to be something that interests you more than sketc Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:47:10.972Z"),
    "question" : "Is it necessary to be good at drawing for interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e05b30e99eeabcd48ec"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-interior-design-ideas-or-suggestions?-",
    "answer" : "Whilst ‘trends’ change and evolve, they do so at different paces – some are popular for years rather than merely a season. There’s no escaping trends. Whether you live by them or feel totally unaffected, from popular paint shades to furniture choices, everything designed for our homes is influenced by a wider trend. Ideally, you should get your home designed by the best home interior designers in Mumbai as nobody has better home interior design ideas than them. From naval blue paint and floral backdrop to shaded cupboards and freestanding tubs, these are the 2020 interior design ideas for home decor that specialists can hardly wait to see. Navy Blue Classic Blue or navy blue is the 2020 Pantone Color of the Year, which implies that you will see a ton of the colour this year. Luckily, it's abso Continue Reading Whilst ‘trends’ change and evolve, they do so at different paces – some are popular for years rather than merely a season. There’s no escaping trends. Whether you live by them or feel totally unaffected, from popular paint shades to furniture choices, everything designed for our homes is influenced by a wider trend. Ideally, you should get your home designed by the best home interior designers in Mumbai as nobody has better home interior design ideas than them. From naval blue paint and floral backdrop to shaded cupboards and freestanding tubs, these are the 2020 interior design ideas for home decor that specialists can hardly wait to see. Navy Blue Classic Blue or navy blue is the 2020 Pantone Color of the Year, which implies that you will see a ton of the colour this year. Luckily, it's abso Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:47:33.571Z"),
    "question" : "What are some interior design ideas or suggestions? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e1ab30e99eeabcd48f2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-design-company?-",
    "answer" : "Rahul Gupta Most of the homeowners are intimidated when it is required to hire an interior designer. You can hire an interior designer for guidance and help with things like paint colour selection, lighting, fabric sourcing, and space planning. When you are moving into a new home or freshening up old-fashioned decor, an interior designer can be your best friend. You should really consider finding an interior design that speaks to your design sensibility, ask friends for recommendations or utilize professional organizations. If selecting an interior designer is all new to you then you should hire one that is professionally certified. Based on the size and scope of your project, you must decide the budget. This amount should be discussed beforehand with the interior designer. Some designers do not take on  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:47:54.682Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior design company? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e2db30e99eeabcd48fc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-an-architect-be-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "100%. Architects have a long training period which deals in all facets of buildings and their design. Obviously there are architects who es-hue some of these topics, such as Interiors and landscape, however architects at heart are creative design professionals, who care and understand not only structure and form; but light, colour, organisation, and aesthetics. As an architect I foremost am concerned with the interior layout and function, working with the clients desires to create a working beautiful space. This then goes hand-in-hand with the exterior expression and location of the building within is situation; thinking about orientation, in regards to sun & shade, as well as key views out and towards the building; as well as how the building sits within its context, in terms of urban desi Continue Reading 100%. Architects have a long training period which deals in all facets of buildings and their design. Obviously there are architects who es-hue some of these topics, such as Interiors and landscape, however architects at heart are creative design professionals, who care and understand not only structure and form; but light, colour, organisation, and aesthetics. As an architect I foremost am concerned with the interior layout and function, working with the clients desires to create a working beautiful space. This then goes hand-in-hand with the exterior expression and location of the building within is situation; thinking about orientation, in regards to sun & shade, as well as key views out and towards the building; as well as how the building sits within its context, in terms of urban desi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:48:13.586Z"),
    "question" : "Can an architect be an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e40b30e99eeabcd4902"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/If-I-have-to-do-interior-designing-then-what-skills-I-have-to-develope?-",
    "answer" : "Arkaneh Urairat The best interior designer and the most successful interior designer are 2 different things, it means the good qualities of one, can not apply to another. I believe, ONE interior designer can not be any better than another if both are in the practice at the same time, ONE can be successful in the business with more projects, more clients / customers thus more money, but another one who takes ‘one project’ at a time and meticulously designing it and micro supervise it- may only have enough clients, not too many but is very contented and satisfied. Take your pick,which ones is more important to you? Best interior designers require qualities like,- Taking in instructions from client attentively.Process a good vision with the ability to create consistent own original style of design.With the abiliContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:48:32.896Z"),
    "question" : "If I have to do interior designing then what skills I have to develope? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e51b30e99eeabcd4908"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-interior-design-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the scope of interior design in india?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:48:49.409Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of interior design in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e62b30e99eeabcd4910"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-you-name-some-good-interior-designers-near-Delhi-NCR?-",
    "answer" : "Today where most of the work is done online, it’s important for the people working to have a feel for the place so a local office is the best for it. These people know Delhi and surrounding areas like the back of their hand and have even established themselves as one of the best planning consulates in the capital. Interior design is a fascinating field. Best interior designing firm near Delhi :- Sanjyt Syngh: Next up in our list of the best interior designer in Delhi, India is Sanjyt Syngh. Mr Sanjyt runs an interior designing studio by the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio in New Delhi. He is famous for his influential work in the field. Some of his famous projects include the interior designing of places like the Gold Gym etc. The factor that makes his presence in this list is that the pattern wh Continue Reading Today where most of the work is done online, it’s important for the people working to have a feel for the place so a local office is the best for it. These people know Delhi and surrounding areas like the back of their hand and have even established themselves as one of the best planning consulates in the capital. Interior design is a fascinating field. Best interior designing firm near Delhi :- Sanjyt Syngh: Next up in our list of the best interior designer in Delhi, India is Sanjyt Syngh. Mr Sanjyt runs an interior designing studio by the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio in New Delhi. He is famous for his influential work in the field. Some of his famous projects include the interior designing of places like the Gold Gym etc. The factor that makes his presence in this list is that the pattern wh Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:49:06.917Z"),
    "question" : "Can you name some good interior designers near Delhi NCR? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e8ab30e99eeabcd4925"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-find-reliable-interior-designers-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I find reliable interior designers in Hyderabad?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:49:46.285Z"),
    "question" : "How do I find reliable interior designers in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8e9cb30e99eeabcd492d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-best-interior-designing-service-in-Delhi?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Who is best interior designing service in Delhi?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:50:04.500Z"),
    "question" : "Who is best interior designing service in Delhi? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8ed4b30e99eeabcd4945"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-Interior-design-company-in-Chennai?-",
    "answer" : "you may have heared so many interior design addresses and their links. but as far as concerned about myself always use the three quotation policy. each time you buy one thing or going to spend money enquire its price from three suppliers. here interior designers. also get help from your male partner to do every thing. once it is came to know that this work is carried out by a female house owner, definitely the designers will try to cheat you by identifying your weakness. don’t handover all the things to the designer and go away from the spot where the work is going on. try to put some known and reliable person to watch everything is going correct or not. watch everyday work and its improvement. don’t let them choose the design and the patterns. see more than 20 or 30 interior designs and choo Continue Reading you may have heared so many interior design addresses and their links. but as far as concerned about myself always use the three quotation policy. each time you buy one thing or going to spend money enquire its price from three suppliers. here interior designers. also get help from your male partner to do every thing. once it is came to know that this work is carried out by a female house owner, definitely the designers will try to cheat you by identifying your weakness. don’t handover all the things to the designer and go away from the spot where the work is going on. try to put some known and reliable person to watch everything is going correct or not. watch everyday work and its improvement. don’t let them choose the design and the patterns. see more than 20 or 30 interior designs and choo Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:51:00.404Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best Interior design company in Chennai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8ee6b30e99eeabcd494e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-i-learn-interior-design-online?-",
    "answer" : "I don’t believe any on line program would prepare you to be an interior designer. Most states have laws. ‘Title act’ which specifies the kind and amount of training PLUS years of work under a licensed Interior Designer is required to promote yourself as an Interior Designer. I would start by looking up the requirements in your state. Go to an accredited interior design program in your state. Do the 4–5 years learning not only taste, trends, etc but drafting materials computer programs like AUTOCAD, Rivit, sketchUp, maybe 2020 and otherprograms that broaden your skills. Take business, sales and marketing classes. You sell yourself every time you meet a perspective client. Join associations like ASID and network in other like associations. Take all the NCIDQ prep classes and pass the test. Co Continue Reading I don’t believe any on line program would prepare you to be an interior designer. Most states have laws. ‘Title act’ which specifies the kind and amount of training PLUS years of work under a licensed Interior Designer is required to promote yourself as an Interior Designer. I would start by looking up the requirements in your state. Go to an accredited interior design program in your state. Do the 4–5 years learning not only taste, trends, etc but drafting materials computer programs like AUTOCAD, Rivit, sketchUp, maybe 2020 and otherprograms that broaden your skills. Take business, sales and marketing classes. You sell yourself every time you meet a perspective client. Join associations like ASID and network in other like associations. Take all the NCIDQ prep classes and pass the test. Co Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:51:18.733Z"),
    "question" : "How do i learn interior design online? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8ef8b30e99eeabcd4954"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-one-is-best-Fashion-designing-or-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "I can’t differentiate which is better, because both has different scope and career path. You can select any programme according to your interest. Selecting course is all about passion. Your passion for your course, and for your future career. Because the secret to happiness is being able to love whatever it is you do in life. The most important consideration when choosing your course is asking yourself why you are looking to study. It’s important to think about what you are interested in, and what course you want to study. Is it because you can see your exciting, glittering career ahead. Let me make you simple for you. Fashion Designing: Fashion design is a form of art. To work as a designer, you should have an artistic and creative personality. You also have to be good at drawing and able t Continue Reading I can’t differentiate which is better, because both has different scope and career path. You can select any programme according to your interest. Selecting course is all about passion. Your passion for your course, and for your future career. Because the secret to happiness is being able to love whatever it is you do in life. The most important consideration when choosing your course is asking yourself why you are looking to study. It’s important to think about what you are interested in, and what course you want to study. Is it because you can see your exciting, glittering career ahead. Let me make you simple for you. Fashion Designing: Fashion design is a form of art. To work as a designer, you should have an artistic and creative personality. You also have to be good at drawing and able t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:51:36.649Z"),
    "question" : "Which one is best Fashion designing or interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8f1eb30e99eeabcd4961"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-think-of-the-Tesla-Model-3-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Darren Charest, \"Tesla Followers\" Admin, a Quora Space with Curated ContentAnswered 11 months ago · Author has 362 answers and 913.2K answer viewsWhat do you think of the Tesla Model 3 interior design? Darren Charest It’s minimalist and elegant, like every Apple product ever invented. For one, there is massive elimination of needless buttons, switches, dials, and gizmos all of which have been replaced by voice commands, a touchscreen, automation, and audible alerts. How many physical buttons do you have on your smartphone? I have 4 and 1 is the nuisance “Bixby” button I accidentally press 12 times per day. The Bixby button is proof-positive the presence of a button can be an unwanted wart. In short, we’ve gone from this to this:  Let’s not forget the original Roadster, Model S and Model X all used “instrument clusters” behind the steering wheel. Tesla has been there, done that.  The Model 3 was a chance for Tesla to adopt a more modern design (see below). Samsung and Apple proved long ago that many buttons, k Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:52:14.131Z"),
    "question" : "What do you think of the Tesla Model 3 interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8f31b30e99eeabcd4969"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-get-the-best-interior-designer-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Where can I get the best interior designer in Bangalore? I’m sharing my experience to give you an insight of the interior designs & decorators for Newly built houses. My dream home has almost reached. Its final completion stage & was due for furnishings. My wife was very keen to get latest designs implemented & had shortlisted some of the renowned interior designers for getting this job done. In the meanwhile, even I joined to her research & had requested for quotes from leading names in the market. Most of the quotes received were priced with max deviation of 5 ~ 10%. Quotes included major Bought out parts name for standard fitment which I too did not want to compromise upon. Before finalizing, We started visiting the completed project sites to gather more knowledge & to check the final finishing & reviews of customers. Most of the sites had impr Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:52:33.177Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I get the best interior designer in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8f59b30e99eeabcd4977"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-do-you-use-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "I do not and would not hire an interior decorator. My wife and I both have a sense of style that we like and share, and, since that involves a lot of personal touches, heirlooms, and family history, I doubt an interior decorator would do us much good. BUT ———- I know a lady well who hires one. Here are the reasons she tells me: She is not confident enough in her own judgement in design to go out and spend lots of money on stuff that she may likely regret later.She works in a high-powered job that sometimes requires her to host gatherings at her house. So her ‘interior decoration’ can have a bearing on her job.She puts in a good many hours. When she has time off, she prefers to spend it with her family, rather than shopping.She has no particular intrinsic interest to learn the components of deContinue Reading I do not and would not hire an interior decorator. My wife and I both have a sense of style that we like and share, and, since that involves a lot of personal touches, heirlooms, and family history, I doubt an interior decorator would do us much good. BUT ———- I know a lady well who hires one. Here are the reasons she tells me: She is not confident enough in her own judgement in design to go out and spend lots of money on stuff that she may likely regret later.She works in a high-powered job that sometimes requires her to host gatherings at her house. So her ‘interior decoration’ can have a bearing on her job.She puts in a good many hours. When she has time off, she prefers to spend it with her family, rather than shopping.She has no particular intrinsic interest to learn the components of deContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:53:13.827Z"),
    "question" : "Why do you use an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8f7cb30e99eeabcd4982"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-Basics-about-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "I'm answering this question in a different way. But these questions would be helpful for anyone working with spaces, whether for study purposes or whilst working in the field. Whenever I am given an interior design project by a new client I like to ask three questions, these are the things I ask after the project has been secured (signed off to me) and we have already discussed budget, do the afore mentioned things before even continuing with the following questions: 1. What are your favorite and least favorite colours? (Even if you are only provided with one colour for each, this will give you enough information to begin creating a space. To include a clients favorite colour in their space shows attention to detail and interest in what appeals to them.) 2. What does this space need to do/ful Continue Reading I'm answering this question in a different way. But these questions would be helpful for anyone working with spaces, whether for study purposes or whilst working in the field. Whenever I am given an interior design project by a new client I like to ask three questions, these are the things I ask after the project has been secured (signed off to me) and we have already discussed budget, do the afore mentioned things before even continuing with the following questions: 1. What are your favorite and least favorite colours? (Even if you are only provided with one colour for each, this will give you enough information to begin creating a space. To include a clients favorite colour in their space shows attention to detail and interest in what appeals to them.) 2. What does this space need to do/ful Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:53:48.773Z"),
    "question" : "What are the Basics about interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8f8fb30e99eeabcd498c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-being-an-interior-designer-a-good-job?-",
    "answer" : "Yog Urkundwar Interior Designers: Salary, career path, job outlook, education and more Education Required A bachelor’s degree is usually required in order to become an interior designer, as are classes in interior design, drawing, and computer-aided design (CAD). A bachelor’s degree in any field is acceptable, and interior design programs are available at the associate’s, bachelor’s, and master’s degree levels.Job Outlook The projected percent change in employment from 2016 to 2026: 5% (As fast as average)(The average growth rate for all occupations is 7 percent.)Licenses/CertificationsLicensure requirements vary by state. In some states, only licensed designers may do interior design work. In other states, both licensed and unlicensed designers may do such work; however, only licensed designers may use thContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:54:07.537Z"),
    "question" : "Is being an interior designer a good job? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c8fa1b30e99eeabcd4993"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-should-I-hire-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "So you are thinking of making decorating decisions for your home? How can you NOT hire an interior designer? Small but important decisions like colors for your rooms or tiles for your kitchen can be handled by the designer with your support. Consider it this way: For you, its your first (or maybe second) project. For them, this is a job. Hence while you will be obviously looking at how things look, they will also look at other factors like functionality and aesthetics within the same budget. Details communications with you will not only lead to your budget being optimized but style, comfort and looks of the place will go up drastically. While a homeowner wants the place to parallel their lifestyle, a contractor or carpenter can never understand this facet since they cannot compare to the sa Continue Reading So you are thinking of making decorating decisions for your home? How can you NOT hire an interior designer? Small but important decisions like colors for your rooms or tiles for your kitchen can be handled by the designer with your support. Consider it this way: For you, its your first (or maybe second) project. For them, this is a job. Hence while you will be obviously looking at how things look, they will also look at other factors like functionality and aesthetics within the same budget. Details communications with you will not only lead to your budget being optimized but style, comfort and looks of the place will go up drastically. While a homeowner wants the place to parallel their lifestyle, a contractor or carpenter can never understand this facet since they cannot compare to the sa Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:54:25.434Z"),
    "question" : "Why should I hire interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c90e5b30e99eeabcd49f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-residential-interior-designers?-",
    "answer" : "The basic difference between an interior designer and interior decorator is that of education. A decorator decides what accessories, artistic pieces, paints, and the like can be used to beautify a given space. A designer, on the other hand, after earning their degree in courses related to the field of interior design has to think about not just the visual aspect of the space but also the structural workings of the building. This involves figuring out where different electricity lines go, which pipeline is connected to which side (this is while designing washrooms and kitchens), etc. An interior designer is, however, usually the decorator of the space as well. An interior design concept is the central theme that all the design elements are focused upon. It exists as an idea first and is brou Continue Reading The basic difference between an interior designer and interior decorator is that of education. A decorator decides what accessories, artistic pieces, paints, and the like can be used to beautify a given space. A designer, on the other hand, after earning their degree in courses related to the field of interior design has to think about not just the visual aspect of the space but also the structural workings of the building. This involves figuring out where different electricity lines go, which pipeline is connected to which side (this is while designing washrooms and kitchens), etc. An interior designer is, however, usually the decorator of the space as well. An interior design concept is the central theme that all the design elements are focused upon. It exists as an idea first and is brou Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T06:59:49.899Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best residential interior designers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c90fbb30e99eeabcd4a02"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-institute-in-pune-for-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which are the best institute in pune for interior designing?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:00:11.752Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best institute in pune for interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9112b30e99eeabcd4a0a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-interior-designing-institutes-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some good interior designing institutes in Bangalore?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:00:34.361Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good interior designing institutes in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c912ab30e99eeabcd4a18"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-interior-designers-think-of-Ikea?-",
    "answer" : "John Powell As an Architect (the real kind) who has worked with Interior Designers and Interior Architects (the real kind), IKEA has been a blessing. This company is fully oriented to people who are homeowners and small businesses looking for low priced high visual appeal merchandise such as cabinetry, fabrics, furniture, lighting, accessories, etc. Quite a lot of hard goods require assembly with easy instructions and simple tools.  The professional designers refer to the realm as FF&E (furniture, fixtures and equipment). Such designers include decorators although they do not require professional licenses from states.  Clientele are insisting on high quality and durable construction. Wood furniture products are rarely veneered on particle board substrates which is often IKEA items.  Let it be known that Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:00:58.039Z"),
    "question" : "What do interior designers think of Ikea? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c913db30e99eeabcd4a21"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-way-after-class-12-to-become-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Nidhi There are three main course available. They are Bachelor’s Degree courses, Diploma or certificate courses Some of the bachelor’s Degree courses related to interior design can be done from any university. (Google for college names ) Minimum marks required are usually around 45-50% aggregate marks from any stream afte 10+2. Diploma in Interior Design or Diploma in Interior Design and Architecture can be done and duration for diploma is 1–2 years. In some institute it is merit based and in some it is direct. Certificate courses are not as valuable as its Degree and Diploma counterparts. But course duration is quite short, when it comes to certificate programs. Certificate in Interior Design or Certificate in Interior Design and Decoration course can be done from any private institution and thier du Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:01:17.388Z"),
    "question" : "What is way after class 12 to become an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9153b30e99eeabcd4a28"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-interior-designers-in-Kerala?-",
    "answer" : "Abraham Cheeran Babu If You ask this question to me I would not recommend you the best interior designers in kerala but I will tell you the main points that should consider for selecting the best interior companies in Kerala. Some of the main Points that I can tell you to select the best interior designers in Kerala are as follows:- Quality and Assurance:- The main Point in the Quality and assurance is that the quality and the trends of that specific design in the present time. The Assurance what I mean is the trust or confidence that the designer gives to the customer. These 2 things are should consider first.Ability to work:- The next thing to consider is that whether the company has the Ability do the work. What I mean is the workers Ability and the creativity of the workers are considered. We should also seContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:01:39.540Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best interior designers in Kerala? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c917bb30e99eeabcd4a38"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-do-a-interior-design-course-after-btech?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Can I do a interior design course after btech?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:02:19.958Z"),
    "question" : "Can I do a interior design course after btech? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9199b30e99eeabcd4a40"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-think-will-be-the-most-popular-interior-design-style-in-2019?-",
    "answer" : "Popular home decor styles that are completely in vogue!! Your home is a reflection of your personality! Home decor is a very personal and unique choice that is often a complicated decision to make because of the sheer variety and styles available in the market. A well styled home can not only transform your home into being the talk of the town but will also have a calming and soothing effect on your soul. Living in a home that matches your personality and enables you to make a style statement therefore becomes extremely important. For all those who are on a lookout for styles to redesign their living, we bring some of the home decor styles that are trendy now a days: 1. Modern Modern Interior DesignImage Source: Pinterest The modern style is for those who see beauty in simplicity. The basic p Continue Reading Popular home decor styles that are completely in vogue!! Your home is a reflection of your personality! Home decor is a very personal and unique choice that is often a complicated decision to make because of the sheer variety and styles available in the market. A well styled home can not only transform your home into being the talk of the town but will also have a calming and soothing effect on your soul. Living in a home that matches your personality and enables you to make a style statement therefore becomes extremely important. For all those who are on a lookout for styles to redesign their living, we bring some of the home decor styles that are trendy now a days: 1. Modern Modern Interior DesignImage Source: Pinterest The modern style is for those who see beauty in simplicity. The basic p Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:02:49.623Z"),
    "question" : "What do you think will be the most popular interior design style in 2019? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c91b3b30e99eeabcd4a4a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-the-INIFD-a-good-institute-for-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Yes It is, The outlook of designing path at INIFD Gandhinagar interior courses are filled with comfort, luxury, aesthetics and growing. The curriculum should generate the scope for opportunities to integrate experiential and exploitative learning in order to understand and achieve a high command of creative innovation and quality. Workshop and training programmer are tailored for the specific aimed at assisting them to put design awareness at primary and secondary level. INIFD Gandhinagar offers 1-2-3 year courses for students who are willing to pick up there future in interior designing world with the best experience. INIFD Gandhinagar is a unique institution with many problem-solving capabilities like in this COVID-19 pandemic we put out with online classes for all of us safety. our innovat Continue Reading Yes It is, The outlook of designing path at INIFD Gandhinagar interior courses are filled with comfort, luxury, aesthetics and growing. The curriculum should generate the scope for opportunities to integrate experiential and exploitative learning in order to understand and achieve a high command of creative innovation and quality. Workshop and training programmer are tailored for the specific aimed at assisting them to put design awareness at primary and secondary level. INIFD Gandhinagar offers 1-2-3 year courses for students who are willing to pick up there future in interior designing world with the best experience. INIFD Gandhinagar is a unique institution with many problem-solving capabilities like in this COVID-19 pandemic we put out with online classes for all of us safety. our innovat Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:03:15.270Z"),
    "question" : "Is the INIFD a good institute for interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c91d7b30e99eeabcd4a56"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-design-app?-",
    "answer" : "My favorite Interior Design application was Autodesk’s Revit. You can create a floor plan with a lot of detail easily, or at least much more easily than with their AuotCAD software. You can put in windows and doors. You can specify the exact dimensions and materials for all of these. Then you can add furniture, appliances, carpets, flooring, tile, etc. Many manufacturers provide Revit families so that you easily insert their products into a Revit design. You can apply materials to the floors, walls, furniture, practically everything. It is all done to a single model (what the architectural industry calls BIM) but you can create from this model all the floor plans, elevations, and renderings that you need. IF you properly specify all your materials, you can click on the 3D button and all of t Continue Reading My favorite Interior Design application was Autodesk’s Revit. You can create a floor plan with a lot of detail easily, or at least much more easily than with their AuotCAD software. You can put in windows and doors. You can specify the exact dimensions and materials for all of these. Then you can add furniture, appliances, carpets, flooring, tile, etc. Many manufacturers provide Revit families so that you easily insert their products into a Revit design. You can apply materials to the floors, walls, furniture, practically everything. It is all done to a single model (what the architectural industry calls BIM) but you can create from this model all the floor plans, elevations, and renderings that you need. IF you properly specify all your materials, you can click on the 3D button and all of t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:03:51.885Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior design app? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c91ecb30e99eeabcd4a60"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-you-suggest-some-good-research-topics-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "All you design students, it’s that time of the year again! The pressure is building up, and there are prime decisions to be taken. Whether you are an Architecture student, interior design, fashion or graphic design, end of semester project or thesis is a tough task to select. Challenging yourself with a suitable project and delivering it with equal finesse, is what your thesis is all about. Following factors can be considered while choosing a thesis topic: 1. INDIVIDUALITY  Your thesis topic is a culmination of your design ideals and philosophies which you’ve picked up over the course of study. It needs to incorporate all the principles and design lessons learnt over the years. Thesis is also about projecting your individuality, and your distinctive design approach. Look for topics which stan Continue Reading All you design students, it’s that time of the year again! The pressure is building up, and there are prime decisions to be taken. Whether you are an Architecture student, interior design, fashion or graphic design, end of semester project or thesis is a tough task to select. Challenging yourself with a suitable project and delivering it with equal finesse, is what your thesis is all about. Following factors can be considered while choosing a thesis topic: 1. INDIVIDUALITY  Your thesis topic is a culmination of your design ideals and philosophies which you’ve picked up over the course of study. It needs to incorporate all the principles and design lessons learnt over the years. Thesis is also about projecting your individuality, and your distinctive design approach. Look for topics which stan Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:04:12.549Z"),
    "question" : "Can you suggest some good research topics for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9201b30e99eeabcd4a68"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-and-how-do-interior-designers-buy-furniture-for-clients?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Where and how do interior designers buy furniture for clients?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:04:33.917Z"),
    "question" : "Where and how do interior designers buy furniture for clients? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c921eb30e99eeabcd4a72"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-designer-company-in-kolkata?-",
    "answer" : "Saify Interiors is among the best interior designers in Kolkata, who take into consideration every aspect of interior designing keeping your choice and taste in mind. We provide designs according to your choice, be it classic or contemporary, fashionable and phenomenal or any theme based design which best suits your lifestyle and personality. So, be it a residential, corporate or a commercial space interior designing, we have experts who will not only work out a beautiful but a very professional design keeping the functionality quotient to the optimum. The reason, we boast to be the best in interior designing is because; it’s not just our years of experience but also the number of projects and satisfied customers we have. Every new project brings new challenges because the choice and requi Continue Reading Saify Interiors is among the best interior designers in Kolkata, who take into consideration every aspect of interior designing keeping your choice and taste in mind. We provide designs according to your choice, be it classic or contemporary, fashionable and phenomenal or any theme based design which best suits your lifestyle and personality. So, be it a residential, corporate or a commercial space interior designing, we have experts who will not only work out a beautiful but a very professional design keeping the functionality quotient to the optimum. The reason, we boast to be the best in interior designing is because; it’s not just our years of experience but also the number of projects and satisfied customers we have. Every new project brings new challenges because the choice and requi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:05:02.357Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior designer company in kolkata? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9230b30e99eeabcd4a7b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-many-years-do-we-study-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How many years do we study interior design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:05:20.209Z"),
    "question" : "How many years do we study interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c926cb30e99eeabcd4a93"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-college-to-study-interior-design-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which is the best college to study interior design in Mumbai?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:06:20.088Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best college to study interior design in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9282b30e99eeabcd4a99"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-a-home-architect-and-interior-designer-at-the-same-time?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I become a home architect and interior designer at the same time?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:06:42.133Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become a home architect and interior designer at the same time? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c92b2b30e99eeabcd4aab"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-most-typical-mistakes-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Check your budget before shopping: Most of us are so much convinced by the idea of designing our home, that we end up making impulsive purchases. Sadly, this is something that can ruin the entire project. If you don’t establish and allocate a proper budget, you will end by buying items that you may not require, and there will be no money left for the project’s completion. Do a bit of homework like preparing a list of things you need, taking proper measurements of your house, seeing the estimated price of the items, etc. Once you are done with a robust planning stick to the parameters and then proceed to the purchase the things. Matching everything in your home: Many often, people feel that matching everything in the home can establish a theme. This is something that needs to be reassessed so Continue Reading Check your budget before shopping: Most of us are so much convinced by the idea of designing our home, that we end up making impulsive purchases. Sadly, this is something that can ruin the entire project. If you don’t establish and allocate a proper budget, you will end by buying items that you may not require, and there will be no money left for the project’s completion. Do a bit of homework like preparing a list of things you need, taking proper measurements of your house, seeing the estimated price of the items, etc. Once you are done with a robust planning stick to the parameters and then proceed to the purchase the things. Matching everything in your home: Many often, people feel that matching everything in the home can establish a theme. This is something that needs to be reassessed so Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:07:30.534Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the most typical mistakes in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c92d8b30e99eeabcd4ab9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-you-in-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Anthony Sully It all started when I was a little boy when drawing became a skill that I was to develop over the years. So my strongest subject at school was art which led me to study at an art school when I was 17. I knew that I wanted to go into the art and design sector but unsure of which path to take. Architecture loomed up as an option but I declined for two reasons: 1) In those days you needed maths and science as part of your entry requirements and as I was poor at both that deterred me from applying, 2) Being responsible for huge buildings was just to much for me to handle. Another important factor was that I began reading ‘Design’ magazine every month and I soon learnt all about the design industry. I was excited by what was going on and how much craft was going into interior design. Interior de Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:08:08.692Z"),
    "question" : "Why are you in an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c92ebb30e99eeabcd4ac1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-benefits-of-hiring-an-interior-designer-for-home?-",
    "answer" : "Why Should You Hire An Interior Designer NOT a Carpenter By Rajesh Manocha published On Dec 14 2016 An interior designer and a carpenter are often perceived as interchangeable artisans by the untrained eyes. Yet this cannot be farther from the truth! Traditionally, carpenters have been our go-to person for household woodwork like creation of wooden cabinets, almirahs, drawers, housing frames etc. An interior designer, on the other hand, specializes in the planning and designing of residential and commercial spaces to aid aesthetics and functionality. Both are skilled in their own right but have stark differences in their job roles that make them poles apart. A dream home is an ultimate aspiration for many and choosing the right person to build the home is as arduous as the actual activity of c Continue Reading Why Should You Hire An Interior Designer NOT a Carpenter By Rajesh Manocha published On Dec 14 2016 An interior designer and a carpenter are often perceived as interchangeable artisans by the untrained eyes. Yet this cannot be farther from the truth! Traditionally, carpenters have been our go-to person for household woodwork like creation of wooden cabinets, almirahs, drawers, housing frames etc. An interior designer, on the other hand, specializes in the planning and designing of residential and commercial spaces to aid aesthetics and functionality. Both are skilled in their own right but have stark differences in their job roles that make them poles apart. A dream home is an ultimate aspiration for many and choosing the right person to build the home is as arduous as the actual activity of c Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:08:27.917Z"),
    "question" : "What are the benefits of hiring an interior designer for home? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c92feb30e99eeabcd4ac7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-laptop-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "*I have lots of interest in computer and have assembled a mid range pc of worth 1000$ for my interior design requirements. My personal suggestion:) I would say set your budget and there are various options to chose from either Mac or a windows. I have worked on both Mac as well as Windows . Here are my experiences I would personally recommended using a Mac for professional interior design presentation. It reduces your burden a lot, trust me. You can become very effective in terms of preparing a design. It's very reliable. The best part about Mac is that , you can connect an external graphic card without the need of a PC using the thunderbolt cable. Since, Mac book is a costly affair, definitely go ahead with windows to make use of the money you are spending and achieve things which you cannot ac Continue Reading *I have lots of interest in computer and have assembled a mid range pc of worth 1000$ for my interior design requirements. My personal suggestion:) I would say set your budget and there are various options to chose from either Mac or a windows. I have worked on both Mac as well as Windows . Here are my experiences I would personally recommended using a Mac for professional interior design presentation. It reduces your burden a lot, trust me. You can become very effective in terms of preparing a design. It's very reliable. The best part about Mac is that , you can connect an external graphic card without the need of a PC using the thunderbolt cable. Since, Mac book is a costly affair, definitely go ahead with windows to make use of the money you are spending and achieve things which you cannot ac Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:08:46.887Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best laptop for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9315b30e99eeabcd4ad1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-colleges-for-masters-in-interior-design-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Beautiful & classy interiors don’t just happen. They are well planned & designed by qualified interior designers who combine their creative artistic skills to create beautiful functional spaces where people can work and live. Becoming a professional interior designer is more than just being creative. To be a successful interior designer, one requires formal education and training along with passion & determination of designing a splendid interior space. Interior designers are professionals who convert an interior space into an attractive and functional home or office space. With their skills & expertise on colors, lighting, and materials to decorate, designs an aesthetic interior. Interior designers may either be self employed or may even work for design servicing firm, architectural busine Continue Reading Beautiful & classy interiors don’t just happen. They are well planned & designed by qualified interior designers who combine their creative artistic skills to create beautiful functional spaces where people can work and live. Becoming a professional interior designer is more than just being creative. To be a successful interior designer, one requires formal education and training along with passion & determination of designing a splendid interior space. Interior designers are professionals who convert an interior space into an attractive and functional home or office space. With their skills & expertise on colors, lighting, and materials to decorate, designs an aesthetic interior. Interior designers may either be self employed or may even work for design servicing firm, architectural busine Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:09:09.592Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best colleges for masters in interior design in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c933eb30e99eeabcd4add"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-colleges-for-interior-designing-in-Delhi?-",
    "answer" : "Sagar Sharma, lives in Panipat, Haryana, IndiaAnswered 7 months agoWhich are the best colleges for interior designing in Delhi? Sagar Sharma Hello Eveyone! If you are living in Haryana Delhi NCR and looking for a college which offer Interior design course then I recommend must Visit Geeta Group of Institutions because this is the only college in the region which offer these kind of new and latest trending courses. This college is affiliated to Kurukshetra University which is one of the top university of Haryana. This institute and university both are NAAC Accredited and approved by AICTE. They has recorded maximum number of placement in the region. They believe in overall development of the students. Interior Design Course Details: Designing is an art of structuring and arrangement of things in a manner so as to reflect synchronization and authenticity of the designed area in consonance with its surrounding. Designing has been a cr Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:09:50.081Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best colleges for interior designing in Delhi? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9361b30e99eeabcd4aec"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-most-painful-part-of-running-your-interior-design-business?-",
    "answer" : "Aditi Shukla, Senior Interior Desginer at Interior Design (2017-present)Answered 6 months agoWhat is the most painful part of running your interior design business? Aditi Shukla 1. MANAGING TIME For interior design firms, time management skills are a must. There are only so many hours in a day and dozens of things need to get done. Organizing your time allows you to budget your hours effectively, prioritize projects, and stay on schedule to meet your forever looming deadlines. 2. SELLING YOUR BIG IDEAS One of the biggest challengers interior designers face is selling big ideas. Often times, you only have pictures or a floor plan to try and express the feel of an entire room. It’s hard to sell something that doesn’t physically exist. Do whatever it takes to get your ideas across. From fabric samples to mood boards, your clients will always appreciate the extra effort to help them understand the vision. 3. HANDLING THE BOOKS Yes—even designers have to handle the books. F Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:10:25.799Z"),
    "question" : "What is the most painful part of running your interior design business? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9374b30e99eeabcd4af1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-architecture-and-interior-design-impact-emotion?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do architecture and interior design impact emotion?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:10:44.504Z"),
    "question" : "How do architecture and interior design impact emotion? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9387b30e99eeabcd4afd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-should-a-interior-designer-must-know?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Zulfikri Fakhruddin",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:11:03.300Z"),
    "question" : "What should a interior designer must know? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c93c0b30e99eeabcd4b11"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-take-up-interior-designing-if-I-have-taken-commerce-stream-in-12th?-",
    "answer" : "I'm going to answer from a US perspective, since that's where I live. Most interior designers in the US have a degree in interior design and something else that affects it-business, etc. You could major in business and have a minor in interior design, and have that be your career.  Generally speaking, interior designers don't have a lot of options these days since everything is increasingly online now. However, with a business degree you can create a startup that focuses on interior design. Build up your client base, and you will use skills you've learned from both business classes and interior design classes.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:12:00.168Z"),
    "question" : "Can I take up interior designing if I have taken commerce stream in 12th? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c93d5b30e99eeabcd4b1b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-suggestions-on-good-interior-designers-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Dane Thomas I recommend DLIFE interior designers in Bangalore if you are planning to do you home interiors. I had availed services of DLIFE interior designers for my apartment in Bangalore in 2020 and had a truly pleasant experience. I had seen the quality of work done by DLIFE at my friend's apartment in Bangalore and when it came to my home interiors I didn't have to think of a second option. They have got a truly professional team who will take their time even at the odd hours to hear your suggestions and make sure it is addressed and sorted out. Great quality of work, timely execution (completed within 45 days) and excellent customer service. They even provide 5 Year Warranty on their products.  They made sure the timely execution with professional excellence and handed over in showroom condition. I  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:12:21.823Z"),
    "question" : "What are suggestions on good interior designers in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c941fb30e99eeabcd4b31"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-interior-design-ideas-for-small-house?-",
    "answer" : "1. Opt For Custom-Made Furniture: Custom-made furniture will be made according to the space available to you. It will, therefore, ensure that not an inch of space is wasted and your home looks bigger and better. Since custom-made furniture is in accordance with your requirement, space is used judiciously. At times, the furniture available in the stores might be bigger than you require and the next available option is smaller than what you can accommodate and what you need. At times, custom-made furniture is also cheaper. For instance, you require a small table for your living room. The ones available at the store will be according to a standard size and will not be according to the small living space you have. In this case, you don't have any option but to buy the big table, which is a waste Continue Reading 1. Opt For Custom-Made Furniture: Custom-made furniture will be made according to the space available to you. It will, therefore, ensure that not an inch of space is wasted and your home looks bigger and better. Since custom-made furniture is in accordance with your requirement, space is used judiciously. At times, the furniture available in the stores might be bigger than you require and the next available option is smaller than what you can accommodate and what you need. At times, custom-made furniture is also cheaper. For instance, you require a small table for your living room. The ones available at the store will be according to a standard size and will not be according to the small living space you have. In this case, you don't have any option but to buy the big table, which is a waste Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:13:35.649Z"),
    "question" : "What is the interior design ideas for small house? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c942fb30e99eeabcd4b37"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-course-is-better-among-interior-designing-and-fashion-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Choice of a career varies from person to person. So it is very much difficult to define which career is best. As career choice depends upon person interest. If someone has interest in fashion then fashion designing might be a good career option for him and if someone has interest in decoration and designing then interior designing may be best career option for him or her. Here is the difference between two and you can choose best option for you as per your interest. Fashion Designing is an art related to creation of clothing, footwear and lifestyle accessories. It is considered as most demanding career stream in India as well as all across the world. So a person who wants to make career as fashion designer should possess some skills like good communication, creativity, good drawing and sket Continue Reading Choice of a career varies from person to person. So it is very much difficult to define which career is best. As career choice depends upon person interest. If someone has interest in fashion then fashion designing might be a good career option for him and if someone has interest in decoration and designing then interior designing may be best career option for him or her. Here is the difference between two and you can choose best option for you as per your interest. Fashion Designing is an art related to creation of clothing, footwear and lifestyle accessories. It is considered as most demanding career stream in India as well as all across the world. So a person who wants to make career as fashion designer should possess some skills like good communication, creativity, good drawing and sket Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:13:51.474Z"),
    "question" : "Which course is better among interior designing and fashion designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c947bb30e99eeabcd4b52"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-interior-designer-for-my-home-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Adithya, lives in Bengaluru, Karnataka, IndiaAnswered December 8, 2020Who is the best interior designer for my home in Bangalore? Adithya If you are looking to design your new home, I would like to suggest you go with Incube Studio! Buying a new home in Bangalore is not at all an easy task as Bangalore being one of the Silicon Valley of India. After buying a home, every person dreams of stunning and beautiful interiors that are personalized for their style. And my interiors were affordable and within the budget too. When I contacted In-cube Studio, I never knew I will be so satisfied with my interiors! The process went smoothly from the first meeting to the execution. I came to know about them from one of their social activity and after a lot of meetings and discussions, I was convinced that my home is in safe hands. They are transparent and professional that made me believe in them. And as promised, they handed my dream home  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:15:07.748Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best interior designer for my home in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c94a0b30e99eeabcd4b5d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-pros-and-cons-of-studying-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the pros and cons of studying interior design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:15:44.788Z"),
    "question" : "What are the pros and cons of studying interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c94c0b30e99eeabcd4b70"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-interior-designer-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "Ranjith Undoubtedly 7Elements Interior Studio is the best interior designers in Hyderabad because they had a unique and exceptionally well-designed process. INTERIOR DESIGN SERVICES IN HYDERABAD  0:00-0:30 Top Interior Designers in Hyderabad Best known for Creating sophisticated, trendy and functional spaces as exceptional as our customers. We are the best interior designers in Hyderabad , that is multi-disciplinary in a way that we offer range of services including residential, commercial, hospitality and retail spaces. We are known for our agility, excellency in creating best solution for your interior design needs. OFFERED DESIGN SERVICES We believe in giving high quality services no matter what solution we are offering we ensure all of them to be top notch quality let it be residential, commercial or may it b Continue Reading 0:00-0:30",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:16:16.759Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best interior designer in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c94d4b30e99eeabcd4b76"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-does-an-interior-designer-earn-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for A2A! Salary depends on the level of the firm and the work you are doing for them as there are so many job profiles in interior design business. if you are a freelancer then it depends on the client’s budget and the project. Your salary can increase along with your experience which is very common in every field. Just for giving you an rough idea i can tell you the average salary of a interior designer. Freshers can earn upto 5,000 to 10,000 in starting. Assistant interior designers ranges between Rs. 30,000 to Rs.40,000 per month according to their experience and quality of the work. For senior interior designers, the salary, including bonuses and commission is approximately Rs. 800,000 to Rs. 3,000,000 per annum. The above numbers are not accurate but just a rough idea of a interior d Continue Reading Thanks for A2A! Salary depends on the level of the firm and the work you are doing for them as there are so many job profiles in interior design business. if you are a freelancer then it depends on the client’s budget and the project. Your salary can increase along with your experience which is very common in every field. Just for giving you an rough idea i can tell you the average salary of a interior designer. Freshers can earn upto 5,000 to 10,000 in starting. Assistant interior designers ranges between Rs. 30,000 to Rs.40,000 per month according to their experience and quality of the work. For senior interior designers, the salary, including bonuses and commission is approximately Rs. 800,000 to Rs. 3,000,000 per annum. The above numbers are not accurate but just a rough idea of a interior d Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:16:36.944Z"),
    "question" : "How much does an interior designer earn in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c94eab30e99eeabcd4b7e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-select-the-best-interior-designing-for-my-house-at-affordable-cost?-",
    "answer" : "Prashant Kulshreshtha, B.Arch.  Architecture & Design, Pune UniversityUpdated 9 months ago · Author has 149 answers and 254K answer viewsHow do I select the best interior designing for my house at affordable cost? Prashant Kulshreshtha Though there are thousands of points to be checked before hiring a designer for your house. We have shortlisted a few after being asked a lot of times. 5 Hidden Criteria For Selecting The Best Interior Designer in 2020? - There are chances that your project may go in the wrong hands if you select the designer randomly. But we have seen that these mentioned points have always given the clients their best buddy. Additionally, I don't know if best, but we have been the most desired candidate till now for whatever projects we executed. Additionally, we have been getting clients without marketing actually (word of mouth have been enough for us) Be it residential or commercial. Why? Because we have been marked 5* for all the projects we executed (till now no negative comments even after handling 125  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:16:58.063Z"),
    "question" : "How do I select the best interior designing for my house at affordable cost? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c94fcb30e99eeabcd4b85"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-examples-of-awful-interior-Design?-",
    "answer" : "Kat Rectenwald Anyone who grew up in the 70’s and 80’s in Germany knows about this abomination: Gelsenkirchener Barock, Baroque from Gelsenkirchen, which was until not that long ago a stinky, ugly industrial city in North Rhine Westphalia. The term Gelsenkirchener Barock was meant ironic, around since the early 30’s and the “style” was everywhere, you would rarely see an Interior Design that was different, and almost never with the working classes. The centerpiece of the living room always was the “Wohnwand” (the “livingwall”), a giant cupcoard, mostly stuffed to the brim and decorated with “Deckchen”, some sort of doilies, crocheted or not. This was a typical living room:  A typical “Wohnwand”  A typical living room table (btw, I got this picture from ebay, there is still plenty of this kind of furniture aroun Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:17:16.044Z"),
    "question" : "What are some examples of awful interior Design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c950eb30e99eeabcd4b8d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-courses-should-a-person-interested-in-interior-design-take?-",
    "answer" : "I went back to get my BFA in Interior Design as an adult, after I'd already been working as an interior designer for a few years—which means by the time I got there I had a good sense of what I \"needed\" to add to my knowledge, and I also had a good idea of which classes my university was requiring me to take, were a waste of my professional time. (Luckily, at my school, I didn't waste a lot of time.) Besides the obvious, as many Interior Design classes as you can get your hands on:  Art history. Expands your horizons, sharpens your eye, fills you and inspires you.Design history, if offered separately. Same reasons.Beginning architecture; if your class schedule permits it, I'd suggest beginning mechanical engineering and electrical engineering as well. Try to learn as much as you can about theContinue Reading I went back to get my BFA in Interior Design as an adult, after I'd already been working as an interior designer for a few years—which means by the time I got there I had a good sense of what I \"needed\" to add to my knowledge, and I also had a good idea of which classes my university was requiring me to take, were a waste of my professional time. (Luckily, at my school, I didn't waste a lot of time.) Besides the obvious, as many Interior Design classes as you can get your hands on:  Art history. Expands your horizons, sharpens your eye, fills you and inspires you.Design history, if offered separately. Same reasons.Beginning architecture; if your class schedule permits it, I'd suggest beginning mechanical engineering and electrical engineering as well. Try to learn as much as you can about theContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:17:34.471Z"),
    "question" : "What courses should a person interested in interior design take? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9522b30e99eeabcd4b93"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-suggested-interior-design-companies-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some suggested interior design companies in Mumbai?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:17:54.896Z"),
    "question" : "What are some suggested interior design companies in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9544b30e99eeabcd4ba2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-does-an-interior-designer-charge-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Disclaimer: I am the co-founder of an interior design startup called Truww.com Interiors in India is done based on sqft rates which may vary from Rs. 70–150/sqft for designing only and Rs. 800–3000/sqft for designing and implementation. This rate is multiplied to the sqft area of the furniture unit. The sqft area of a furniture is calculated by multiplying the width and height (Its not the sqft area of the floor). To read more on how the calculation is done check out this guide: A brief guide to woodwork costing in bangalore-Truww The rates vary depending on materials, type of furniture and expertise of an interior firm. Here are the prevalent rates in Bangalore:  Image is taken from the post on Truww As you would see, I have only given a range of the pricing and the exact rate depends on the kin Continue Reading Disclaimer: I am the co-founder of an interior design startup called Truww.com Interiors in India is done based on sqft rates which may vary from Rs. 70–150/sqft for designing only and Rs. 800–3000/sqft for designing and implementation. This rate is multiplied to the sqft area of the furniture unit. The sqft area of a furniture is calculated by multiplying the width and height (Its not the sqft area of the floor). To read more on how the calculation is done check out this guide: A brief guide to woodwork costing in bangalore-Truww The rates vary depending on materials, type of furniture and expertise of an interior firm. Here are the prevalent rates in Bangalore:  Image is taken from the post on Truww As you would see, I have only given a range of the pricing and the exact rate depends on the kin Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:18:28.916Z"),
    "question" : "How much does an interior designer charge in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c956bb30e99eeabcd4bb0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-most-effective-home-interiors-design-website?-",
    "answer" : "No such thing. To begin with, what would make a site better than every other site? More ideas? More pictures? More do-it-yuoself? More displays of new manufacturer merchandise? Eventually, more of everything would just create confusion and clutter. Better advice? Well then, what makes advice “better”? And if one site could offer a more inspired advice-giver, why would not some other site find one or more equally or even increasingly inspired advisers? “Best” also has to be determined in terms of the users. The best site for an amateur, looking to furnish an apartment, would be useless for a wealthy person furnishing a mansion. “Best” also has to be seen in terms of their focus. Some interior design is done with modernistic styles. Some is done with traditional motifs. Some deals with antiques. Continue Reading No such thing. To begin with, what would make a site better than every other site? More ideas? More pictures? More do-it-yuoself? More displays of new manufacturer merchandise? Eventually, more of everything would just create confusion and clutter. Better advice? Well then, what makes advice “better”? And if one site could offer a more inspired advice-giver, why would not some other site find one or more equally or even increasingly inspired advisers? “Best” also has to be determined in terms of the users. The best site for an amateur, looking to furnish an apartment, would be useless for a wealthy person furnishing a mansion. “Best” also has to be seen in terms of their focus. Some interior design is done with modernistic styles. Some is done with traditional motifs. Some deals with antiques. Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:19:07.875Z"),
    "question" : "What is the most effective home interiors design website? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9592b30e99eeabcd4bbc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-become-a-self-taught-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Shaila Hegde Any new interest can turn into passion or daily routine when one starts putting time and effort into it. In my case, interests transformed from one to another over the years. Every year we have a custom in my family to go for at least one big vacation. In every trip, I used to buy all cute locally hand-made, beautiful handicrafts. So slowly that became my passion to collect beautiful wall-plaques, coins, toy cars etc. The collections slowly came out of storage box and got life on my home walls ! They became part of my home décor and it gave me immense pleasure to look at them every day. It just ignited a brand new interest within me to decorate every single wall my own unique way. I STRONGLY believe, home décor is for myself.. not for others. So I put things around the house which triggers a Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:19:46.512Z"),
    "question" : "How can I become a self-taught interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c95b7b30e99eeabcd4bcb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-unknown-interior-design-tips?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the best unknown interior design tips?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:20:23.896Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best unknown interior design tips? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c95dab30e99eeabcd4bda"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-institute-for-interior-design-course-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "Dushkriti ChackoAnswered 2 years ago · Author has 186 answers and 419.3K answer viewsWhich is the best institute for interior design course in Hyderabad? Dushkriti Chacko IIFA Lancaster Degree college IIFA - LANCASTER an Institute for Interior designing, Fashion designing and Animation is a part of LANCASTER Group of Institutions which was established in the year 1991. The institute has a vision to be top institutions in the country. The institution is provides varieties of designing and animation courses under one roof with the state-of-art infrastructure facilities and excellent faculty network. The Core Purpose of the institution is to provide professional services associated with education and training in the field of Interior design, Fashion design and Animation, by adhering to International Standards, which are reviewed continuously for improvement to accomplish consistent customer satisfaction. Our faculty team is an integral part of the organization’ Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:20:58.252Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best institute for interior design course in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c95ecb30e99eeabcd4be4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-compulsory-to-be-a-maths-student-to-do-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "No, its not if you are going for a diploma or a degree. The diploma consist of two years and three years in college. The degree is a three years course. The interior design course can be done after 10th SSC boards. The diploma course admissions are being given on the merit list of your SSC boards percentage in some colleges. Whereas, for the Degree you may need to give a basic entrance examination. So you can do it any point of time no math subject required. But, I suggest if you are seeking for an Interir Design Course I suggest to go after completing 12th HSC and you may apply for the course. Yet, you still pursue for degree either from the college or IDOL courses(Institute of Distance & Open Learning) its basically a bachelor course where you have to give the exam just once a year and in Continue Reading No, its not if you are going for a diploma or a degree. The diploma consist of two years and three years in college. The degree is a three years course. The interior design course can be done after 10th SSC boards. The diploma course admissions are being given on the merit list of your SSC boards percentage in some colleges. Whereas, for the Degree you may need to give a basic entrance examination. So you can do it any point of time no math subject required. But, I suggest if you are seeking for an Interir Design Course I suggest to go after completing 12th HSC and you may apply for the course. Yet, you still pursue for degree either from the college or IDOL courses(Institute of Distance & Open Learning) its basically a bachelor course where you have to give the exam just once a year and in Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:21:16.794Z"),
    "question" : "Is it compulsory to be a maths student to do interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c95fcb30e99eeabcd4be8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-careers-correlate-with-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "This is such a great question and honestly, I wish this was being discussed more with current students of interior design because the shocking reality is most with an ID degree don’t end up working as interior designers (I mean the classic designer who works at a design firm doing large-scale residential and/or commercial design projects) upon graduating. Rather, many find careers in alternative/related fields, unless they get in with a firm early on through an internship, work their way in with great connections, or start their own business (like I did). Other careers that those with a background in interior design may find employment in include: set designingprop styling for photo shootsevent styling and/or planningwedding styling and/or planning (somewhat related: I actually have a friendContinue Reading This is such a great question and honestly, I wish this was being discussed more with current students of interior design because the shocking reality is most with an ID degree don’t end up working as interior designers (I mean the classic designer who works at a design firm doing large-scale residential and/or commercial design projects) upon graduating. Rather, many find careers in alternative/related fields, unless they get in with a firm early on through an internship, work their way in with great connections, or start their own business (like I did). Other careers that those with a background in interior design may find employment in include: set designingprop styling for photo shootsevent styling and/or planningwedding styling and/or planning (somewhat related: I actually have a friendContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:21:32.789Z"),
    "question" : "What careers correlate with interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c961fb30e99eeabcd4bf6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-advantage-of-being-an-Interior-Designer?-",
    "answer" : "Kanad LawandeAnswered 5 years ago · Author has 298 answers and 453.2K answer viewsWhat is the advantage of being an Interior Designer? Kanad Lawande All designing professions seem to have the HALO effect around them. You introduce yourself as a designer and instantly get a friendly approving nod in return, sometimes a lot more than a nod.... If you are creative, I dont have to tell you the possibilities of this... ;) The biggest perk is that interior designers usually get their places done for damn cheap or free.Having known professionals from other interior designing related fields and being instrumental in providing them business, Interior designers enjoy free services or massive discounts on their private spaces.Apart from this, sponsored trips abroad, free VIP invitations to exhibitions and product launches, free samples and festival \"greetings\", discounts at places designed like hotels, hospitals, spas etc make this one a very lu Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:22:07.372Z"),
    "question" : "What is the advantage of being an Interior Designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c965cb30e99eeabcd4c0a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-you-get-a-job-as-an-interior-designer-without-going-to-design-school?-",
    "answer" : "There was a time when interior design wasn’t even an actual profession. And that time was not too Long ago actually. In the recent past, the job of interior design was either done by architects or by people who occupied the spaces that needed decorating. It is when businesses began demanding more and more personalized designs for their buildings and individuals started getting more creative with how they wanted their homes to look, that the demand for people who were professionals in their field and whose sole job was to decorate the inner space of a building sprung up.Today, these professionals are in high demand across the globe and, in most cases, are getting paid handsomely for their work. Many people have seen this rise in demand for interior designers andwish to indulge in this art t Continue Reading There was a time when interior design wasn’t even an actual profession. And that time was not too Long ago actually. In the recent past, the job of interior design was either done by architects or by people who occupied the spaces that needed decorating. It is when businesses began demanding more and more personalized designs for their buildings and individuals started getting more creative with how they wanted their homes to look, that the demand for people who were professionals in their field and whose sole job was to decorate the inner space of a building sprung up.Today, these professionals are in high demand across the globe and, in most cases, are getting paid handsomely for their work. Many people have seen this rise in demand for interior designers andwish to indulge in this art t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:23:08.702Z"),
    "question" : "How do you get a job as an interior designer without going to design school? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9673b30e99eeabcd4c12"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-think-interior-designers-have-skill?-",
    "answer" : "As in any profession, there is a level of educated needed, and if you are a good student you may understand principles to help you when designing. However, you will need to understand the clients’ needs, create plans according to building codes when necessary, and be able to complete a project within a timeline and budget. To answer your question - yes! Here's where I believe an interior designer brings value. Educating a client though excellent communication.I was hired by a woman who had problems with her kitchen installation and insisted she wanted Marble countertops. The client lives on Florida’s intercostal, and her husband and boys go fishing. They prepped, cleaned, and seasoned their fish on the countertops. When I arrived I let her rant for a bit and then placed down a sample of CarrarContinue Reading As in any profession, there is a level of educated needed, and if you are a good student you may understand principles to help you when designing. However, you will need to understand the clients’ needs, create plans according to building codes when necessary, and be able to complete a project within a timeline and budget. To answer your question - yes! Here's where I believe an interior designer brings value. Educating a client though excellent communication.I was hired by a woman who had problems with her kitchen installation and insisted she wanted Marble countertops. The client lives on Florida’s intercostal, and her husband and boys go fishing. They prepped, cleaned, and seasoned their fish on the countertops. When I arrived I let her rant for a bit and then placed down a sample of CarrarContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:23:31.647Z"),
    "question" : "Do you think interior designers have skill? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9684b30e99eeabcd4c18"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-stream-should-we-choose-after-10th-for-getting-into-interior-or-fashion-designing-later?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which stream should we choose after 10th for getting into interior or fashion designing later?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:23:48.493Z"),
    "question" : "Which stream should we choose after 10th for getting into interior or fashion designing later? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9696b30e99eeabcd4c20"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-interior-design-masters-in-usa?-",
    "answer" : "The US is home to more than 130 million families and is the land of modernism and lavishness. When it comes to interior designing, the country has some of the world's best interior designers, as the USA is one of the best places to live in the world. At Sara Hospitality, we have compiled a list of top 6 interior designers in the USA for ideas, inspiration, and more. Michael S. Smith  Michael Smith is the White House's favorite interior designer and is at the top of his game. Michael S Smith completed his studies from the Victoria and Albert Museum and has been crafted under the memorable Gep Durenberger. His work portrays the beautiful balance of American modernism, European classicism, and has always surprised the critiques by unique furniture settings, and decor with one of the most elegant Continue Reading The US is home to more than 130 million families and is the land of modernism and lavishness. When it comes to interior designing, the country has some of the world's best interior designers, as the USA is one of the best places to live in the world. At Sara Hospitality, we have compiled a list of top 6 interior designers in the USA for ideas, inspiration, and more. Michael S. Smith  Michael Smith is the White House's favorite interior designer and is at the top of his game. Michael S Smith completed his studies from the Victoria and Albert Museum and has been crafted under the memorable Gep Durenberger. His work portrays the beautiful balance of American modernism, European classicism, and has always surprised the critiques by unique furniture settings, and decor with one of the most elegant Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:24:06.951Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best interior design masters in usa? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c96a6b30e99eeabcd4c28"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-college-matter-in-interior-designing-and-why?-",
    "answer" : "There is no straight answer or a short one. In some countries, this profession is regulated, and it does require a person to hold a degree to practice it. At the same time in other countries you do not need, but it’s an unwritten law that clients will accept you better if you have a degree. From my experience, I can say that degree does not make a designer tremendous, and I know interior designers with amazing skills and very famous without any degrees or certificates. What a designer do needs is integrity and insurance liability; the rest is just background noise. Eighty per cent of all interior designers are dishonest, and they offer design based on their commissions. PS: One of the most important skills you should have as an interior designer is the management of your team, projects, time an Continue Reading There is no straight answer or a short one. In some countries, this profession is regulated, and it does require a person to hold a degree to practice it. At the same time in other countries you do not need, but it’s an unwritten law that clients will accept you better if you have a degree. From my experience, I can say that degree does not make a designer tremendous, and I know interior designers with amazing skills and very famous without any degrees or certificates. What a designer do needs is integrity and insurance liability; the rest is just background noise. Eighty per cent of all interior designers are dishonest, and they offer design based on their commissions. PS: One of the most important skills you should have as an interior designer is the management of your team, projects, time an Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:24:22.739Z"),
    "question" : "Does college matter in interior designing and why? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c96cab30e99eeabcd4c34"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-country-is-best-to-study-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "As told by karan and shiva earlier Italy is the place to be in if you want to learn world class interior design. However you also need to consider what kind of market/which country you want to cater to. If its India then i would suggest you to stay in India and study interior design in a good institute. The reason is simple, response to context, you cant understand the problems and requirements of Indian consumer sitting somewhere in europe. You will learn good designing but to understand the functional and cultural requirements you have to be here so that in your formative years you see, learn and improvise things",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:24:58.024Z"),
    "question" : "Which country is best to study interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c96ddb30e99eeabcd4c3d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-part-of-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Speaking from our hearts, it has to be seeing happy families and all our homeowner clients-turned-friends moving into their homes that were designed by us. To hear that they look forward to coming home everyday and the increased efforts to bond with each other more than before is why we do what we do. For single homeowners, they would also feedback that they never want to step out of their house because there is no other place more cozy and entertaining than their newly renovated homes. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:25:17.684Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best part of interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c96ffb30e99eeabcd4c4a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-softwares-do-professional-interior-designers-use?-",
    "answer" : "The designing Softwares help interior designers in creating floor plans as well as design spaces easily, efficiently, and quickly. There are three main criteria for which these Softwares are chosen: The subscription costThe ease of useIs it value for money?Some of the interior design software used most by professional designers Are as follows: Foyr Neo The subscription cost: It offers a 14-day free trial. The paid plans start at $49/month and go up to $199/month. If you need custom solutions then they are available too.Ease of Use: It is easy for beginners to pick up.Value for Money: Unlike other design Softwares, it does not require a high-power computer or downloadable tool. It is completely cloud-based.SketchUp The subscription cost: It also offers free and paid subscriptions. The lowest-paContinue Reading The designing Softwares help interior designers in creating floor plans as well as design spaces easily, efficiently, and quickly. There are three main criteria for which these Softwares are chosen: The subscription costThe ease of useIs it value for money?Some of the interior design software used most by professional designers Are as follows: Foyr Neo The subscription cost: It offers a 14-day free trial. The paid plans start at $49/month and go up to $199/month. If you need custom solutions then they are available too.Ease of Use: It is easy for beginners to pick up.Value for Money: Unlike other design Softwares, it does not require a high-power computer or downloadable tool. It is completely cloud-based.SketchUp The subscription cost: It also offers free and paid subscriptions. The lowest-paContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:25:51.361Z"),
    "question" : "What softwares do professional interior designers use? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9715b30e99eeabcd4c54"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-latest-trends-in-home-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Everyone is looking to update their home, especially when the last season trends have started to fade away. The beauty of design is its ability to morph, adapt, and incorporate influences that enhance style and function. Now is the time to roll on a new coat of paint, redo your designs and add more personality to your home. Of the top paint colors, refresh the heart of your home. Here are some of the latest trends found to be trending in today’s market. Earth Tones: Last year the colour that was most frequently used was blue. However, there’s a new pattern emerging. Earth tones are trending and in demand this year. Olive green, yellow ochre and burnt orange are shades that not only bring warmth but also a connection to the great outdoors. Furniture and accessories mimic natural elements of  Continue Reading Everyone is looking to update their home, especially when the last season trends have started to fade away. The beauty of design is its ability to morph, adapt, and incorporate influences that enhance style and function. Now is the time to roll on a new coat of paint, redo your designs and add more personality to your home. Of the top paint colors, refresh the heart of your home. Here are some of the latest trends found to be trending in today’s market. Earth Tones: Last year the colour that was most frequently used was blue. However, there’s a new pattern emerging. Earth tones are trending and in demand this year. Olive green, yellow ochre and burnt orange are shades that not only bring warmth but also a connection to the great outdoors. Furniture and accessories mimic natural elements of  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:26:13.155Z"),
    "question" : "What are the latest trends in home interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c975eb30e99eeabcd4c6d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-marketing-strategies-for-interior-designers?-",
    "answer" : "Franz Rivoira Well, it actually depends on what you are looking for. And I mean, the kind of clients and projects you want to make. As an expert in furniture and interior design, and longtime communications professional, I have found that the best way to get noticed is the oldest. Word-of-mouth Everything else is just a collateral. You can have the best social media appraoach, the best website, publich the most interesting projects around the web - but if your clients are not suggesting to their clients your name, you are a dead duck in the water. So, what to do? Assuming you want to specialize on residential projects: I suggest you to begin locally. Find a graphic designer, make him create your logo and stationery, make business cards (and try to make them smart and beautiful, not cheap-looking), and then com Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:27:26.841Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best marketing strategies for interior designers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c977bb30e99eeabcd4c76"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-would-you-describe-your-personal-interior-design-style?-",
    "answer" : "Tawny Bolivar  My favorite decorating style is Mid-Century Modern. It's the interior design that defines all the compartments of my house since it's based on the practical, minimalist, functional, and one elegant aesthetic inspired by the simple and basic. When we decided to furnish the place according to this trend, so that the indoors had a visual coherence and was really a defined style, we agreed that it was best to add replicas of the furniture pieces characteristic of this style, especially in the living room, which is the most representative area of the house. Thus, we chose an Arco lamp, a Noguchi table, an Eames Lounge Chair, a Flag Halyard Chair, among other amazing designs of the MCM. Most of these replicas are found in online stores specialized in furniture of this type, such as Manhattan Hom Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:27:55.539Z"),
    "question" : "How would you describe your personal interior design style? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c978cb30e99eeabcd4c7e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-ways-to-market-an-interior-design-business?-",
    "answer" : "Suzanne Al-Gayaar One of my biggest client is an in interior design company who offers a full, bespoke interior decorating service - this includes providing clients with everything from wallpaper and flooring options to new build furniture and reupholstery of antiques. My 5 Most Effective Ways to Market an Interior Design Business: Sharing projects on social media - use Facebook and Twitter to post updates as your current projects progress. People love to see your process and showing the craftsmanship involved in your work will give your business credibility. Make sure you add successful projects to your website too, you can quickly repurpose a series of social media posts into a case study showing the customer’s original room scheme, what they wanted to achieve and how you helped them through the design procContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:28:12.731Z"),
    "question" : "What are ways to market an interior design business? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c979fb30e99eeabcd4c86"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-classes-should-I-take-in-high-school-if-I-want-to-become-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Here in the U.S., I would say you should get a broad education that includes writing, history, math (particularly geometry), and all the arts. Other helpful subjects would be architectural history, art history, physics, technical drafting, and software training (AutoCad, Revit, SketchUp, Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Excel, etc.). You may even consider taking Drama or Theater or some performing art, as you will be making many presentations throughout your education and career. Good luck! Reem Elkady",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:28:31.089Z"),
    "question" : "Which classes should I take in high school if I want to become an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c97b1b30e99eeabcd4c8b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-online-interior-design-services-exist?-",
    "answer" : "Independent companies are the beat of India's economy. From assembling to the administration segment, they are a noticeable work generator for many individuals, making their development basis for the improvement of the country. In any case, given that a noteworthy number of residents today are additionally Hyderabad, the development of business at any scale is inseparably connected with having a solid computerized nearness. As indicated by the Telecom Subscription Data distributed by Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI), India has 1,156.44 million remote supporters, (the individuals who have bought in for either 2G, 3G or 4G administrations) as of January 2020. Of these, 644.54 million are urban-based remote supporters, while the rest are country-based. Private companies that are now Continue Reading Independent companies are the beat of India's economy. From assembling to the administration segment, they are a noticeable work generator for many individuals, making their development basis for the improvement of the country. In any case, given that a noteworthy number of residents today are additionally Hyderabad, the development of business at any scale is inseparably connected with having a solid computerized nearness. As indicated by the Telecom Subscription Data distributed by Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI), India has 1,156.44 million remote supporters, (the individuals who have bought in for either 2G, 3G or 4G administrations) as of January 2020. Of these, 644.54 million are urban-based remote supporters, while the rest are country-based. Private companies that are now Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:28:49.607Z"),
    "question" : "What online interior design services exist? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c97c8b30e99eeabcd4c96"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-architectural-interior-design-institute-in-Jaipur?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which is the best architectural interior design institute in Jaipur?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:29:12.344Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best architectural interior design institute in Jaipur? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c97dab30e99eeabcd4c9d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-interior-design-best-after-civil-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Aamrapali Bhogle This is a pretty curious template wherein context of the question changes depending on what words you lay emphasis on while reading! Nevertheless, we'll attempt to solve all possibilities.  Is Interior Design best after Civil Engineering? Not really. It is just one of the numerous fabulous career options that unfold for a candidate once they have completed Civil Engineering. The other options range from Structural Design, Irrigation, Road & Rail Engineering, Geology, Geotechnical Engineering, Construction Management and Research to Software Development. What a candidate carries natural aptitude and liking for, is the faculty they should take up.  Is Interior Design best after Civil Engineering? Unlike popular perception, Interior Design is a highly technical field. And it requires an equally rigoro Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:29:30.899Z"),
    "question" : "Is interior design best after civil engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c97eeb30e99eeabcd4ca3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-a-cool-and-creative-name-for-an-interior-design-firm?-",
    "answer" : "Jack Hu",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:29:50.076Z"),
    "question" : "What is a cool and creative name for an interior design firm? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9825b30e99eeabcd4cb6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-find-good-interior-designer-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Sankett, lives in Mumbai, Maharashtra, IndiaAnswered December 17, 2020 · Author has 104 answers and 34K answer viewsHow can I find good interior designer in Mumbai? Sankett It is often difficult to decide which interior design meets your needs and lifestyle the most because most designs usually do not show the need for improvements or alterations until you are actually using them. However, an interior designer will help you avoid finding yourself with a newly built or renovated house that could have been done better because all interior designers are trained to help their clients choose a design according to their lifestyle. But they do not only take care of the layout but they also help you choose the right decor, lightning, paint colour, etc. depending on what you want to leave over to an expert and how much you can afford to spend on the project. ARNAV CONSTRUCTION AND INTERIORS is an interior design and construction firm located in Mumbai Suburb is special Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:30:45.936Z"),
    "question" : "How can I find good interior designer in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9836b30e99eeabcd4cc2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-designing-company-in-Kottayam?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Which is the best interior designing company in Kottayam? In my knowledge as a 9-year experienced freelance supervisor, I had worked with most the builders in Kottayam. I can simply say that I would vote for Suvarnarekha Design Consultants since they give importance to the quality of their service more than the volume of contracts and business they hire into. While working with other companies, I had experienced a few moments that I felt a bit awkward regarding the kind the vendor attitude towards the customer once they signed up for the work, Because I as a supervisor can only suggest to the vendor that we should be using these and that materials to these purposes but most of the vendors only try to look into the cost and work completion rather than the lasting period of that thing. This is where I would appreciate Suvarnarekha Architects and their Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:31:02.488Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior designing company in Kottayam? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9845b30e99eeabcd4ccb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-the-trend-in-interior-design-develop?-",
    "answer" : "Marketing Acanthus We are knowing these days develop the different different technology in different sectors but interior design is differ from others. So we are describing below… 1.The Ceiling Trend It is said that the color and pattern of the ceiling should be matching or equivalent to the color of walls. But today’s book of architecture doesn’t state the same. You can play well with ceiling patterns. If we talk about the ceiling trend then statement ceilings are the new one, as more and more searches are there at Interest of the same. 2. The Kitchen Trend The kitchen is not only the place to cook. More, a housewife spends 70% of her time into the same. So, following the trend is necessary in the case. Moreover, “Mix-n-Match” is emerging nowadays, without keeping it all the same. For example, painting base wall Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:31:17.855Z"),
    "question" : "How the trend in interior design develop? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9867b30e99eeabcd4cd3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-take-up-interior-designing-courses-after-graduating?-",
    "answer" : "Would suggest to go for a full fledged course rather than a diplomas which are not valid unless and until you plan to start your own business. there are interior design diplomas and certifications programmes in every nook and corner   Sir JJ School of Art offers a four year BFA in Interior Design degree. Prospective students need to have passed their 12  board exams and the Maharashtra Applied Arts & Crafts-Common Entrance Test. the four year course takes a practical approach to interior design with focus on subjects such as furniture design, colour theory and visualization.  Check out St. Francis Institute of Art & Design and INIFD...  Cindrebay School of Fashion and Interior Design (Calicut- Kerala and Bangalore ) is another premier institute which offers both Diploma (18 Months) and Degree  Continue Reading Would suggest to go for a full fledged course rather than a diplomas which are not valid unless and until you plan to start your own business. there are interior design diplomas and certifications programmes in every nook and corner   Sir JJ School of Art offers a four year BFA in Interior Design degree. Prospective students need to have passed their 12  board exams and the Maharashtra Applied Arts & Crafts-Common Entrance Test. the four year course takes a practical approach to interior design with focus on subjects such as furniture design, colour theory and visualization.  Check out St. Francis Institute of Art & Design and INIFD...  Cindrebay School of Fashion and Interior Design (Calicut- Kerala and Bangalore ) is another premier institute which offers both Diploma (18 Months) and Degree  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:31:51.239Z"),
    "question" : "How can I take up interior designing courses after graduating? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9878b30e99eeabcd4cdd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-interior-designing-hacks-one-should-know-of?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some interior designing hacks one should know of?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:32:08.695Z"),
    "question" : "What are some interior designing hacks one should know of? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c988bb30e99eeabcd4ce5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-interior-design-tips-for-a-happy-home?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the interior design tips for a happy home?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:32:27.748Z"),
    "question" : "What are the interior design tips for a happy home? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c989db30e99eeabcd4cea"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-key-differences-between-interior-design-and-decorating?-",
    "answer" : "Most often, Interior Design and Interior Decoration or decor are mistaken to mean the same thing. Though many similarities exist between the two, they cannot be thought to mean the same things as both perform different roles in the process to give a perfect finish. To understand how critically different the two are, let’s look at their scope of work: · Interior Design is related to conceptualization of design ideas, to building, to handing over of the project. It is an art and a science that seeks to understand the behaviour of people in the design process. To do this, an interior designer would try to understand how the space, light, sound and other design aspects could affect the behaviour of people and ergonomics. They also manage and monitor construction, structural engineering and inst Continue Reading Most often, Interior Design and Interior Decoration or decor are mistaken to mean the same thing. Though many similarities exist between the two, they cannot be thought to mean the same things as both perform different roles in the process to give a perfect finish. To understand how critically different the two are, let’s look at their scope of work: · Interior Design is related to conceptualization of design ideas, to building, to handing over of the project. It is an art and a science that seeks to understand the behaviour of people in the design process. To do this, an interior designer would try to understand how the space, light, sound and other design aspects could affect the behaviour of people and ergonomics. They also manage and monitor construction, structural engineering and inst Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:32:45.684Z"),
    "question" : "What are the key differences between interior design and decorating? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c98adb30e99eeabcd4cf1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-Commerce-graduate-take-up-interior-designing-course?-",
    "answer" : "Ninad Chavan Of course. What has commerce, arts or science has to do anything with interior designing. Any individual can take up interior designing irrespective of he being any graduate. I did my course 12th in commerce because my college was lazy enough to release my leaving till it was to late to submit admission forms in colleges providing BMS graduation. I did a two year school diploma suggested by my cousin, who is an Architect. Initialy I felt so stupid, because it wanted to do BMS as everyone around me including my parents were wanting me to do that. Well fortunately that did not happen.. I’ve been successful for past 8 years now. Infact I have not even completed my diploma, I need to clear two subjects to be an Interior Designer on papers. Designing has nothing to do with what you have learned b Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:33:01.245Z"),
    "question" : "Can a Commerce graduate take up interior designing course? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c98bcb30e99eeabcd4cfb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-make-a-living-by-being-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Aviva Vaughn 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:33:16.496Z"),
    "question" : "How can I make a living by being an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9909b30e99eeabcd4d11"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-do-I-get-good-interior-designers-in-Bangalore-to-design-my-living-room-and-family-room?-",
    "answer" : "Mohammed Shahrukh You don’t need to find interior designers in Bangalore. The place where you buy furniture there will always be a decor so you just need to talk to him and tell him what kind of a design u was in your living room there is the company named vadiya Pvt. Ltd. in R.R.Nagar, Bangalore you visited the place and have a look at their projects they provide best in class interior for your living room We don't use maximum space but optimum space. We understand the correct usage of a dimension that will bring out your desired vibe and feeling. From corners to spacious halls, our focus and importance remain the same throughout the project execution. Before stepping into reality, if you wish to see a 3D model of your dream project, we can help you with that. This 3D model will help you understand and exe Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:34:33.381Z"),
    "question" : "Where do I get good interior designers in Bangalore to design my living room and family room? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9919b30e99eeabcd4d17"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-we-do-interior-design-after-class-10?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Can we do interior design after class 10?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:34:49.973Z"),
    "question" : "Can we do interior design after class 10? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c992ab30e99eeabcd4d1f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-well-known-interior-designing-firms-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Interior design is the art and science of enhancing the interior of a building to achieve a healthier and more aesthetically pleasing environment for the people using the space. An interior designer is someone who plans, researches, coordinates, and manages such enhancement projects. Interior design is a multifaceted profession that includes conceptual development, space planning, site inspections, programming, research, communicating with the stakeholders of a project, construction management, and execution of the design. When talking about interior designing, one of the most important element is interior designers. Designers put in their best foot forward to make sure that people understand and appreciate the importance of the work done by them. Designers understand the need of their clie Continue Reading Interior design is the art and science of enhancing the interior of a building to achieve a healthier and more aesthetically pleasing environment for the people using the space. An interior designer is someone who plans, researches, coordinates, and manages such enhancement projects. Interior design is a multifaceted profession that includes conceptual development, space planning, site inspections, programming, research, communicating with the stakeholders of a project, construction management, and execution of the design. When talking about interior designing, one of the most important element is interior designers. Designers put in their best foot forward to make sure that people understand and appreciate the importance of the work done by them. Designers understand the need of their clie Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:35:06.515Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the well known interior designing firms in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9939b30e99eeabcd4d27"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-top-interior-design-firms-work?-",
    "answer" : "They work very hard, paying attention to even the smallest details and that is why they are so expensive. Imagine an interior design service as a digital image and the resolution of that image as the amount of work invested in that service.The higher the resolution, the image becomes sharper and of higher quality.So, the more work you put into an interior design job, the better it will look and more sense it will have.Top interior design firms work on smaller number of more expensive projects which give them more time to develop their designs, while avarage interior design firms do a lot of small jobs that are cheap so they don’t have enough time to fully develop each project. As a result of a well developed project, clients get comprehensive and fully developed project documentation, whi Continue Reading They work very hard, paying attention to even the smallest details and that is why they are so expensive. Imagine an interior design service as a digital image and the resolution of that image as the amount of work invested in that service.The higher the resolution, the image becomes sharper and of higher quality.So, the more work you put into an interior design job, the better it will look and more sense it will have.Top interior design firms work on smaller number of more expensive projects which give them more time to develop their designs, while avarage interior design firms do a lot of small jobs that are cheap so they don’t have enough time to fully develop each project. As a result of a well developed project, clients get comprehensive and fully developed project documentation, whi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:35:21.748Z"),
    "question" : "How do top interior design firms work? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c994bb30e99eeabcd4d2d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-most-famous-interior-designers-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "I cannot say this company is ‘The Best’ because each Interior Designer or Architect will do their best to bring a great outcome doing Home Interiors for a Client. I would ask you to figure out in which way you mean ‘the best interiors in Bengaluru’ QualityDesignPriceFirst you should understand there is two types of service providers: (i) E-commerce business like Home-lane, Design-cafe.,,etc.. (ii) Independent Interior Designer or Architect (Professionals) like Olive Architecture Studio,. etc., ( best way google Architect or Interior Designer near me) Quality: E-commerce business provide factory made Interiors. It will be convenient if you dont want it to be done at site (hassle free manufacturing) and definitely good quality sure does the business claim but you cannot verify. So I suggest you t Continue Reading I cannot say this company is ‘The Best’ because each Interior Designer or Architect will do their best to bring a great outcome doing Home Interiors for a Client. I would ask you to figure out in which way you mean ‘the best interiors in Bengaluru’ QualityDesignPriceFirst you should understand there is two types of service providers: (i) E-commerce business like Home-lane, Design-cafe.,,etc.. (ii) Independent Interior Designer or Architect (Professionals) like Olive Architecture Studio,. etc., ( best way google Architect or Interior Designer near me) Quality: E-commerce business provide factory made Interiors. It will be convenient if you dont want it to be done at site (hassle free manufacturing) and definitely good quality sure does the business claim but you cannot verify. So I suggest you t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:35:39.391Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the most famous interior designers in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9960b30e99eeabcd4d39"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-think-will-be-the-new-interior-design-trend-of-2020?-",
    "answer" : "We are lucky to witness the powerful reign of the Scandinavian style and light with its white or pale colors in every detail. If you are into interior design, the following interior design trends will come in handy. They will help you stay on the wave and catch up with the modern trends which have become household words in the last couple of months. Bold Colors Monochromatic solutions are going to rank in the interior design trends for years. However, their realization may differ: instead of pale colors, bold design becomes more and more popular. Dewberry Blue, Mulberry Purple, Kelly Green, etc. — juiciness and brightness is a way to evoke positive emotions and stay in a good mood all day long.  Earth Colors Among the leading interior design trends 2020, you can see a lot of color shifts. Nowad Continue Reading We are lucky to witness the powerful reign of the Scandinavian style and light with its white or pale colors in every detail. If you are into interior design, the following interior design trends will come in handy. They will help you stay on the wave and catch up with the modern trends which have become household words in the last couple of months. Bold Colors Monochromatic solutions are going to rank in the interior design trends for years. However, their realization may differ: instead of pale colors, bold design becomes more and more popular. Dewberry Blue, Mulberry Purple, Kelly Green, etc. — juiciness and brightness is a way to evoke positive emotions and stay in a good mood all day long.  Earth Colors Among the leading interior design trends 2020, you can see a lot of color shifts. Nowad Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:36:00.284Z"),
    "question" : "What do you think will be the new interior design trend of 2020? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c997fb30e99eeabcd4d45"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-popular-interior-design-sites-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Mellie Hens You know, if you copy this question and paste it on Google, you will come across tons of articles that will direct to many interior design sites. But should you really use them? You know, most companies that provide home and office interior design services are completely new in this game. They have amateur artists and cheap designing ideas that would make your house or office look like hell. Therefore, before opting for an interior design service, you should always do an intensive research to find a right firm. After all, the interior design of your office or house will be representing yourself. However, one good company that I’d like to suggest you to try out is Nitido Designs. They have many skilled artisans who are not just good at designing corporate offices, but can turn your house into a dr Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:36:31.036Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most popular interior design sites in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9990b30e99eeabcd4d4b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-a-better-carrer-product-design-or-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "R S Baghel  Carpet Couture",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:36:48.507Z"),
    "question" : "Which is a better carrer product design or interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c99bab30e99eeabcd4d5b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-images-of-the-best-interior-designs-you-came-across?-",
    "answer" : "Sourabh Kashetwar, B.E. Software Engineering & Artwork, Peoples High School, Nanded (2014)Answered 2 years ago · Author has 93 answers and 718.2K answer viewsWhat are some of the images of the best interior designs you came across? Sourabh Kashetwar What are some of the images of the best interior designs you came across? Here are some of the best interior designs I came across 1.  2.  3.  4.  5.  6.  7.  8.  9.  10.  11.  12.  13.  14.  15.  16.  17.  18.  19.  20.  21.  22.  Image source: Pinterest Do follow me for such interesting contents. Do upvote if you like. Have a nice day ahead :) Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:37:30.850Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the images of the best interior designs you came across? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c99cab30e99eeabcd4d60"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-interior-decorator-in-Chennai?-",
    "answer" : "When we started from plan layout - ID interiors, pallikaranai, Chennai has given us stage by stage consultation which fulfilled our updated traditional expectation for my home. The highlight of ID interiors, Pallikaranai - Chennai is they suggest applicable design facts for modular kitchen, bedroom wardrobe, and room dividers more sensibly. More important they give complete professional response with utmost care till completing the assigned project. I suggest ID interiors in Pallikaranai is the best interior designer in chennai. 2",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:37:46.759Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best interior decorator in Chennai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c99edb30e99eeabcd4d6f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-interior-design-institutes-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the best interior design institutes in india?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:38:21.422Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best interior design institutes in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c99fdb30e99eeabcd4d74"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-contact-Vishakha-and-Munider-for-my-house-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Ryan Delgado, lives in New York CityUpdated 1 year agoHow can I contact Vishakha and Munider for my house interior design? Ryan Delgado Vishakha Dholakia is the principal architect at SiCiDi. She is a licensed architect in India and has 15 years of experience in architecture and interior design in a diverse range of projects in the US and India. Her focus is high-end residential work and retail interiors.5th Avenue Boutique stores, luxury apartments in NYC and Mumbai, weekend homes in Upstate New York and Alibaug are all on her resume. Her clients include Jimmy Choo, ABCL, Amitabh + Jaya Bachchan, Abu Jani + Sandeep Khosla, Sonali Bendre Behl and Anushka Sharma.Vishakha also anchors the hit reality tv show on interiors, ‘Small Budget Big Makeover’, now in its second season on FYItv18. FMC caught up with Vishakha last week to quiz her on her glamorous lifestyle. For your interior design, you can contact them by the below a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:38:37.335Z"),
    "question" : "How can I contact Vishakha and Munider for my house interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a0db30e99eeabcd4d79"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-interior-designers-struggle-with-most-in-their-businesses?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What do interior designers struggle with most in their businesses?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:38:53.671Z"),
    "question" : "What do interior designers struggle with most in their businesses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a1db30e99eeabcd4d83"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-cost-of-an-interior-designer-in-Bangalore?-Specifically,-how-much-would-it-cost-to-fully-furnish-an-apartment?-Also,-how-much-would-it-cost-to-semi-furnish-it-with-basic-wardrobes-and-kitchen-to-rent-it-out?-",
    "answer" : "Sriharsha Kandi Greetings, I am the founder of FabDiz - Interior Design Studio, formally known as In-Built Concepts. I have 15 years of professional experience in Retail, star hotels, and a decade of experience as a Founder of the interior design firm. My completed projects are more than 350. I have never seen a similar pattern of cost expenditure on home interiors and any other interior project. The expense should not be more the 10% to 15% of property cost for complete interiors of the house. However, in some cases, the expectations of the design details are more, and the client looks for more excellence. According to the client’s desire, it can reach 20% and 30% of property cost too. There is a quick table work based on my experience for a better understanding of the cost of the interior we offer and sho Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:39:09.535Z"),
    "question" : "What is the cost of an interior designer in Bangalore? Specifically, how much would it cost to fully furnish an apartment? Also, how much would it cost to semi furnish it with basic wardrobes and kitchen to rent it out? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a2db30e99eeabcd4d89"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-government-interior-designing-colleges-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which are the best government interior designing colleges in india?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:39:25.088Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best government interior designing colleges in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a3eb30e99eeabcd4d8f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-beautiful-examples-of-home-offices?-",
    "answer" : "What a great question! I love home offices and I think decorating them beautifully is a great way to create a productive space in your home. Stark white? Bold colors? Warm woods? Sleek glass? Which home office style is your signature look? When it comes to matters of personal home office style, no two workistas are the same. When I am on Pinterest looking at home office style inspiration, there are so many chic, stylish, unique takes on this valuable room in your home. Chances are your office decor will match the home decor style in the rest of your home. My house is what I would call transitional. It’s a newer home with modern lines and features, but I have a healthy mix of contemporary and traditional elements. Although I would say it leans a little more to the modern side. Transitional Transit Continue Reading What a great question! I love home offices and I think decorating them beautifully is a great way to create a productive space in your home. Stark white? Bold colors? Warm woods? Sleek glass? Which home office style is your signature look? When it comes to matters of personal home office style, no two workistas are the same. When I am on Pinterest looking at home office style inspiration, there are so many chic, stylish, unique takes on this valuable room in your home. Chances are your office decor will match the home decor style in the rest of your home. My house is what I would call transitional. It’s a newer home with modern lines and features, but I have a healthy mix of contemporary and traditional elements. Although I would say it leans a little more to the modern side. Transitional Transit Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:39:42.258Z"),
    "question" : "What are some beautiful examples of home offices? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a4db30e99eeabcd4d96"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-interior-design-and-exterior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between interior design and exterior design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:39:57.996Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between interior design and exterior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a5cb30e99eeabcd4d9d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-investment-is-needed-to-start-your-own-interior-design-firm?-",
    "answer" : "Hi, I’m an Interior Designer, and I have been in this line of job( freelance designer )- for as long as I can remember. I graduated 1983, worked for different companies and different fields of Art. Anyhu, with me, all I needed back then and now is mobilization money and money for the materials that I’ll be needing to present my design to a client. Never the less, these will all be paid for after the client approves or your design. First of all, you need to have a client who umderstands what you do. You have to be clear in stating to that client - that you have a consultation fee..upon your first meeting, because this will cover your time, the effort of measuring that you need to do, and your transportation and materials ( in my case - since I’m old school)- bond papers and coloured pencils. Continue Reading Hi, I’m an Interior Designer, and I have been in this line of job( freelance designer )- for as long as I can remember. I graduated 1983, worked for different companies and different fields of Art. Anyhu, with me, all I needed back then and now is mobilization money and money for the materials that I’ll be needing to present my design to a client. Never the less, these will all be paid for after the client approves or your design. First of all, you need to have a client who umderstands what you do. You have to be clear in stating to that client - that you have a consultation fee..upon your first meeting, because this will cover your time, the effort of measuring that you need to do, and your transportation and materials ( in my case - since I’m old school)- bond papers and coloured pencils. Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:40:12.812Z"),
    "question" : "What investment is needed to start your own interior design firm? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9a6eb30e99eeabcd4da5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-theory-of-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for the Answer Request. I'm not a theorist myself, however I would say either your question is quite open-ended without purpose; or it is extremely loaded with reason. If you had asked a particular Theory {noun} of Interior Design, I would have written to you about History and Evolution of Design, it's styles and how certain concepts came to prevail over others and why. However, if you are asking about THE theory of Interior Design, it is not easy to answer in a few simple sentences. The aim of this stream of art is to create spaces which are functional, comfortable and harmonious - meaning an overall good experience when you walk into the building. In order to achieve this, different tools, techniques and materials are used, such as Symmetry, Repetition, Colour, Texture, by means of m Continue Reading Thanks for the Answer Request. I'm not a theorist myself, however I would say either your question is quite open-ended without purpose; or it is extremely loaded with reason. If you had asked a particular Theory {noun} of Interior Design, I would have written to you about History and Evolution of Design, it's styles and how certain concepts came to prevail over others and why. However, if you are asking about THE theory of Interior Design, it is not easy to answer in a few simple sentences. The aim of this stream of art is to create spaces which are functional, comfortable and harmonious - meaning an overall good experience when you walk into the building. In order to achieve this, different tools, techniques and materials are used, such as Symmetry, Repetition, Colour, Texture, by means of m Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:40:30.615Z"),
    "question" : "What is the theory of interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9aa4b30e99eeabcd4dbb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-generate-potential-customer-leads-for-my-interior-designing-startup?-",
    "answer" : "Hi this is Nehal I am an agency owner where we have been working for a couple of interior clients helping them generate quality leads and upto 20 to 50 clients every month We use a paid ads for generating leads and use social media and google platforms for advertising. The best part is, these leads are specifically for you When it comes to generating leads using facebook for interior this is one of the best ways that has got quality results for our clientsWe use lead generation funnels and a prequalification form to qualify the leads in order to have better resultsAutomations and facebook groups are used for nurturing the leads and constantly being there on their minds for higher conversion and increasing inbound flow of leadsWe provide a thankyou page offer so that the conversion ratio improContinue Reading Hi this is Nehal I am an agency owner where we have been working for a couple of interior clients helping them generate quality leads and upto 20 to 50 clients every month We use a paid ads for generating leads and use social media and google platforms for advertising. The best part is, these leads are specifically for you When it comes to generating leads using facebook for interior this is one of the best ways that has got quality results for our clientsWe use lead generation funnels and a prequalification form to qualify the leads in order to have better resultsAutomations and facebook groups are used for nurturing the leads and constantly being there on their minds for higher conversion and increasing inbound flow of leadsWe provide a thankyou page offer so that the conversion ratio improContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:41:24.762Z"),
    "question" : "How can I generate potential customer leads for my interior designing startup? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ab5b30e99eeabcd4dc1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-Importance-of-lighting-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Jack William, lives in Dallas, TX (1990-present)Answered 1 year ago · Author has 173 answers and 51.4K answer viewsWhat is the Importance of lighting in interior design? Jack William The best light source in nature is the sun. Humans have been adapting for thousands of years. Therefore, it is generally accepted that the closer the light is to the sun, the better it is. However, the indoor environment is usually not such a modest standard. Lighting, in terms of interior design, not only plays the role of \"illumination of space\", it is equivalent to the catalyst of the entire space, it can make the space show a visual sense of hierarchy, can create a different artistic atmosphere, and can also create people's Feeling extremely comfortable indoor environment, make the whole space feel warm, relaxed and safe. Now in the decoration design, apart from the civic decoration design with specific commercial functions and high-end and refined home decoration design, designers rarel Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:41:41.624Z"),
    "question" : "What is the Importance of lighting in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ac6b30e99eeabcd4dc8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-become-an-interior-designer-with-a-commerce-background-in-12th?-",
    "answer" : "Hi there Today as we can see there are ample online sites which provide the Interior designer courses online from the experts who are having a great experience in interior designing. please have a look at the Best online sites which provide the training Top Interior Design Courses Online - Updated [April 2019] Photoshop Tutorials for Interior Design - YouTube Top 7 free and paid interior design courses But in my opinion you can go for in-class training is much more beneficial in respect of the environment which includes the students with whom you are getting the training with, moreover, the faculties of these colleges are having a whole lot of experience too And getting training in an old-style is much better Although apart from the course curriculum you can refer to these online sites for better Continue Reading Hi there Today as we can see there are ample online sites which provide the Interior designer courses online from the experts who are having a great experience in interior designing. please have a look at the Best online sites which provide the training Top Interior Design Courses Online - Updated [April 2019] Photoshop Tutorials for Interior Design - YouTube Top 7 free and paid interior design courses But in my opinion you can go for in-class training is much more beneficial in respect of the environment which includes the students with whom you are getting the training with, moreover, the faculties of these colleges are having a whole lot of experience too And getting training in an old-style is much better Although apart from the course curriculum you can refer to these online sites for better Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:41:58.669Z"),
    "question" : "How do I become an interior designer with a commerce background in 12th? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ad8b30e99eeabcd4dcf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-cost-of-an-interior-designer-in-pune?-",
    "answer" : "There are such services available, on the net; too; nowadays, especially in metro areas. To a large extent, their charges are inclusive of supervision of the work till it gets completed to the (near) satisfaction of the owner; this increases their income, in this field. There are also interior software, introduced by paint manufacturers, furniture ditto, commercial software for exteriors and interiors and Sketch Up (the free version, which I have been using for about 4/5 years, now). Do remember, that whatever you do : you will always come up with minor changes (for the better !) after the work is complete ! The charge may vary anywhere from Rs 20 per sq foot to Rs 400 ~ 2000 Rs per sq foot at the higher end. For your ready reference, I am mentioning the areas covered by consultants. Your indivi Continue Reading There are such services available, on the net; too; nowadays, especially in metro areas. To a large extent, their charges are inclusive of supervision of the work till it gets completed to the (near) satisfaction of the owner; this increases their income, in this field. There are also interior software, introduced by paint manufacturers, furniture ditto, commercial software for exteriors and interiors and Sketch Up (the free version, which I have been using for about 4/5 years, now). Do remember, that whatever you do : you will always come up with minor changes (for the better !) after the work is complete ! The charge may vary anywhere from Rs 20 per sq foot to Rs 400 ~ 2000 Rs per sq foot at the higher end. For your ready reference, I am mentioning the areas covered by consultants. Your indivi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:42:16.004Z"),
    "question" : "What is the cost of an interior designer in pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b0cb30e99eeabcd4de2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-Top-interior-design-institutes-in-Delhi-NCR?-",
    "answer" : "Ipshita Mukharjii PS: Thank you all for taking out time and reading my views. Interior designing is fast becoming an extremely popular career choice in India 😊 The craze for this profession has gone to another level where you can get a lot of benefits in this field but it definitely depends how best use you can make from this. 👉 The first and foremost is the “SELECTION OF COLLEGE”…..🤔 Here are some of the best colleges for Interior Designing in Delhi-NCR JUST DESIGNS INSTITUTE: - This institute provide you with a thorough comprehension of style and design elements, enabling you to deconstruct and reconstruct any kind of style with excellence. ACADEMY OF APPLIED ARTS: - This institute help budding interior and retail designers refine their design knowledge and skills, in the process allowing them to channel theContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:43:08.071Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the Top interior design institutes in Delhi NCR? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b1cb30e99eeabcd4de9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-scope-of-interior-design-in-Canada?-",
    "answer" : "Canada is very conservative about creating new classifications of engineering. There are many degree granting programs in the US that simply do not exist in Canada for example. It is also illegal to call a position as engineering if it is not to be filled by a P.Eng. I have never heard of an interior design engineer in Canada as either a graduate or a job position and I have been an engineer for over 50 years. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:43:24.996Z"),
    "question" : "What is the scope of interior design in Canada? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b4bb30e99eeabcd4df8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-do-start-up-interior-designers-charge?-",
    "answer" : "Hello there, I am freelance interior designer and start up with charge on 25% of your budget for your home or office or salon or boutique or reesturant etc… \"Are you looking for Interior designer ? \" Me, I am Rajie Nathanz: I Live between Pune and Mumbai, have studied design at the London University and I am deaf. But that poses no problem to my communication with clients as I can fortunately lip read quiet well. Styling and designing all kinds of rooms, be it just a bedroom or a lounge, salons, quirky offices, powder rooms,or a cafe,am happy to take on any assignment, be it big or small. I have done a few projects and you will find those pictures on my facebook page.. I am experienced reliable honest and precise. I do, on my own, printing textiles for curtains, wall coverings and linens Basically Continue Reading Hello there, I am freelance interior designer and start up with charge on 25% of your budget for your home or office or salon or boutique or reesturant etc… \"Are you looking for Interior designer ? \" Me, I am Rajie Nathanz: I Live between Pune and Mumbai, have studied design at the London University and I am deaf. But that poses no problem to my communication with clients as I can fortunately lip read quiet well. Styling and designing all kinds of rooms, be it just a bedroom or a lounge, salons, quirky offices, powder rooms,or a cafe,am happy to take on any assignment, be it big or small. I have done a few projects and you will find those pictures on my facebook page.. I am experienced reliable honest and precise. I do, on my own, printing textiles for curtains, wall coverings and linens Basically Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:44:11.218Z"),
    "question" : "How much do start up interior designers charge? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b5db30e99eeabcd4e00"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-stream-should-I-take-in-class-11th-to-be-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Prashant Singh 7",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:44:29.971Z"),
    "question" : "Which stream should I take in class 11th to be an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b77b30e99eeabcd4e09"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-design-my-home-with-modern-interior-style?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How do I design my home with modern interior style?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:44:55.858Z"),
    "question" : "How do I design my home with modern interior style? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9b88b30e99eeabcd4e10"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-qualifications-do-I-need-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "The space for a good designer is contempt in somewhere between the boundaries of the Triangle of excellence. It has three edges: The edge of art. A good Interior Designer has taste, elegance and a sense of proportion. It can use aesthetical references form any period to incorporate it in its current design. The edge of applied sciences. A good interior Design knows and manage, from an intuitive point of view, physical concepts like space, light, air flows. The edge of projects. All designs are new projects. Every time you do it, you will find new unexpected challenges. All designs have to deal with budgets and timelines that have to be accomplished. You may be a good artistic designer, but if you fail your timelines or budget, you can damage your own work.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:45:12.464Z"),
    "question" : "What qualifications do I need for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ba8b30e99eeabcd4e1a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-tools-does-interior-designers-use?-",
    "answer" : "Manmohan Kasana, Interior Exterior DesignerAnswered 1 year agoWhat tools does interior designers use? Manmohan Kasana Nowadays, an interior designer must know the CAD software tools in order to be competitive and successful on the market. These tools became a fundamental part of the interior design business. Even an entry-level designer is expected to have knowledge of more than one CAD tool for interior design. Hand-drawn designs are old-fashioned and no one prefers them. It is much easier to design using these software tools, rather than the traditional method of hand-drawn designs. In addition, the output will be simply better and more realistic. SketchUp was under the ownership of Google from 2006 to 2012. This popular 3D modeling computer program is one of the most basic interior design software tools to begin with. It has two versions: SketchUp Make (free) and SketchUp Pro (paid) and also has an onli Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:45:44.627Z"),
    "question" : "What tools does interior designers use? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9bb8b30e99eeabcd4e26"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-create-a-high-quality-interior-design-portfolio?-",
    "answer" : "If you are going to college for interior design & also planning to graduate with an Interior Design Degree (which is the only way you can actually call yourself one, especially in regulated States). You'll actually spend the last year learing how to turn your school projects into a viable portfolio & that will give you a start. My final college grade was based off my portfolio. If you don't have a degree in Interior Design & aren't getting one, you can be known as an Interior decorator…not a designer...you can create your own portfolio by combining the completed decorating projects you've done. A portfolio is a compilation of all your best work so potential clients can see what you're capable of. There is actually an issue in the industry where young new designers & decorators steal photos Continue Reading If you are going to college for interior design & also planning to graduate with an Interior Design Degree (which is the only way you can actually call yourself one, especially in regulated States). You'll actually spend the last year learing how to turn your school projects into a viable portfolio & that will give you a start. My final college grade was based off my portfolio. If you don't have a degree in Interior Design & aren't getting one, you can be known as an Interior decorator…not a designer...you can create your own portfolio by combining the completed decorating projects you've done. A portfolio is a compilation of all your best work so potential clients can see what you're capable of. There is actually an issue in the industry where young new designers & decorators steal photos Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:46:00.503Z"),
    "question" : "How do I create a high quality interior design portfolio? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9bceb30e99eeabcd4e30"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-design-my-interior-for-a-new-house?-",
    "answer" : "Hello! There are several ways to improve your home interior design! Check out these tips to figure out your particular style!  1- Think it Though Take the time to sit down and think how you want your space to look. Write everything down. At this point, don’t edit what you are putting down. Anything that comes to your head about decor that you like, write it down. If you want a hanging egg chair to read books in, put it down. If you like industrial lighting, write it down. Do you like simple decor, or more storage? Painted walls, wallpaper, or neither? Go through every room in your home and think about what you want. Once you go through each room, then go over the lists again. Maybe an idea you wrote at the beginning you aren’t fond of anymore. Scratch it off. Repeat until you’ve whittled down  Continue Reading Hello! There are several ways to improve your home interior design! Check out these tips to figure out your particular style!  1- Think it Though Take the time to sit down and think how you want your space to look. Write everything down. At this point, don’t edit what you are putting down. Anything that comes to your head about decor that you like, write it down. If you want a hanging egg chair to read books in, put it down. If you like industrial lighting, write it down. Do you like simple decor, or more storage? Painted walls, wallpaper, or neither? Go through every room in your home and think about what you want. Once you go through each room, then go over the lists again. Maybe an idea you wrote at the beginning you aren’t fond of anymore. Scratch it off. Repeat until you’ve whittled down  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:46:22.632Z"),
    "question" : "How do I design my interior for a new house? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9be1b30e99eeabcd4e36"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-do-you-choose-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Why do you choose interior designing?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:46:41.608Z"),
    "question" : "Why do you choose interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9bf4b30e99eeabcd4e3e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-country-has-the-highest-scope-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "All countries have their own characteristic styles, and all are worthy of study. You want to choose a program at least at the Master’s level or better and one accredited by CIDA — the Council for Interior Design Accreditation. Andrew Gadama",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:47:00.188Z"),
    "question" : "Which country has the highest scope for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9c24b30e99eeabcd4e4e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-free-interior-designing-courses?-",
    "answer" : "I’ve recently been looking for options as well, and after some searching, here is what I’ve come up with so far for free online interior design courses: Design 101 from HGTV is a series that teaches about design in each episode.Online Interior Design Classes | Start Learning for Free | SkillshareInterior Design Basics | HowcastFree Online Interior Decoration Program by Rhodec InternationalDaylighting is an MIT open courseware course about natural and artificial lighting in spacesFree Decorating Your Home Online Course looks quite dated, but has some information about rooms, color matching, and so onHouzz - Home Design, Decorating and Remodeling Ideas and Inspiration, Kitchen and Bathroom Design is an incredible resource of ideas, examples, and help forumsI’ll add to this list as I find more Continue Reading I’ve recently been looking for options as well, and after some searching, here is what I’ve come up with so far for free online interior design courses: Design 101 from HGTV is a series that teaches about design in each episode.Online Interior Design Classes | Start Learning for Free | SkillshareInterior Design Basics | HowcastFree Online Interior Decoration Program by Rhodec InternationalDaylighting is an MIT open courseware course about natural and artificial lighting in spacesFree Decorating Your Home Online Course looks quite dated, but has some information about rooms, color matching, and so onHouzz - Home Design, Decorating and Remodeling Ideas and Inspiration, Kitchen and Bathroom Design is an incredible resource of ideas, examples, and help forumsI’ll add to this list as I find more Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:47:48.693Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best free interior designing courses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9c3fb30e99eeabcd4e58"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-famous-interior-designers-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Who are the famous interior designers in India?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:48:15.690Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the famous interior designers in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9c53b30e99eeabcd4e60"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-college-for-interior-designing-in-Chhattisgarh?-",
    "answer" : "• Chandigarh is the ever popular educational destination not only for natives of Chandigarh but also for the students of every nook and corner of t country. Even institutes with design importance are located in Chandigarh and universities in Chandigarh and one of the most eminent universities is \"Chandigarh University\". • The University has a beautiful campus and serene atmosphere ideally suited for design students. The infrastructure and facilities available on campus are amongst the best. It is a wholly self-contained campus comprising of everything that students on campus would ever require. • The faculty is well experienced and they also have a wide array of practical experience in diverse design fields, providing a balanced approach to theoretical and practical teaching. • Chandigarh Uni Continue Reading • Chandigarh is the ever popular educational destination not only for natives of Chandigarh but also for the students of every nook and corner of t country. Even institutes with design importance are located in Chandigarh and universities in Chandigarh and one of the most eminent universities is \"Chandigarh University\". • The University has a beautiful campus and serene atmosphere ideally suited for design students. The infrastructure and facilities available on campus are amongst the best. It is a wholly self-contained campus comprising of everything that students on campus would ever require. • The faculty is well experienced and they also have a wide array of practical experience in diverse design fields, providing a balanced approach to theoretical and practical teaching. • Chandigarh Uni Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:48:35.248Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best college for interior designing in Chhattisgarh? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9c67b30e99eeabcd4e66"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Hamstech-good-for-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is Hamstech good for interior designing?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:48:55.206Z"),
    "question" : "Is Hamstech good for interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9c9db30e99eeabcd4e7a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-an-interior-architect-and-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between an interior architect and an interior designer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:49:49.436Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between an interior architect and an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9cafb30e99eeabcd4e83"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-designing-firm-in-Thrissur?-",
    "answer" : "ZERAH homes, situated in Kokkalai near Casino hotels. is the one who designed my home interiors. They are more specialised into kitchens. They have wide range of designs and do offers customisation as per customer wishes, unlike other monopolies and their predefined designes. As kitchen is the space which consists lots of cupboards and all, I ask to few of my friends in thrissur, those who are into construction related areas about vendors, and I chose one from few suggested companies. The things which I considered were Engineer who assisted me was very much help full to make me understand each things and the varieties of material that they use. And the customisation they provide aswell. I ve visited finished sites of few companies and I found, more of the companies using same designs in al Continue Reading ZERAH homes, situated in Kokkalai near Casino hotels. is the one who designed my home interiors. They are more specialised into kitchens. They have wide range of designs and do offers customisation as per customer wishes, unlike other monopolies and their predefined designes. As kitchen is the space which consists lots of cupboards and all, I ask to few of my friends in thrissur, those who are into construction related areas about vendors, and I chose one from few suggested companies. The things which I considered were Engineer who assisted me was very much help full to make me understand each things and the varieties of material that they use. And the customisation they provide aswell. I ve visited finished sites of few companies and I found, more of the companies using same designs in al Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:50:07.540Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior designing firm in Thrissur? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9cc4b30e99eeabcd4e8b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-interior-designers-considered-artists?-",
    "answer" : "Like many things, it’s probably a matter of: opinion, anddegree.But I would say that they are artists, but they are not fine artists. Fine art is created primarily, if not solely, for their aesthetic, imaginative, or intellectual content. Examples of fine arts: paintingsculturemusicdancepoetry(architecture)film making*photography*Applied arts, on the other hand, apply art and decoration to other things. Examples of applied arts: interior design(architecture)furniture makingtextile designpottery/ceramicsstained glassclothing & fashionjewelry makingfilm making*photography*There may be more in each category. Some are debatable or are included in both categories ( parentheses and asterisks) . If you want to know more, read about the distinctions between fine art and applied art. And while you’re a Continue Reading Like many things, it’s probably a matter of: opinion, anddegree.But I would say that they are artists, but they are not fine artists. Fine art is created primarily, if not solely, for their aesthetic, imaginative, or intellectual content. Examples of fine arts: paintingsculturemusicdancepoetry(architecture)film making*photography*Applied arts, on the other hand, apply art and decoration to other things. Examples of applied arts: interior design(architecture)furniture makingtextile designpottery/ceramicsstained glassclothing & fashionjewelry makingfilm making*photography*There may be more in each category. Some are debatable or are included in both categories ( parentheses and asterisks) . If you want to know more, read about the distinctions between fine art and applied art. And while you’re a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:50:28.211Z"),
    "question" : "Are interior designers considered artists? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9cd9b30e99eeabcd4e95"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-interesting-facts-in-interior-design-psychology?-",
    "answer" : "Shraddha Jadhav, Jr. Executive (Architect) (2018-present)Answered 2 years agoWhat are the most interesting facts in interior design psychology? Shraddha Jadhav Interior designing is not just about making the room look asthetically appealing but making the best use of the room is very important. Few facts about interior design psychology are as follows: Light coloured walls and ceiling helps in reflecting more light and than the dark coloured ones.Using mirrors makes a small room look big and brighter.Keeping small planters in the room purfies the air and also is pleasing to the eyes.Color therapy works well in the areas like hospitals, schools,offices. Using the right colors with respect to the function makes the users more attracted towards a space.Light coloured flooring makes a room spacially bigger than it actually is.Following a common color throughout all the rooms keeps less scope for a wow factor. Using diff colors adds a spark and wow factContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:50:49.100Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most interesting facts in interior design psychology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d00b30e99eeabcd4ea5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-an-interior-design-concept?-Can-anybody-tell-me-a-good-definition-of-a-design-concept-that-will-make-it-clear-to-the-students-what-they-are-supposed-to-do-when-asked-to-come-up-with-a-design-concept-for-a-project?-",
    "answer" : "I feel “Design Concept” has a fairly subjective definition and different people understand different layers of a design concept differently. Goes without saying - this is my understanding of a concept, and yours could be totally different. And this one is going to be long. For a client, a design concept normally could be more of a visual entity that communicates on behalf of the designer. As many other people have already pointed out here, design concepts often take form of a “Mood-board” that can help a client visualize the space before it has been physically realized. A mood-board essentially is a palette of space-making elements such as furniture, furnishing, art pieces, etc. alongside aspects like colors & textures, materials, design language & style, etc. Depending upon the conciseness Continue Reading I feel “Design Concept” has a fairly subjective definition and different people understand different layers of a design concept differently. Goes without saying - this is my understanding of a concept, and yours could be totally different. And this one is going to be long. For a client, a design concept normally could be more of a visual entity that communicates on behalf of the designer. As many other people have already pointed out here, design concepts often take form of a “Mood-board” that can help a client visualize the space before it has been physically realized. A mood-board essentially is a palette of space-making elements such as furniture, furnishing, art pieces, etc. alongside aspects like colors & textures, materials, design language & style, etc. Depending upon the conciseness Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:51:28.774Z"),
    "question" : "What is an interior design concept? Can anybody tell me a good definition of a design concept that will make it clear to the students what they are supposed to do when asked to come up with a design concept for a project? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d10b30e99eeabcd4eaa"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-commercial-interior-designers-in-pune?-",
    "answer" : "Every space tells a story. A commercial space should attract your clients. They do this by understanding your business and growth plans. The spaces they design are practical as well as creatively appealing. This is because they want your space to be a pleasurable experience. I have come across an interior designing firm named Arrivae. It is a professional interior designing firm specialising in Residential & Commercial interiors. They provide services to the major cities like Mumbai, Pune, Bangalore, Ahmedabad & Delhi NCR. They have the best proficient designing team with the desired skills to fulfil the client needs and also believes in providing a budget friendly interior design solution to the clients.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:51:44.462Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best commercial interior designers in pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d30b30e99eeabcd4eb8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-books-to-read-as-a-beginner-in-Interior-Design?-",
    "answer" : "Everything you can. A quick scan of the bookseller Barnes and Noble says there are 164 textbooks that can be purchased on the subject. There are also many trade magazines available to read. Visit your local library and see if some of these resources are available in your area. Start with the fundamentals of interior design and go from there. But immersion in the subject is going to be key to your success! Best wishes to you!!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:52:16.499Z"),
    "question" : "What books to read as a beginner in Interior Design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d47b30e99eeabcd4ebf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-do-I-find-the-best-interior-designers-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Where do I find the best interior designers in Mumbai?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:52:39.004Z"),
    "question" : "Where do I find the best interior designers in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d5ab30e99eeabcd4ec7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-basic-interior-design-books?-",
    "answer" : "1) Elements of Style: Designing a Home & a Life 4.9 ratings from Barnes & Noble 3.9 ratings from Goodreads 5 ratings from Walmart 2) Habitat: The Field Guide to Decorating 4.2 ratings from Barnes & Noble 4 ratings from Goodreads 4 ratings from Walmart 3) The New Bohemians: Cool and Collected Homes 4.3 ratings from Barnes & Noble 4.5 ratings from Goodreads 4.6 ratings from Walmart 3) Styled: Secrets for Arranging Rooms, from Tabletops to Bookshelves 4.9 ratings from Barnes & Noble 4.9 ratings from Goodreads 5 ratings from Walmart 5) Love the Home You Have: Simple Ways To...Embrace Your Style *Get Organized *Delight in Where You Are 4.9 ratings from Barnes & Noble 4.8 ratings from Goodreads 4.9 ratings from Walmart",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:52:58.100Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best basic interior design books? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d6cb30e99eeabcd4ece"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-types-of-mathematics-are-good-to-know-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Matt Westwood  All the math skills used to read blueprints and measure spaces lead to another set of mathematical abilities designers need to develop -- accounting. Sticking to a budget requires the interior designer to carefully purchase the right amount of furniture, lighting fixtures and accessories for the space. It’s vital that interior designers accurately account for every piece to be used in the rooms before making the purchases, so that there are sufficient funds to cover the entire project. They need to be able to predict the number of hours they’ll spend on the job to write estimates and follow an appropriate fee structure.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:53:16.072Z"),
    "question" : "What types of mathematics are good to know for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9d82b30e99eeabcd4ed7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-will-be-trending-in-interior-design-in-2018?-",
    "answer" : "It is usually difficult to predict what interior design patterns are going to be for 2018. If you study interior design you will see that there are certain cyclical patterns that tend to repeat themselves after a certain number of years. We have tried to predict what interior design patterns are going to be and we have written several blog posts on www.propbuying.com. You can read the best realty blogs on Propbuying.com. We have printed blogs on why you need to have modular kitchens in your house. Modular kitchens are making a big comeback in houses these years. If you are looking to purchase a home, you have to get one with a Modular Kitchen. It’s not just about the decoration of the interior but people are working hard to make sure their balconies are also appropriately decorated. Read our  Continue Reading It is usually difficult to predict what interior design patterns are going to be for 2018. If you study interior design you will see that there are certain cyclical patterns that tend to repeat themselves after a certain number of years. We have tried to predict what interior design patterns are going to be and we have written several blog posts on www.propbuying.com. You can read the best realty blogs on Propbuying.com. We have printed blogs on why you need to have modular kitchens in your house. Modular kitchens are making a big comeback in houses these years. If you are looking to purchase a home, you have to get one with a Modular Kitchen. It’s not just about the decoration of the interior but people are working hard to make sure their balconies are also appropriately decorated. Read our  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:53:38.308Z"),
    "question" : "What will be trending in interior design in 2018? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9dbbb30e99eeabcd4eea"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-doing-interior-design-in-India-really-worth-it-as-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Manish Datt According to me, interior design is one of the best career options to pursue. This profession helps you express your creativity and imagination via your brilliant work. In a developing country like India, the demand for real estate projects is growing day by day. As a result, the demand for interior designers will also increase. But before I proceed further, I would like you to know that interior design is not just restricted to the decoration of interiors; it also focuses on the decoration of the exterior of buildings. As you know that different types of buildings have their unique design and varies with the purpose of their creation. Like 3 BHK apartments will look completely different from office space. Agree? You can consider this as an artful science that focuses on enhancing the functi Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:54:35.023Z"),
    "question" : "Is doing interior design in India really worth it as a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e0fb30e99eeabcd4f09"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-possible-to-do-Masters-in-Architecture-after-doing-bachelors-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Anindita Chaudhary it actually depends on your bachelors in interior design course duration and accredition and where you want to do your masters from. Indian institutions do NOT allow a bachelors in interior design graduate to pursue a Masters in Architecture. The reason is there are Structural Engineering, Building Technology and Materials, HVAC, Plunbing, Working Drawing courses along with several others that are mandatory for a B.Arch in India and thats why a B.Arch candidate can apply for a license from the COA (Council of Architecture) in India. If you have a bachelors in interior design that is 3–5 years and is accredited in India for example the 5 year interior design course in CEPT then you cpuld technically apply for an accredited or post professional masters in architecture in the United States or Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:55:59.563Z"),
    "question" : "Is it possible to do Masters in Architecture after doing bachelors in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e21b30e99eeabcd4f13"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-get-genuine-interior-design-leads?-",
    "answer" : "Firstly, you choose your company name and logo then make your social web page on Instagram & Facebook post your past work or either academy portfolio if you’re new only if you have done it well or even post some pictures. Be socially active keep giving your visting cards to people you meet. Make good contacts with all the raw material dealers like Timber, Tiles, wallpaper, hardware,bath fittings, etc. the reason for this is because there should an existense of your name in the market. Also, register your self with just dial and other marketing companies give attracting ads on the news paper that you design at a very affordable rate. Be confident about yourself when someone ask you about your work even thoug you might be think that how are you going to do ? doesn’t matter if you don’t know an Continue Reading Firstly, you choose your company name and logo then make your social web page on Instagram & Facebook post your past work or either academy portfolio if you’re new only if you have done it well or even post some pictures. Be socially active keep giving your visting cards to people you meet. Make good contacts with all the raw material dealers like Timber, Tiles, wallpaper, hardware,bath fittings, etc. the reason for this is because there should an existense of your name in the market. Also, register your self with just dial and other marketing companies give attracting ads on the news paper that you design at a very affordable rate. Be confident about yourself when someone ask you about your work even thoug you might be think that how are you going to do ? doesn’t matter if you don’t know an Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:56:17.905Z"),
    "question" : "How can I get genuine interior design leads? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e38b30e99eeabcd4f19"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-commerce-student-do-interior-designing-outside-India?-",
    "answer" : "Yes you are eligible. That’s the way, you are going to earn a Master degree in Interior design and increase your chances of getting into the industry with a support of Commerce Background. We at LISAA School of Design, Bangalore are offering Undergraduate and Post Graduate courses in Fashion design, Graphic design and Interior design. For a B.Com student, we suggest a post graduate course and most of the students who apply for PGD in Interior design are from Civil Engineering and Commerce Background. They get to know the insights of interior design and the management related subjects like Business law, Economics and Accounting. As a commerce graduate, you will find it relevant to study advanced subjects  0:00-0:30 in management along with designing subjects mentioned above. This programme not only helps  Continue Reading Yes you are eligible. That’s the way, you are going to earn a Master degree in Interior design and increase your chances of getting into the industry with a support of Commerce Background. We at LISAA School of Design, Bangalore are offering Undergraduate and Post Graduate courses in Fashion design, Graphic design and Interior design. For a B.Com student, we suggest a post graduate course and most of the students who apply for PGD in Interior design are from Civil Engineering and Commerce Background. They get to know the insights of interior design and the management related subjects like Business law, Economics and Accounting. As a commerce graduate, you will find it relevant to study advanced subjects  0:00-0:30 in management along with designing subjects mentioned above. This programme not only helps  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:56:40.269Z"),
    "question" : "Can a commerce student do interior designing outside India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e70b30e99eeabcd4f2c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-an-interior-designer-worth-the-money?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is an interior designer worth the money?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:57:36.485Z"),
    "question" : "Is an interior designer worth the money? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e86b30e99eeabcd4f35"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-interior-design-process-of-a-bedroom?-",
    "answer" : "The interior design of a room should be looked at in its entirety. First of all, Who is the bedroom for? Bedrooms are spaces to rest, get ready for work, watch TV, work or study, play, relax, etc based on the age of the person using the room. Now decide the bed design you will be placing in the bedroom. Are you purchasing a new bed, using an existing one or making a built in bed. Decide the location and size of the bed, king, queen, double, single or twin bed. In bedrooms, the wardrobe is the biggest piece of furniture or woodwork. So the wardrobe location and shutter design plays a crucial role in deciding the ambience of the room. Once the wardrobe and bed location with sizes is finalised, look at the electrical provisions in the room. It is important to have atleast one power socket on eithe Continue Reading The interior design of a room should be looked at in its entirety. First of all, Who is the bedroom for? Bedrooms are spaces to rest, get ready for work, watch TV, work or study, play, relax, etc based on the age of the person using the room. Now decide the bed design you will be placing in the bedroom. Are you purchasing a new bed, using an existing one or making a built in bed. Decide the location and size of the bed, king, queen, double, single or twin bed. In bedrooms, the wardrobe is the biggest piece of furniture or woodwork. So the wardrobe location and shutter design plays a crucial role in deciding the ambience of the room. Once the wardrobe and bed location with sizes is finalised, look at the electrical provisions in the room. It is important to have atleast one power socket on eithe Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:57:58.529Z"),
    "question" : "What is the interior design process of a bedroom? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9e99b30e99eeabcd4f3f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Anyone-suggest-me-good-interior-designers-for-a-restaurant?-",
    "answer" : "Michelle A. Smith As you stroll into a restaurant, the main thing that stands out enough to be noticed is the interior. As a client, you will mainly pick a restaurant dependent on two variables – vibe and sustenance. There are several restaurants around the globe that make a decent attempt to hang out as far as auxiliary design and cuisine. In any case, there are just not many that get the support with first-time clients walking in again. Hence, while setting up a restaurant, it's critical to give incredible consideration to its interiors. Here are not many interior design thoughts to enable you to set a decent restaurant interior.  The Main Entrance The passageway to a restaurant is the primary thing that draws in or discourages clients. Ensure the passage is well-designed highlighting the name of the restaura Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:58:17.398Z"),
    "question" : "Anyone suggest me good interior designers for a restaurant? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9eacb30e99eeabcd4f43"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-some-of-the-top-interior-designers-in-Kolkata?-",
    "answer" : "Top interior designers in Kolkata ? It is a question that depends on the choice of work you like as per design goes. If design and correct implementation of the same design from board to reality 'Estate Lookup Interiors' comes in with a practical approach to get you with the design which is sleek and not that it will look good in 3d but not in actual when the renovation/construction is done. Voted as one of top interior decorators 2018–19 in India by top10s list(Google it). Being in the business for years 'Estate Lookup Interiors' is backed up by a team of professionals to lookup after your interior designing and decoration goals with the best they can for you to select the design and let the company take care of the job when you are busy with your daily work affairs. For contacting Estate Look Continue Reading Top interior designers in Kolkata ? It is a question that depends on the choice of work you like as per design goes. If design and correct implementation of the same design from board to reality 'Estate Lookup Interiors' comes in with a practical approach to get you with the design which is sleek and not that it will look good in 3d but not in actual when the renovation/construction is done. Voted as one of top interior decorators 2018–19 in India by top10s list(Google it). Being in the business for years 'Estate Lookup Interiors' is backed up by a team of professionals to lookup after your interior designing and decoration goals with the best they can for you to select the design and let the company take care of the job when you are busy with your daily work affairs. For contacting Estate Look Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:58:36.374Z"),
    "question" : "Who are some of the top interior designers in Kolkata? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ebeb30e99eeabcd4f49"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-hard-to-get-a-bachelor-degree-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is it hard to get a bachelor degree in interior design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:58:54.443Z"),
    "question" : "Is it hard to get a bachelor degree in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9ed0b30e99eeabcd4f53"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-you-best-interior-design-tips-for-someone-on-a-budget?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are you best interior design tips for someone on a budget?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T07:59:12.292Z"),
    "question" : "What are you best interior design tips for someone on a budget? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9f09b30e99eeabcd4f67"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-interior-design-have-future-prospects-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Good Interior Designers are needed now in India. Everybody wants its residential and commercial spaces to be beautiful now and for this purpose professionals are being hired who can very well plan the space and aesthetically give the best look for the defined space. With the growing technology there is many smart furnitures coming up one should know the best purpose and space for utility. Everyone is an artist but Professionals are trained and experts in their field so people hire interior designers for renovating their spaces or making new space. India has a bright future for interior designers as people wants to restore their old heritage giving it a new touch and the new ones to blend with the old ones. Unlike traditional, interior designing does not have fixed clientele or regular work Continue Reading Good Interior Designers are needed now in India. Everybody wants its residential and commercial spaces to be beautiful now and for this purpose professionals are being hired who can very well plan the space and aesthetically give the best look for the defined space. With the growing technology there is many smart furnitures coming up one should know the best purpose and space for utility. Everyone is an artist but Professionals are trained and experts in their field so people hire interior designers for renovating their spaces or making new space. India has a bright future for interior designers as people wants to restore their old heritage giving it a new touch and the new ones to blend with the old ones. Unlike traditional, interior designing does not have fixed clientele or regular work Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:00:09.684Z"),
    "question" : "Does interior design have future prospects in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9f1bb30e99eeabcd4f6e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-interior-designer-in-Coimbatore?-",
    "answer" : "For all the people who search for the most professional and best smart home interior designers in Coimbatore, the answer simply would be Thaw Designers. Their interior firm is experienced and well versed in designing the interior for a smart home. When I approached Thaw Designers to design the interior of my home and wanted them to transform it into a smart home. I must say their designs perfectly imparted technology and beauty seamlessly into one. As I expected their work transformed my abode truly into a smart home. By having a first-hand experience with Thaw Designers I strongly recommend it to people in Coimbatore and other surroundings who desire to have a smart home interior.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:00:27.335Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best interior designer in Coimbatore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9f2eb30e99eeabcd4f73"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-best-interior-designing-colleges-in-Chennai?-",
    "answer" : "A2A Well, I am not from Chennai, so I am not quite aware of it. Took help of google for the same. Below are few links:- Interior Design Courses in Chennai Top Interior Design Institutes in Chennai, Best Colleges 2017 Interior Designing Institutes in Chennai - Justdial Interior Designing Colleges in Chennai, Tamil Nadu Architecture/ Interior Designing Colleges in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, Top Colleges in Chennai conducting Architecture/ Interior Designing courses,Regular Colleges or Educational Institutions list Count - Hope it is useful.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:00:46.292Z"),
    "question" : "What are best interior designing colleges in Chennai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9f7cb30e99eeabcd4f91"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-interior-designers-in-Trivandrum?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Who are the best interior designers in Trivandrum?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:02:04.297Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best interior designers in Trivandrum? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9fdab30e99eeabcd4fb0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-interior-designer-in-lucknow?-",
    "answer" : "Ennov8 Interiors is the best Designer in lucknow. Affordable price as compare to the other interior service provider. Yogesh Shukla",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:03:38.591Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best interior designer in lucknow? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9fecb30e99eeabcd4fb7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-easy-to-get-into-interior-design-field?-",
    "answer" : "Franz Rivoira Not at all easy, even if the field is mostly non-regulated worldwide. That is, everybody can set up shop one day, and claim to be an interior designer even if he doesn’t have any formal academic qualification. This means that you can do it right away. But from this to actually get clients, there is a big difference. What does all of this involve? First of all, you should be able to sketch ideas, and show your sketches to your clients. Second, you should have some good design and color sense, because you are going to work on that. Third, you should have some cultural references about the different styles of interior design and furniture, because you will be going to need them. And lastly, you should have lots of relations skills, because most of your work will be to establish relations with y Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:03:56.081Z"),
    "question" : "Is it easy to get into interior design field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603c9fffb30e99eeabcd4fbf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-scope-in-doing-MBA-in-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is there any scope in doing MBA in interior designing?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:04:15.165Z"),
    "question" : "Is there any scope in doing MBA in interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca026b30e99eeabcd4fcb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-most-important-principles-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Hi, Interior design principles used by every interior designer to create a great design, and who knows maybe you’ll also save some money, or start a new career !Interior designers are often responsible for ensuring that a project is completed successfully to the client's satisfaction. 1) Unity: Interior design should serve as a visual guide for a person to understand a living space, and without unity, the visual guide will only end up confusing the person. 2) Balance: Balance is only achieved when the visual weight of the elements are evenly distributed along a central axis or point that can be both real and imaginary. Balance can be achieved by three popular ways namely Symmetrical, Asymmetrical and Radial.Symmetrical balance is characterized by the same objects repeated in the same position Continue Reading Hi, Interior design principles used by every interior designer to create a great design, and who knows maybe you’ll also save some money, or start a new career !Interior designers are often responsible for ensuring that a project is completed successfully to the client's satisfaction. 1) Unity: Interior design should serve as a visual guide for a person to understand a living space, and without unity, the visual guide will only end up confusing the person. 2) Balance: Balance is only achieved when the visual weight of the elements are evenly distributed along a central axis or point that can be both real and imaginary. Balance can be achieved by three popular ways namely Symmetrical, Asymmetrical and Radial.Symmetrical balance is characterized by the same objects repeated in the same position Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:04:54.621Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the most important principles in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca04fb30e99eeabcd4fdb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-interview-questions-should-I-ask-an-interior-decorator?-",
    "answer" : "A decorator usually does not do serious remodeling. No bathroom or kitchen remodeling or structural changes. So in answering this question, I am asssuming you are using the correct term, for I won’t assume construction questions would be a part. I have written about the differences between a designer and a decorator, if you check my articles, in case you are unclear. I have also written about what questions you might hear from a designer which would relate to your question: Carolyn Robbins's answer to What questions should an interior designers ask clients? Here are the questions you might want to ask: How will you present us with a plan of what you will be doing? How will you determine this plan? How will we participate in this plan? How will both of our styles be incorporated or will they be? Continue Reading A decorator usually does not do serious remodeling. No bathroom or kitchen remodeling or structural changes. So in answering this question, I am asssuming you are using the correct term, for I won’t assume construction questions would be a part. I have written about the differences between a designer and a decorator, if you check my articles, in case you are unclear. I have also written about what questions you might hear from a designer which would relate to your question: Carolyn Robbins's answer to What questions should an interior designers ask clients? Here are the questions you might want to ask: How will you present us with a plan of what you will be doing? How will you determine this plan? How will we participate in this plan? How will both of our styles be incorporated or will they be? Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:05:35.538Z"),
    "question" : "What interview questions should I ask an interior decorator? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca060b30e99eeabcd4fe4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-Ikea-provide-professional-interior-design-service?-",
    "answer" : "Belinda Corani Makeen Osman Bill Martin",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:05:52.583Z"),
    "question" : "Does Ikea provide professional interior design service? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca074b30e99eeabcd4fee"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-some-of-the-most-famous-interior-designers-and-why?-",
    "answer" : "Interior designing is one of the best career choices that you can make in 2019. All you need is a unique imagination, communication skills and effective area management skills. Some of the most famous Interior Designers are:- Sanjyt Syngh: Sanjyt runs his studio in New Delhi with the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio. He is known for his bespoke designs and the incredible space management designs that are a treat for the eyes. She and her mother manage the firm and he is known as the face of the modern age Indian Interior Designers. Ajay Shah: The maestro of retail space designing, Ajay Shah is known for his great work with the concept of space management. He is a well-known interior designer who is also famous for his architectural and industrial projects. Lipika Sud: When it comes to the designing of Continue Reading Interior designing is one of the best career choices that you can make in 2019. All you need is a unique imagination, communication skills and effective area management skills. Some of the most famous Interior Designers are:- Sanjyt Syngh: Sanjyt runs his studio in New Delhi with the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio. He is known for his bespoke designs and the incredible space management designs that are a treat for the eyes. She and her mother manage the firm and he is known as the face of the modern age Indian Interior Designers. Ajay Shah: The maestro of retail space designing, Ajay Shah is known for his great work with the concept of space management. He is a well-known interior designer who is also famous for his architectural and industrial projects. Lipika Sud: When it comes to the designing of Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:06:12.060Z"),
    "question" : "Who are some of the most famous interior designers and why? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca0ceb30e99eeabcd500a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-most-beautiful-interior-designs-worldwide?-",
    "answer" : "What are some of the most beautiful interior designs worldwide?  Le Corbusier's Villa Savoye encapsulates the Modernist style Here are the rest of them, I do not own the pictures and please check the sources if needed: The Clock Tower Apartment in Brooklyn, NY  The Yellowstone Club in Big Sky, Montana  The Firefly ski chalet in Zermatt, Switzerland  Resort in St. Lucia  Chalet Brickell in the Rhone-Alpes, France  Converted cathedral  The Over Water Bungalow at Le Meridien in Bora Bora  The Igloo Village in Kakslauttanen, Finland  The Ladera Resort in St. Lucia Resort  The Underwater bedroom in the Maldives  The Garden House in Brazil  The Pretty Beach House on the Bouddi Peninsula in Australia  Jade Mountain in St. Lucia  The Southern Ocean Lodge on Kangaroo Island in Australia  The Tree House in Costa Rica  The Redwood gro Continue Reading What are some of the most beautiful interior designs worldwide?  Le Corbusier's Villa Savoye encapsulates the Modernist style Here are the rest of them, I do not own the pictures and please check the sources if needed: The Clock Tower Apartment in Brooklyn, NY  The Yellowstone Club in Big Sky, Montana  The Firefly ski chalet in Zermatt, Switzerland  Resort in St. Lucia  Chalet Brickell in the Rhone-Alpes, France  Converted cathedral  The Over Water Bungalow at Le Meridien in Bora Bora  The Igloo Village in Kakslauttanen, Finland  The Ladera Resort in St. Lucia Resort  The Underwater bedroom in the Maldives  The Garden House in Brazil  The Pretty Beach House on the Bouddi Peninsula in Australia  Jade Mountain in St. Lucia  The Southern Ocean Lodge on Kangaroo Island in Australia  The Tree House in Costa Rica  The Redwood gro Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:07:42.679Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the most beautiful interior designs worldwide? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca0deb30e99eeabcd5012"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-institute-in-Kerala-to-study-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "TEN TIPS FOR CHOOSING THE BEST INTERIOR DESIGN COLLEGE  It is that month of the year- admissions are open across various colleges that have a variety of courses to offer. Once you have decided to study interior design, it is very important to secure a seat in a premium college that offers world class education. This applies to Interior Design as well. Read on the following tips to understand how you can select the best college to study interior design. EXPERIENCE MATTERS! Once you have shortlisted some colleges, the first thing you should look for is their field experience. Years add quality to the services and an established college is a sure way to a successful career.APPROACH TO THE COURSE. Interior design is a course which relies heavily on practical or hands-on sessions as well as theoryContinue Reading TEN TIPS FOR CHOOSING THE BEST INTERIOR DESIGN COLLEGE  It is that month of the year- admissions are open across various colleges that have a variety of courses to offer. Once you have decided to study interior design, it is very important to secure a seat in a premium college that offers world class education. This applies to Interior Design as well. Read on the following tips to understand how you can select the best college to study interior design. EXPERIENCE MATTERS! Once you have shortlisted some colleges, the first thing you should look for is their field experience. Years add quality to the services and an established college is a sure way to a successful career.APPROACH TO THE COURSE. Interior design is a course which relies heavily on practical or hands-on sessions as well as theoryContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:07:58.559Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best institute in Kerala to study interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca0fdb30e99eeabcd501e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-good-distance-education-courses-available-in-India-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "With my views, Interior designing is more about experience rather than a course. Books and classroom training is just 30% of this journey. (Assuming there is no Interior designing institute available at your place locally) If you are looking for a correspondence course, I would rather suggest to gain knowledge for 2–3 months from resources like a local carpenter shop and various youtube channels available. They will give you a very good experience and practical knowledge. Later try to join an architect or a firm as assistant for a year. And then its all about your imagination to convert set of walls into a beautiful space. Final line, Correspondence course in this field may not be a good idea.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:08:29.593Z"),
    "question" : "What are the good distance education courses available in India for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca111b30e99eeabcd5024"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-design-companies-in-dubai?-",
    "answer" : "GDM Interiors is one of the best interior design companies in Dubai. They are well know for their disciplined and timely project completions. GDM Interiors has been established as one of the premier fit out companies and specialist joinery manufacturers in Dubai for over 40 years. From humble beginnings the company has now grown into a technologically ultra-modern factory of over 30,000 sq.ft. GDM Interiors provides a comprehensive turn-key interior solution to your space from designing to execution and every step in between. Our creative Designers and Engineers have a vast knowledge of managing complex projects, linking the many aspects of building work together including concrete, glass fabrications, metal fabrications as well as joinery. We are forever striving to exceed our customers’ exp Continue Reading GDM Interiors is one of the best interior design companies in Dubai. They are well know for their disciplined and timely project completions. GDM Interiors has been established as one of the premier fit out companies and specialist joinery manufacturers in Dubai for over 40 years. From humble beginnings the company has now grown into a technologically ultra-modern factory of over 30,000 sq.ft. GDM Interiors provides a comprehensive turn-key interior solution to your space from designing to execution and every step in between. Our creative Designers and Engineers have a vast knowledge of managing complex projects, linking the many aspects of building work together including concrete, glass fabrications, metal fabrications as well as joinery. We are forever striving to exceed our customers’ exp Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:08:49.907Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior design companies in dubai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca123b30e99eeabcd502e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-interior-designers-get-Great-job-opportunity?-",
    "answer" : "Yes sure. Interior designers have huge scope now a days. Once you develop your design and execution skills then you can start working with renowned companies and designers You can work at design consultancies working on projects ranging from home interior to corporate design. There is a revolution going on in the interior industry where e-commerce interior design companies are offering great opportunities to work and grow. There are also opportunities in retail companies like Tesco, reliance for interior designers where you can work in more aggressive and fast track market. If you have the passion to design and can work hard to achieve your projects goals then interior designing is the field for you. For more architecture and interior design related ideas, visit my blog DzignChakra : Design simp Continue Reading Yes sure. Interior designers have huge scope now a days. Once you develop your design and execution skills then you can start working with renowned companies and designers You can work at design consultancies working on projects ranging from home interior to corporate design. There is a revolution going on in the interior industry where e-commerce interior design companies are offering great opportunities to work and grow. There are also opportunities in retail companies like Tesco, reliance for interior designers where you can work in more aggressive and fast track market. If you have the passion to design and can work hard to achieve your projects goals then interior designing is the field for you. For more architecture and interior design related ideas, visit my blog DzignChakra : Design simp Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:09:07.801Z"),
    "question" : "Can interior designers get Great job opportunity? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca135b30e99eeabcd5034"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-a-successful-career-path-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Brian Durance  What would be a successful career path in Interior Design First you should love it with passion not just like it.Invest time.. By employing yourself to a famous, renowned interior firm in your country.. Coz experience can't be bought but is an actual process journey.. for you to be able to honed the artist or designer in you.Put up your own firm once you have establish a name/turf. Good Luck!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:09:25.954Z"),
    "question" : "What would be a successful career path in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca192b30e99eeabcd5056"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-luxury-hotels-Interior-Designers?-",
    "answer" : "Ashleys Interior The Ashleys definitely come in the category of best Leisure hotel interior designers. They have designed many budget hotels, business hotels, cafes, Fine dining restaurants. Ashleys have executed every project handed to them flawlessly. Ashley's signature style always gives away the best designs ever. They strive to advance minimalist background, devising drama and eye-catching contrast against the decor elements. Ashleys believes in adding importance to space by creating designs more prolific, and valuable marketing tools, rather than capital investments. They surely know about making their designs exceeding the parameters, concerning a variety of other project prototypes. Ashleys works to devise the correct vibe by designing the perfect decor. They conceive hotel interior design with a gr Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:10:58.614Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best luxury hotels Interior Designers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca1bbb30e99eeabcd5064"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-fees-for-an-interior-designing-course?-",
    "answer" : "InteriorDesign Edu Admin  There are various factors that determine the fee structure. This includes the softwares that are taught, course duration , materials and stationery (if provided) and the taxes ofcourse. It widely varies for every institution based on their curriculum and faculty too. It's is tough to put a common fee tag for the course.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:11:39.170Z"),
    "question" : "What are the fees for an interior designing course? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca1e4b30e99eeabcd5074"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-Noida-best-and-Top-interior-designers?-",
    "answer" : "Taruna TejwaniAnswered 1 year agoWho are the Noida best and Top interior designers? Taruna Tejwani Finding a decent interior decorators is a really tough job and I had nightmares with at least 4 people before I found Chandra Interiors and Construction. These guys are 40 years into the business and are very clear about what and how they are doing their job. I got my 3200sq.ft floor renovated and after being troubled for 2 and a half month I met Mr. Sarthak Gupta who was very clear in what needs to be done and how. We were given 3d designs and finally I could see was I was about to get before execution. I would really recommend anyone looking for a good interior or construction company to go for chandra interiors and construction.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:12:20.220Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the Noida best and Top interior designers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca230b30e99eeabcd508a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What’s-a-fair-price-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Shortest Asnwer: “Fair is whatever fits in your budget and suits your needs.” I am not a professional interior designer at all but as far as i know there is nothing like fair price until unless you can’t afford it because the price vary from designer to designer or company to company. But what you can do to not to cross your budget is make a proper list of what you need and what you don’t need because this will save you a lot more than what you expect. It also depends on the area which you want to decorate/design as designers will charge you according to the space if it’s a single room then it will cost you little less but if it’s your entire house then it can cost you more. it depends! Always keep in mind when searching for a interior designer that don’t just stuck to one designer in the mark Continue Reading Shortest Asnwer: “Fair is whatever fits in your budget and suits your needs.” I am not a professional interior designer at all but as far as i know there is nothing like fair price until unless you can’t afford it because the price vary from designer to designer or company to company. But what you can do to not to cross your budget is make a proper list of what you need and what you don’t need because this will save you a lot more than what you expect. It also depends on the area which you want to decorate/design as designers will charge you according to the space if it’s a single room then it will cost you little less but if it’s your entire house then it can cost you more. it depends! Always keep in mind when searching for a interior designer that don’t just stuck to one designer in the mark Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:13:36.309Z"),
    "question" : "What’s a fair price for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca243b30e99eeabcd5090"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-necessary-for-an-interior-designer-to-learn-Vastu?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is it necessary for an interior designer to learn Vastu?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:13:55.222Z"),
    "question" : "Is it necessary for an interior designer to learn Vastu? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca266b30e99eeabcd509f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-your-favorite-style-of-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is your favorite style of interior design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:14:30.290Z"),
    "question" : "What is your favorite style of interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca276b30e99eeabcd50a5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-common-mistakes-when-hiring-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "The relationship between an Interior designer and the client is critical. You will be together in the case of a remodel for up to a year. I have had clients take 7 years to finish design projects. there are many variables in that time table. Sometimes the budget has to be stretched over long periods. or in the case of construction there can be delays,. The fist thing you need to do is have an honest discussion with your designer about timelines. when you have an idea of how long it will take to get custom furniture, a plan for how you will function in your home during the remodel, and an idea of what is expected of you the design will go much smoother. i like to meet with my clients and make sure that I understand the direction that we as a team are going. i keep my clients involved in the  Continue Reading The relationship between an Interior designer and the client is critical. You will be together in the case of a remodel for up to a year. I have had clients take 7 years to finish design projects. there are many variables in that time table. Sometimes the budget has to be stretched over long periods. or in the case of construction there can be delays,. The fist thing you need to do is have an honest discussion with your designer about timelines. when you have an idea of how long it will take to get custom furniture, a plan for how you will function in your home during the remodel, and an idea of what is expected of you the design will go much smoother. i like to meet with my clients and make sure that I understand the direction that we as a team are going. i keep my clients involved in the  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:14:46.793Z"),
    "question" : "What are common mistakes when hiring an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca285b30e99eeabcd50ac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-interior-designers-cheat?-",
    "answer" : "So many times, we start discussions with guys who seem to give great prices and top it off with factory finish jargon. It just seems too good and we go for it blindly. Today in Prestige Lakeside Habitat, Bangalore, we met a real life fellow who was giving just things which were hand made in another place instead of being factory made with substandard material and passing it off to his clients as factory finish.Here is a small update on that. Sorry for the sound. Connect to link below to avoid the beginning sound at least. #FactoryInterior #ModularInterior",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:15:01.653Z"),
    "question" : "Do interior designers cheat? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca295b30e99eeabcd50b5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-find-good-interior-designs-for-small-areas?-",
    "answer" : "Hi...I agree with Gretchen on Apartment Therapy...and IKEA is always a good backup for small space ideas. You can also check out Decorilla which has professional interior designers who can give you various design concept ideas at an affordable price. Check out this small NY loft space designed. Easy online decorating transformation! Good luck! Annie Wang",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:15:17.699Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I find good interior designs for small areas? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca2a7b30e99eeabcd50ba"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-Instagram-accounts-to-follow-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Here is a list of the top 10 interior designers to follow on Instagram for some real and easy-to-apply design inspirations: 1) @inspire_me_home_decor As the name suggests, this Instagram account showcases home décor inspiration from different designers and architects worldwide. Curated by design expert Farah Merhi, the account features some cool DIY ideas and the latest interior décor trends. 2) @em_henderson An interior designer by profession and passion, Emily Henderson’s Instagram account features stunning pictures of home interiors designed by her. The New York Times bestselling author of STYLED also gives you plenty of tips and tricks you can apply to your home. 3) @hem_inspiration Looking for inspiration for a particular room? This account will give you luxurious yet pocket-friendly decor  Continue Reading Here is a list of the top 10 interior designers to follow on Instagram for some real and easy-to-apply design inspirations: 1) @inspire_me_home_decor As the name suggests, this Instagram account showcases home décor inspiration from different designers and architects worldwide. Curated by design expert Farah Merhi, the account features some cool DIY ideas and the latest interior décor trends. 2) @em_henderson An interior designer by profession and passion, Emily Henderson’s Instagram account features stunning pictures of home interiors designed by her. The New York Times bestselling author of STYLED also gives you plenty of tips and tricks you can apply to your home. 3) @hem_inspiration Looking for inspiration for a particular room? This account will give you luxurious yet pocket-friendly decor  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:15:35.005Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best Instagram accounts to follow for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca2b5b30e99eeabcd50c3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-call-myself-interior-designer-without-any-diploma?-",
    "answer" : "Brandon Cole, M.S. Architecture, Kansas State University (2020)Answered 4 years ago · Author has 135 answers and 251.7K answer viewsCan I call myself interior designer without any diploma? Brandon Cole If you're in America, I’be never seen it stop someone. Most the stars on HGTV I believe don’t have diplomas. The thing about being an interior designer though is the extent to what they can do is pretty small without an architect and engineer. Interior design cannot change the structure, if you want to mess with your houses structural supports then you’ll have to get it cleared by an architect, who will talk to an engineer. It's illegal to remove structural supports without someone with certification signing off on it. That being said, interior design, although only a cosmetic field, can be a fun one! Even though you require an architect that only means their name is on the blueprints. You still get to design as long as it's safe! If you think you hav a talent for it, try it! Worst case scen Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:15:49.843Z"),
    "question" : "Can I call myself interior designer without any diploma? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca2f1b30e99eeabcd50d7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-would-you-attract-clients-to-an-interior-design-firm?-",
    "answer" : "Ken Lewis Your grouping of Google PPC (Adwords) and Facebook ads together feels inherently misplaced. Google is a search engine.  People go there with questions. Facebook is a social space.  People go there to connect to people  & causes, and to be in the loop (get news). While Google sounds like it would be the better option for interior design firms, from my years of experience I have found the opposite to be true.  We get better results with Facebook ads. It actually is hard to track and measure- unless you want to set-up separate tracking phone numbers for each channel.  Otherwise, people will simply say \"I found you on the Internet.\"  (This is the disadvantage of not being e-commerce with clearly tracked conversions). But, our clients report that Facebook leads convert more than Google Adwords leads Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:16:49.671Z"),
    "question" : "How would you attract clients to an interior design firm? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca302b30e99eeabcd50de"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-money-do-interior-designers-make-a-year?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:17:06.188Z"),
    "question" : "How much money do interior designers make a year? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca313b30e99eeabcd50e8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-cost-of-an-interior-designer-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "Cost of an interior designer means you want to know the fee a designer charges for the design. Right? It totally depends from one designer to another. From The fresher and the experienced also. If you are looking for just designs you'll be charged accordingly and if you want your designer to complete the work under supervision, you'll be charged that way. The charges of a designer depends on the kind of design you expect from the designer. It depends on your demand of work. As a designer has to put the effort accordingly and you will be charged accordingly. A very Basic design of an designer can start from Rs. 2000/- per design from a normal experienced designer for a room (in detail) or for the layout of your house basic 2–3bhk. It all varies from person to person. So choose wisely. Hope this h Continue Reading Cost of an interior designer means you want to know the fee a designer charges for the design. Right? It totally depends from one designer to another. From The fresher and the experienced also. If you are looking for just designs you'll be charged accordingly and if you want your designer to complete the work under supervision, you'll be charged that way. The charges of a designer depends on the kind of design you expect from the designer. It depends on your demand of work. As a designer has to put the effort accordingly and you will be charged accordingly. A very Basic design of an designer can start from Rs. 2000/- per design from a normal experienced designer for a room (in detail) or for the layout of your house basic 2–3bhk. It all varies from person to person. So choose wisely. Hope this h Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:17:23.254Z"),
    "question" : "What is the cost of an interior designer in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca322b30e99eeabcd50ed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-interior-design-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Alok Kumar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:17:38.511Z"),
    "question" : "What is interior design technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca354b30e99eeabcd50ff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-interior-designers-afraid-of-the-most?-",
    "answer" : "I don't think there is a quick or easy answer. I've been in the Interior Design industry for 17 year's & the thing's that I see most designer's stress over & that I have experienced…that can make you wide eyed & looking for red flags…or the other shoe to drop…are this. Client's who won't pay you or you have to keep reminding them to pay you. What's worse is when they tell you they have money but they like to get thing's for cheap. If they tell you this before your initial visit, then you are not their designer. If they tell you after that initial visit, you are going to be struggling the whole time you work with them proving your value & getting paid. This mentality is scarcity mindset…partnered with entitlement. This can go along with client's who don't pay…yet it can be a separate issue. I Continue Reading I don't think there is a quick or easy answer. I've been in the Interior Design industry for 17 year's & the thing's that I see most designer's stress over & that I have experienced…that can make you wide eyed & looking for red flags…or the other shoe to drop…are this. Client's who won't pay you or you have to keep reminding them to pay you. What's worse is when they tell you they have money but they like to get thing's for cheap. If they tell you this before your initial visit, then you are not their designer. If they tell you after that initial visit, you are going to be struggling the whole time you work with them proving your value & getting paid. This mentality is scarcity mindset…partnered with entitlement. This can go along with client's who don't pay…yet it can be a separate issue. I Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:18:28.850Z"),
    "question" : "What are interior designers afraid of the most? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca366b30e99eeabcd5104"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-interior-designers-in-San-Francisco?-",
    "answer" : "Whitney M Bouck, COO at HelloSign and home cookAnswered 10 years ago · Author has 149 answers and 434.3K answer viewsWho are the best interior designers in San Francisco? Whitney M Bouck The best course of action is to look at several designers' web sites on line, and only contact those that have done projects that appeal to your preferred aesthetic.  Talk to them and interview to see how they approach design, have them walk you through their portfolio and see if their style of interaction works for you.  We did this with our designer a couple of years ago and still work with him regularly to do small projects to augment the larger one we did initially.  He's fantastic, and I can't recommend him highly enough...Charles de Lisle, of CDL Workshop. You can check him out at http://cdlworkshop.com/. Funny story, but when we first talked with him (among several others we were interviewing), he asked us if there were hotels or restaurants in the city whose aesthetic we really like Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:18:46.715Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best interior designers in San Francisco? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca378b30e99eeabcd510b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-perfect-gift-for-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Great question! Especially with so much more time spent in the home this year, the interior designers I know love the little thoughtful upgrades, as well as small luxuries. Here are a few that are bound to please: Cult classic Always Pan Best Sellers | ASSOULINE - ASSOULINE table books The unique & standout Moya champagne serving set https://www.lsa-international.com/drinkware/moya-champagne-serving-set If you liked these there are 15 more in this guide to the best gifts for lovers of interior decor! The Best Home Interior Gifts for Interior Designers & Decor Lovers",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:19:04.518Z"),
    "question" : "What is the perfect gift for an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca38ab30e99eeabcd5115"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-anyone-provide-me-the-name-of-top-interior-design-company-in-Bangladesh?-",
    "answer" : "Samira Mitra Tilottoma Limited is an award winning interior design company in Bangladesh with a track record of excellence and timely project completion. They have completed a number of interior design projects for both local companies in Bangladesh and also for multinational companies. They do both residential and commercial interior design. Apart from things like home design, they also offer services like architecture, furniture design and landscaping. They focus completely on the client as far as interior design is concerned. They will take time to understand what exactly the client wants and develop an idea of client needs. And then they concentrate on completing the design project on time and exactly as was explained to the client. They also take care to keep the client in the loop and informed of a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:19:22.108Z"),
    "question" : "Can anyone provide me the name of top interior design company in Bangladesh? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca39ab30e99eeabcd511b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-entrance-exam-for-diploma-in-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "See, if you are seeking only for a diploma in interior designing then some colleges prefer for an entrance test while many of them use merit-based admission. But if you are looking for a whole 5-years course (B.des then M.des) from a reputed college like NID-Ahmedabad or NIFT then you do have to give an entrance exam for sure. I hope it helped you. Mayank Mishra",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:19:38.202Z"),
    "question" : "Is there any entrance exam for diploma in interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca3afb30e99eeabcd5123"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-interior-design-a-dying-profession?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Rose Dc 2",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:19:59.797Z"),
    "question" : "Is interior design a dying profession? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca3dbb30e99eeabcd5131"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-interior-designer-in-Ahmedabad?-",
    "answer" : "I have come across an interior design firm named Arrivae. The spaces they design are practical as well as aesthetically appealing. They provide professional and latest technology integrated services to design and decorate your home and office. They have the best proficient designing team with the desired skills to fulfill the client needs and also believes in providing a budget friendly interior design solution to the clients. The location, the density and the scale of the project could be anything. They spend a lot of time and energy into understanding the lifestyle and the culture of the occupants who are going to inhabit that space. It provides services to the major cities like Mumbai, Pune, Ahmedabad, Bangalore and Delhi NCR etc.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:20:43.092Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best interior designer in Ahmedabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca40cb30e99eeabcd5147"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-tips-for-those-starting-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Arav Somani, lives in Mumbai, Maharashtra, IndiaAnswered 3 years agoWhat are tips for those starting interior design? Arav Somani Interior designing provides one with the canvas to paint the creative imaginations of the mind. Wherein, one can go experimental and create a captivating space, transform the home or any kind of space into a beautiful place where anyone would love to stay. That’s the magic of an interior designer!! SO, its obviously awesome. Now when someone really into this job then it implies that one has the passion for “Interior Designing”. And when someone loves their job it can never be stressful. If one has such notion then its better to realise your real choice, the job which inspires you to create something new each day.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:21:32.822Z"),
    "question" : "What are tips for those starting interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca41db30e99eeabcd514d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-do-interior-designers-make-on-Decorist-and-Homepolish?-",
    "answer" : "Hi Claudia, I am afraid I genuinely have no idea. I have wondered myself given the low costs of the service. If you try and think it through - the owners of the site and trademark need to take a cut. I m guessing anything in the region of 10–20%? Then it depends on the job, how the designer works, and how slow or fast and efficient they are in creating mood boards, using photoshop, sourcing products etc. I mean what is the final hourly rate per project…it is anyones guess. I suppose most of these companies allow the designers to also keep any profit made on trade discounts if this is the way they operate. I do e-design and pass most of the discount onto clients, only keeping a small amount, as this allows me to keep my actual per room fees to a minimum whilst still saving the client money  Continue Reading Hi Claudia, I am afraid I genuinely have no idea. I have wondered myself given the low costs of the service. If you try and think it through - the owners of the site and trademark need to take a cut. I m guessing anything in the region of 10–20%? Then it depends on the job, how the designer works, and how slow or fast and efficient they are in creating mood boards, using photoshop, sourcing products etc. I mean what is the final hourly rate per project…it is anyones guess. I suppose most of these companies allow the designers to also keep any profit made on trade discounts if this is the way they operate. I do e-design and pass most of the discount onto clients, only keeping a small amount, as this allows me to keep my actual per room fees to a minimum whilst still saving the client money  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:21:49.201Z"),
    "question" : "How much do interior designers make on Decorist and Homepolish? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca430b30e99eeabcd5157"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-type-of-licence-is-required-for-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Not in India, no. However, a businessman/businesswoman needs to have a license for running the business. So, if an interior designer is running their own business and has their own firm, they need to have a license and a GST number. That is regardless of the profession one is in. However, an interior designer working a full-time job or a freelance interior designer does not need to have any license to practice in their profession.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:22:08.726Z"),
    "question" : "What type of licence is required for an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca47bb30e99eeabcd516f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-interior-design-fall-under-architecture?-",
    "answer" : "Ayman Anthony Thompson, studied Architecture at New York Institute of TechnologyUpdated 3 years ago · Author has 248 answers and 813.1K answer viewsDoes interior design fall under architecture? Ayman Anthony Thompson Short answer Yes. Detailed answer, No. Think of it like this, everything falls under architecture; structure, MEP, interiors etc. Why? Because: All of the design teams report back to the architect who integrates everythingAt one point in time (for a very, very long time) Architecture was one discipline entailing everything, even construction. That was until the invention of the “general contractor” around 1700s.Also consider this important principal: An architect can do interior design, but an interior designer cannot do architecture. Not to say there are not exceptions to this.So the reality is that every project will be different, as mentioned. And sometimes the architect will do both ans other times there will be a designated consultant for interiors as is with the rest of the disiplines. Ho Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:23:23.436Z"),
    "question" : "Does interior design fall under architecture? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca48eb30e99eeabcd5175"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-necessary-to-hold-a-degree-in-interior-design-to-start-an-interior-design-company?-",
    "answer" : "Angela Brady, Ph.D. Virology and Gene Therapy, Mayo Clinic College of Medicine (2023)Answered 5 years agoIs it necessary to hold a degree in interior design to start an interior design company? Angela Brady Eh, I don't know. Check with your local regulations - some places require a certification of some sort, but you can self-study for many of those. But as far as a degree goes, it depends.  Do you think you can start an interior design company because everyone compliments the color you had your living room painted?  Or have you studied design principles, color theory, architectural styles and methods, drawing and rendering, building codes, ADA regulations, materials and processes, human factors in design, lighting principles, acoustics, building systems, design history, etc.?  Do you know how to use CAD? BIM software? 3D modeling software? Can you read blueprints? Do you have a portfolio, references, insurance, and an established history with vendors, contractors, and suppliers? Can you actually Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:23:42.938Z"),
    "question" : "Is it necessary to hold a degree in interior design to start an interior design company? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca4b9b30e99eeabcd5185"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-facts-about-the-interior-designs?-",
    "answer" : "yes it is a good question . for interior designs you need to examine that where you should use lights to have all places lightened. the other thing is how you decorate small pleaces like corners of some small rooms . in this answer i am going to tell you about 5–6 things which you neeed to know. 1.first of all according to your budget you need to manage everything. then think of sources about you designs. because sometimes we got a design but it is iver over budget so keep in mind this point first of all. 2.yes, also you can list out some best apps for you interior design like : PaperGraphisoft BIMxMyPantone3. an interior would look better with a bookshelf and the bookshelf should be placed in a manner that it looks amazing . 4.for walls which are important which are important you can do many th Continue Reading yes it is a good question . for interior designs you need to examine that where you should use lights to have all places lightened. the other thing is how you decorate small pleaces like corners of some small rooms . in this answer i am going to tell you about 5–6 things which you neeed to know. 1.first of all according to your budget you need to manage everything. then think of sources about you designs. because sometimes we got a design but it is iver over budget so keep in mind this point first of all. 2.yes, also you can list out some best apps for you interior design like : PaperGraphisoft BIMxMyPantone3. an interior would look better with a bookshelf and the bookshelf should be placed in a manner that it looks amazing . 4.for walls which are important which are important you can do many th Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:24:25.317Z"),
    "question" : "What are some facts about the interior designs? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca4c8b30e99eeabcd518b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-top-interior-designer-company-for-my-office-interior-designing-in-Delhi-NCR?-",
    "answer" : "The best way to get yourself face to face with the reality is by learning about those who are already in the Industry and have achieved a great name and reputation for themselves. So, if you are also looking forward to building your career in the field of Interior designing then this article will help you to get a gist about the life and achievements of the veterans in the field. Ambrish Arora: Ambrish entered started his career as an interior designer in 2003. With his skills and the passion to restore and decorate historical buildings and museums, he made a name for himself.Since the start of his career, he has worked on a number of projects which include him working on retail, residential and even commercial projects. In 2015, we were awarded with the title of the leading Interior designeContinue Reading The best way to get yourself face to face with the reality is by learning about those who are already in the Industry and have achieved a great name and reputation for themselves. So, if you are also looking forward to building your career in the field of Interior designing then this article will help you to get a gist about the life and achievements of the veterans in the field. Ambrish Arora: Ambrish entered started his career as an interior designer in 2003. With his skills and the passion to restore and decorate historical buildings and museums, he made a name for himself.Since the start of his career, he has worked on a number of projects which include him working on retail, residential and even commercial projects. In 2015, we were awarded with the title of the leading Interior designeContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:24:40.874Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the top interior designer company for my office interior designing in Delhi NCR? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca4ddb30e99eeabcd5193"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-find-the-best-online-communities-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "We execute a remarkable project, we bring in remarkable professionals. We provide turnkey interior solutions to relieve you from the burdens of different agencies. We take full responsibility for all the aspects of designing and bring incredible external sources if required. Vadhia interior Pvt. Ltd. . They provide you the best service for decor your home or office and they furnish your place also they not only help you in decoring your home or office they also help you in decoring restaurant, store, and all the other commercial spaces. They will not us much space of your for designing they only use the space how much is required to have a perfect design as per your imagination about your place they have a special team who take cares of the perfect dimensions which is required. After you t Continue Reading We execute a remarkable project, we bring in remarkable professionals. We provide turnkey interior solutions to relieve you from the burdens of different agencies. We take full responsibility for all the aspects of designing and bring incredible external sources if required. Vadhia interior Pvt. Ltd. . They provide you the best service for decor your home or office and they furnish your place also they not only help you in decoring your home or office they also help you in decoring restaurant, store, and all the other commercial spaces. They will not us much space of your for designing they only use the space how much is required to have a perfect design as per your imagination about your place they have a special team who take cares of the perfect dimensions which is required. After you t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:25:01.814Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I find the best online communities for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca50bb30e99eeabcd51a2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-corporate-offices-are-using-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Nada El-Kadouri Importance of Great Office Interior Design In a typical work week, people spend more time at work than they do at home. This is not to say that an office should feel like a home, but it should have great design qualities that make it not only a comfortable environment, but a productive one as well. Great office interior design allows employees to work as efficiently as possible while maintaining brand cohesiveness. Employee Productivity & Satisfaction   Ensuring that employees are happy and comfortable in the office will, in turn, ensure that they are productive. This is done by offering multiple spaces within a workplace that employees can go depending on what type of work they are doing. For example, when working on a project where collaboration is vital, working in an open and creatively sti Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:25:47.361Z"),
    "question" : "Why corporate offices are using interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca566b30e99eeabcd51d1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-famous-interior-designers-in-Mumbai?-",
    "answer" : "Mumbai is one of the developed city in every sense. People from different areas migrate to Mumbai to get some job opportunities and it is definitely a beautiful city. Accommodation here is a major factor. But there is no house without interior beauty. When you plan to design your house you will need some expert designers to get your dream house. You can have some plans for your house in your mind but the execution can be done only by an top interior designers in mumbai. If you are looking for any such interior designer than the best choice would be Neelanjan Gupto Design Co. This company is located in Thane.  The owner of this company has more than 15 years of experience in this field including 5 years of international experience. He is known for his unique, smart & tasteful design work. He i Continue Reading Mumbai is one of the developed city in every sense. People from different areas migrate to Mumbai to get some job opportunities and it is definitely a beautiful city. Accommodation here is a major factor. But there is no house without interior beauty. When you plan to design your house you will need some expert designers to get your dream house. You can have some plans for your house in your mind but the execution can be done only by an top interior designers in mumbai. If you are looking for any such interior designer than the best choice would be Neelanjan Gupto Design Co. This company is located in Thane.  The owner of this company has more than 15 years of experience in this field including 5 years of international experience. He is known for his unique, smart & tasteful design work. He i Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:27:18.009Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the famous interior designers in Mumbai? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca578b30e99eeabcd51d6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-should-I-hire-you-as-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Why 3D Interior Design Presentation is Important? Interior Design Presentation By Amer. K | Expert In Architecture And 3D Design Imagination is the first step in Design!. You imagine what you desire, you will what you imagine and at last you create what you will – George Bernard Shaw. One of the most suitable examples of this statement is the 3D Interior Designing Services. It’s just like displaying your ideas and imagination into reality. 3D design service has immensely helped lots of architects and interior designers. From floor plans to appropriate 3D space representations, it has benefitted in creating a perfect scenario on the basis of laid-out design. Thus, 3d interior design presentation is becoming a standard in the interior design and real estate market due to the realistic and belie Continue Reading Why 3D Interior Design Presentation is Important? Interior Design Presentation By Amer. K | Expert In Architecture And 3D Design Imagination is the first step in Design!. You imagine what you desire, you will what you imagine and at last you create what you will – George Bernard Shaw. One of the most suitable examples of this statement is the 3D Interior Designing Services. It’s just like displaying your ideas and imagination into reality. 3D design service has immensely helped lots of architects and interior designers. From floor plans to appropriate 3D space representations, it has benefitted in creating a perfect scenario on the basis of laid-out design. Thus, 3d interior design presentation is becoming a standard in the interior design and real estate market due to the realistic and belie Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:27:36.296Z"),
    "question" : "Why should I hire you as an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca58bb30e99eeabcd51dc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Amity-University-good-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers ANKIT SHUKLA 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:27:55.097Z"),
    "question" : "Is Amity University good for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca59eb30e99eeabcd51e8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-top-10-interior-designers-in-Kochi?-",
    "answer" : "If you are looking for the list of interior designers in Kochi, these are your top 10 designers:- Lemon Interior DesignersGreentech InteriorsAllegra DesignsDlife interiorsArena interiorsTheoz interiorsRak interiorsActive DesignersPencileplusGingertree interiorsSo the above are my top 10 list for you. I would like to add more value to you, so I will give you my best choice. Lemon Interior Designers is an interior designer who provides some of the best quality works within your budget. They are creating beautiful interiors since 2012. They provide services in Home interior designVilla interior designFlat interior designKitchen interior designBedroom interior designKid’s room interior designOffice interior designLiving room interior design  Presenting some of the snaps taken from their projects. If  Continue Reading If you are looking for the list of interior designers in Kochi, these are your top 10 designers:- Lemon Interior DesignersGreentech InteriorsAllegra DesignsDlife interiorsArena interiorsTheoz interiorsRak interiorsActive DesignersPencileplusGingertree interiorsSo the above are my top 10 list for you. I would like to add more value to you, so I will give you my best choice. Lemon Interior Designers is an interior designer who provides some of the best quality works within your budget. They are creating beautiful interiors since 2012. They provide services in Home interior designVilla interior designFlat interior designKitchen interior designBedroom interior designKid’s room interior designOffice interior designLiving room interior design  Presenting some of the snaps taken from their projects. If  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:28:14.123Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the top 10 interior designers in Kochi? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca5b0b30e99eeabcd51ef"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-be-an-Interior-designer-by-self-learning?-",
    "answer" : "The title, “Interior Designer,” is illegal to use in some states if you aren’t licensed. It means you have met some formal requirements of education and has little to do with natural talent. One of the hardest things to develop is taste. It takes years of looking and seeing to develop a working knowledge of good design. Knowing how to achieve it in a MacMansion that’s long on sheet rock and misplaced mechanicals takes skill that's hard to find in course work. I’ve seen some talented people who can get a look picking furniture off of the street on collection day and educated, design society members who need help hanging ornaments on a Christmas tree. Education in frivolous fields can be a strong indication of privilege. Not every talented person is discovered and given the resources to realize Continue Reading The title, “Interior Designer,” is illegal to use in some states if you aren’t licensed. It means you have met some formal requirements of education and has little to do with natural talent. One of the hardest things to develop is taste. It takes years of looking and seeing to develop a working knowledge of good design. Knowing how to achieve it in a MacMansion that’s long on sheet rock and misplaced mechanicals takes skill that's hard to find in course work. I’ve seen some talented people who can get a look picking furniture off of the street on collection day and educated, design society members who need help hanging ornaments on a Christmas tree. Education in frivolous fields can be a strong indication of privilege. Not every talented person is discovered and given the resources to realize Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:28:32.335Z"),
    "question" : "Can I be an Interior designer by self-learning? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca5d4b30e99eeabcd51ff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-a-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "John Huerta Samiksha has the right answer. If you want the certified letters that go at the end of your name that signifies you are an interior designer you need to have the schooling. You can learn the majority of the information for free from various books or online resources but you won't get all of it and you can't rightfully call yourself and Interior designer. Here are a few definitions from our old friend Google.  An interior designer is someone who coordinates and manages such projects. Interior design is a multifaceted profession that includes conceptual development, communicating with the stakeholders of a project and the management and execution of the design. Interior design is the art and science of understanding people's behavior to create functional spaces within a building. Decorati Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:29:08.096Z"),
    "question" : "What is a interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca5e4b30e99eeabcd5206"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-interior-design-course-at-LPU?-",
    "answer" : "Tushar Srivastava Hello The eligibility for B.design(Interior and Furniture) is Pass with 60% aggregate marksin 10+2 (with English) or equivalent, subject to qualifying LPUNEST or UCEED. For a candidate, who has not studied English as a subject, the condition of English may be waived off provided the candidate in his qualifying exam has studied in English medium. For academics, LPU provides the ultimate learning experience with a commitment to innovation .students get theoretical as well as practical knowledge at the university Such as- Interior Furniture Design And Product Industrial Design Students During Experiential Learning Week. Students are exposed to real work on-site situations /live design projects in–house and external visits. Skill Oriented And Application Based Teaching Intensive exposure to practical Continue Reading Hello The eligibility for B.design(Interior and Furniture) is Pass with 60% aggregate marksin 10+2 (with English) or equivalent, subject to qualifying LPUNEST or UCEED. For a candidate, who has not studied English as a subject, the condition of English may be waived off provided the candidate in his qualifying exam has studied in English medium. For academics, LPU provides the ultimate learning experience with a commitment to innovation .students get theoretical as well as practical knowledge at the university Such as- Interior Furniture Design And Product Industrial Design Students During Experiential Learning Week. Students are exposed to real work on-site situations /live design projects in–house and external visits. Skill Oriented And Application Based Teaching Intensive exposure to practical Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:29:24.373Z"),
    "question" : "How is the interior design course at LPU? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca60ab30e99eeabcd5211"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-interior-designers-feel-about-Houzz?-",
    "answer" : "I love Houzz, I can get lost in the photos for hours. Don’t look at it and expect to duplicate the design 100%. When people don’t knw what they like I encourage people to find color schemes that they feel speaks to them. Get ideas from Houzz, then you can go shopping at a place that you will find things within your budget and find items that will create a similar look and feel. It don’t cost anything on Houzz for inspiration.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:30:02.507Z"),
    "question" : "How do interior designers feel about Houzz? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca62ab30e99eeabcd5220"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-interior-design-course-should-I-take-after-civil-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "You could take B.A in communication design as this interior designing course is involved with various types of advanced illustration which would help in the interactive and creative industry. Graphic designing is taught in detail in this course. There is also an advantage about enrolling at ITM institute there are many courses available under the umbrella of interior designing and it helps you grasp complicated concepts easily. They also make you learn different software which would help you gain knowledge that is not just theoretical but also practical. Communication design today has been opted by many because of the demand in the digital area. I would say go for it!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:30:34.671Z"),
    "question" : "What interior design course should I take after civil engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca661b30e99eeabcd523a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-one-define-‘style’-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "La Moneda De Hierro The best way to acknowledge your own style is watching and watching and watching. Watch everything, even styles that you dislike, or feel uncomfortable. In every sample you should try to find something nice. Interior Design is a mix where creativity, ability and resources are bond by balance. It's ideal to watch styles in real life and see how they look, but if you can't, internet is an excellent source, of course. Get info of what are the main trends. In the top 5 group there will be something you find interesting. Generally, people tend to divide in two main fields: classical and disruptive. The main trends right now are: Scandinavian; Mid Century Modern; Coastal Living and Traditional. For example Mid Century Modern, or MCM is a movement originated in the 1950s , and it has been unstoppable s Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:31:29.735Z"),
    "question" : "How does one define ‘style’ in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca686b30e99eeabcd5247"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-top-interior-designers-in-Cochin?-",
    "answer" : "Tony John Those who want to buy a new house, apartment, office or building a new home in Kochi always search for the top interior designers in Cochin. It doesn’t matter whether you are looking for residence interior designers, commercial interior designers or office interior designers in Kochi, Greentech Interiors would be the ideal choice. Bygone are the days when the interior of your home and working space were dull with whitewashed walls and ordinary furniture that made the space boring and uncomfortable most often.  Being one of the most trustworthy interior designers in Kerala, Greentech Interiors is known for their quality designing projects and successful delivery of the projects in a very timely manner. For more than two decades, Greentech Interiors has been designing, decorating and furnishin Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:32:06.467Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the top interior designers in Cochin? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca6a6b30e99eeabcd5254"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-market-size-of-interior-design-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Interior Designing Industry of India is expected to grow at a CAGR of around 8% from US$ 837 Million in 2017 to US$ 1,138 Million in 2021. India is expected to rank third in terms of volumes of constructions by 2030 with a target of 11 Million buildings to be constructed, therefore highlighting bright future prospects for the industry. According to the research, growth has been driven by construction of commercial and residential buildings over the past 5 years. The foremost reason for the up trends in the industry is the construction of a large number of multi-storey buildings, bungalows, offices, etc owing to rise in disposable incomes and standard of living of middle-class Indian population. Also, surging demand for good and a comfortable life has led to a high booming growth in the Inte Continue Reading Interior Designing Industry of India is expected to grow at a CAGR of around 8% from US$ 837 Million in 2017 to US$ 1,138 Million in 2021. India is expected to rank third in terms of volumes of constructions by 2030 with a target of 11 Million buildings to be constructed, therefore highlighting bright future prospects for the industry. According to the research, growth has been driven by construction of commercial and residential buildings over the past 5 years. The foremost reason for the up trends in the industry is the construction of a large number of multi-storey buildings, bungalows, offices, etc owing to rise in disposable incomes and standard of living of middle-class Indian population. Also, surging demand for good and a comfortable life has led to a high booming growth in the Inte Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:32:38.133Z"),
    "question" : "What is the market size of interior design in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca6bab30e99eeabcd525c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-have-a-perfect-interior-design-for-my-office?-",
    "answer" : "Successful office design is about comfortable workspaces that include adaptable conference rooms, inspiring reception areas, and other key features. The office design layout depends on your goals. Find out your main goals whether you are moving, renovating, or expanding. Do you want to prepare for growth, want to hire new talent. A well-designed office serves as a branding tool and improves the chances of future growth.  [Image source: The Design District] Here are some design options: Open office design: This is popular among many IT industries and call-centers. Everyone in the office sits together, including managers, and discussions flowing freely across the open space. This inexpensive design option and it can yield operational efficiencies. Cellular office design: This is also a popular desig Continue Reading Successful office design is about comfortable workspaces that include adaptable conference rooms, inspiring reception areas, and other key features. The office design layout depends on your goals. Find out your main goals whether you are moving, renovating, or expanding. Do you want to prepare for growth, want to hire new talent. A well-designed office serves as a branding tool and improves the chances of future growth.  [Image source: The Design District] Here are some design options: Open office design: This is popular among many IT industries and call-centers. Everyone in the office sits together, including managers, and discussions flowing freely across the open space. This inexpensive design option and it can yield operational efficiencies. Cellular office design: This is also a popular desig Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:32:58.406Z"),
    "question" : "How can I have a perfect interior design for my office? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca6dfb30e99eeabcd526a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-bdes-interior-designing-and-bsc-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:33:35.160Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between bdes interior designing and bsc interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca6f0b30e99eeabcd5270"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-apply-for-an-interior-design-job-abroad?-",
    "answer" : "Tiyana Marie White Darpan Shah",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:33:52.980Z"),
    "question" : "How do I apply for an interior design job abroad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca701b30e99eeabcd527c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-7-elements-of-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "As the old saying goes, “The whole is more than the sum of its parts.” The same thing is true for interior design — which is really just an illusion created by balancing different elements effectively. Think of it like this: learning about the ingredients that go into your favorite recipes will help you master cooking. In the same way, learning about the design elements that go into your favorite styles will help you master decorating. So what are the seven key elements of interior design? They include: ColorFormLightLinePatternTextureSpaceColor Color is more than just an aesthetic choice — it can also influence the entire mood and feeling of a space. For example, most people think of red as a “passionate” or “intense” hue, while blues and greens are usually perceived as “tranquil” or “soothing” and yellow is often associated with words like “happy” and “optimistic.” Think about not only your visual preferences, but also, the sort of energy or attitude you’re trying to cultivate when deciding on a color scheme for your room.  Form “Form” is simply another term for “shape,” expressing the contours of any artwork, furniture, or other 3-D object you could imagine. Furniture, sculpture, and even rooms themselves can take on two types of forms: organic forms (which are natural and irregular, with curvy or abstract shapes), and geometric forms (which feature sharp, man-made lines and edges, like squares or triangles).  Light Have you ever cringed at a photograph that was taken in bad lighting? Then you already know the power that lighting has to affect our perception! Quality lighting is integral to any space, whether its sources are natural, man-made, or some combination of both. When choosing lighting for your room, think about factors like the color of the light (cool blue or warm yellow?), the light intensity (bright for cooking, or soft for reading?), and whether the light should be dimmable.  Line Think of line as the perimeter around a form or shape. For example, if you were to draw any object in the room, you would probably start with its outline. Lines can be “vertical” (up-and-down), “horizontal” (side-to-side), or “dynamic” (lines that express motion, like zig-zags or curlicues). Design experts say that horizontal lines create a feeling of security, while vertical lines are expressive and bold. Dynamic lines, which follow their own set of rules, can add a fun, exciting touch to any space when used strategically.  Pattern A pattern is the intentional repetition of forms, lines, or other design elements. Patterns usually pop up on wallpaper or fabrics, but can appear anywhere in the home, even in the use of light or other design elements. While patterns can add life and motion to a space, too many clashing patterns can start to look chaotic, so tread lightly when choosing your favorite prints.  Texture Not to be confused with pattern, texture is the way an object feels. This can mean the way the object literally feels to the touch, or the sense it gives when simply observing the object. For example, you might say that a surface looks “weathered” or “vintage” without actually touching it, thanks to the creative use of texture. Careful consideration of texture is especially important in parts of the home that you contact frequently, like your flooring. We can help you find floors with the perfect, comfortable texture to start every day on the right foot.  Space Last but not least, space is at the heart of virtually every design decision. There are two basic types of space to consider: 2-D space (which accounts for the length and width of a room), and 3-D space (which covers height). For example, only 2-D space is important when thinking of carpets or rugs — but you’ll need to think about 3-D space before adding new shelving or furniture. It’s also important to leave enough empty or “negative” space to allow for fluid, easy navigation (and break the room up visually).",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:34:09.410Z"),
    "question" : "What are the 7 elements of interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca715b30e99eeabcd5284"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-interior-designing-company-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which are the best interiors in Hyderabad?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:34:29.295Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best interior designing company in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca726b30e99eeabcd5288"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-architects-take-interior-designers-seriously?-",
    "answer" : "Anitya Satkaryavada A true, professional, and certified Interior Designer? Very seriously. Finishes, furniture, and furnishings are some of the most complex, intricate, fastest-changing, and continually developing of the building technologies. And one of the most critical, because they have a very strong impact on what the client actually perceives when they walk into the space you have designed. And a good Interior Designer is just that, a good designer whose specialty is a person’s experience when in a built environment. I have learned so much working with the interior designers that we have used as consultants for our work - and even more from the interior designers who are part of our firm. Decorators now - someone who just picks pretty paint colors and waxes eloquent about superficial appearances - are not  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:34:46.466Z"),
    "question" : "Do architects take interior designers seriously? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca737b30e99eeabcd5290"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-mistakes-beginner-architectural-and-interior-designers-often-make?-",
    "answer" : "Urvanx Architecture While creating your own practice is certainly a huge milestone, you must be wary of the fact that you will have competitors in your field that will try to outmaneuver your Interior Design Firms in Miami. With that being said, like any other seasoned professional, just being able to do what your colleagues and competitors can do will only get you so far. Sure, if you can perform at your best this is saying something. You’ll probably be able to pay the bills and you might foster strong relationships with your clients along the way. Understanding your Why Of course, playing-to-win means you need to devise a plan to ensure that you’re victorious. Strategies and tactics are key components that will take your Interior Design Firms in Miami to new heights. Your plans need to have a specific objective, Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:35:03.569Z"),
    "question" : "What are mistakes beginner architectural and interior designers often make? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca74cb30e99eeabcd529c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-way-to-market-an-interior-design-startup?-",
    "answer" : "Anna Kovalchenko  As we all know there's no sure shot procedure in marketing but what i have learned in past one year as cmo at @houssup.com is to never sell interior design upfront ,always establish the design entity of your brand ,be vocal about the elements you follow and the design philosophies u imbibe ,from daily knowledge sharing to humor in different social media posts .When you do this the trust develops and customers come in on their own trusting ur design sense.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:35:24.113Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best way to market an interior design startup? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca76eb30e99eeabcd52ad"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-makes-interior-designing-popular?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What makes interior designing popular?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:35:58.761Z"),
    "question" : "What makes interior designing popular? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca77fb30e99eeabcd52b5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-government-interior-design-college-in-Pune?-",
    "answer" : "In short..there aren't any Government courses on this. There are quite a few institutes in Pune which have university certified courses. I would however suggest the MIT (Maeer institute) in Pune located in Fursrungi. They are we very well, funded, have great faculty and it's a well exposed institute. I’ve worked with a couple of MIT interior design graduates and found thier approach well rounded with respect to design, and at the same time pragmatic and not held back in doubt over material applicability and performance . When a college is well funded, the facilities available to students are good. These guys (Maeers) have a full fledged workshop of all materials which is equivalent to a professionally run fablab. Learning Interior design is a lot to do with hands on working in the initial yea Continue Reading In short..there aren't any Government courses on this. There are quite a few institutes in Pune which have university certified courses. I would however suggest the MIT (Maeer institute) in Pune located in Fursrungi. They are we very well, funded, have great faculty and it's a well exposed institute. I’ve worked with a couple of MIT interior design graduates and found thier approach well rounded with respect to design, and at the same time pragmatic and not held back in doubt over material applicability and performance . When a college is well funded, the facilities available to students are good. These guys (Maeers) have a full fledged workshop of all materials which is equivalent to a professionally run fablab. Learning Interior design is a lot to do with hands on working in the initial yea Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:36:15.694Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best government interior design college in Pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca7c7b30e99eeabcd52d0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-interior-designers-know-about-design-that-the-rest-of-us-do-not?-",
    "answer" : "Adding to the previous comments: An understanding of construction standards and why they are in place.the ability to design with all past and future considerations taken into account (will this flooring withstand heavy traffic on a daily basis, is this material water resistant enough to be used in a bathroom with continuous steam for years, Is this floor too slippery for a hospital, can this leather sofa withstand being next to the windows in a hot city, etc.)Making sure your design is flexible enough for MEP’s and other engineers to work with (if you’re not doing it yourself of course, because most interior designers determine HVAC, lighting, switches, electrical outlets, etc. And each of these has their own set of standards). Below is an RCP, do you understand what it means? can you read Continue Reading Adding to the previous comments: An understanding of construction standards and why they are in place.the ability to design with all past and future considerations taken into account (will this flooring withstand heavy traffic on a daily basis, is this material water resistant enough to be used in a bathroom with continuous steam for years, Is this floor too slippery for a hospital, can this leather sofa withstand being next to the windows in a hot city, etc.)Making sure your design is flexible enough for MEP’s and other engineers to work with (if you’re not doing it yourself of course, because most interior designers determine HVAC, lighting, switches, electrical outlets, etc. And each of these has their own set of standards). Below is an RCP, do you understand what it means? can you read Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:37:27.887Z"),
    "question" : "What do interior designers know about design that the rest of us do not? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca7d9b30e99eeabcd52d5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-get-interior-design-ideas-for-my-home-and-office?-",
    "answer" : "1. TAKE STOCK Step back and appearance at your existing article of furniture and interior decoration. to form area, get eliminate article of furniture that is broken, outdated, too large, too small, or {that you|that you simply|that you simply} just detest any longer. If it is a family heirloom or a bit you wish to stay that does not slot in the front room, provides it a brand new spot in different places in your house. 2. Select an outsized floor covering Choosing a bigger rug—even during a daring pattern—is a trick that produces an area feel bigger. in contrast to smaller rugs, the massive size does not visually cut up the ground. this will conjointly facilitate anchor the area and provides you a decent staple piece to style the remainder of the area around. Corner seating can even assist y Continue Reading 1. TAKE STOCK Step back and appearance at your existing article of furniture and interior decoration. to form area, get eliminate article of furniture that is broken, outdated, too large, too small, or {that you|that you simply|that you simply} just detest any longer. If it is a family heirloom or a bit you wish to stay that does not slot in the front room, provides it a brand new spot in different places in your house. 2. Select an outsized floor covering Choosing a bigger rug—even during a daring pattern—is a trick that produces an area feel bigger. in contrast to smaller rugs, the massive size does not visually cut up the ground. this will conjointly facilitate anchor the area and provides you a decent staple piece to style the remainder of the area around. Corner seating can even assist y Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:37:45.097Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I get interior design ideas for my home and office? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca81db30e99eeabcd52ed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-rustic-style-in-interior?-",
    "answer" : "Rustic Style, mostly originated from the United States, commonly seen in rural government and private structures and their landscape interior design. It was influenced by the American Crafstmen style. In the world of architecture, the style is defined as having the characteristic of rough textures, seemingly unfinished in a good way trying to be as natural as possible. During the Roman Empire era until the Renaissance, the style is more focused on facade, combined with ornaments to furnished the interiors. Some of the more obvious characters of rustics style we could see nowadays are: Natural materials with seemingly old and rough feels on itExposed atticNatural colours such as grey, terracotta, soil, black, pale yellow and of course wood brown.Usually the surface of plane elements such as wa Continue Reading Rustic Style, mostly originated from the United States, commonly seen in rural government and private structures and their landscape interior design. It was influenced by the American Crafstmen style. In the world of architecture, the style is defined as having the characteristic of rough textures, seemingly unfinished in a good way trying to be as natural as possible. During the Roman Empire era until the Renaissance, the style is more focused on facade, combined with ornaments to furnished the interiors. Some of the more obvious characters of rustics style we could see nowadays are: Natural materials with seemingly old and rough feels on itExposed atticNatural colours such as grey, terracotta, soil, black, pale yellow and of course wood brown.Usually the surface of plane elements such as wa Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:38:53.262Z"),
    "question" : "What is rustic style in interior? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca82db30e99eeabcd52f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-interior​-design​ing-job-and-its-earning?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How much does an interior designer earn in india?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:39:09.949Z"),
    "question" : "How is interior​ design​ing job and its earning? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca842b30e99eeabcd5300"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-do-top-tier-Interior-Design-Firms-find-wall-decor?-",
    "answer" : "Top tier Interior Design Firms buy at high end art and antique auctions,  They travel the world and scout unique pieces.  They  commission great artists and masters to paint or build a piece.  In short, they use original one of a kind art.  Many of us will never have the opportunity to use a top tier firm, but with a bit of careful study and a willingness to wait and search for just the right item, we can add exquisite but affordable pieces to our surroundings.   There are three questions to each art purchase....\"Is the color right?  Is it the proper proportion for my area?  Does it tell my story?\"     If all three answers are \"Yes!\", it is time to ask the price.  Think beyond the usual.  Attend art shows and fairs for a bit.  Look at scrumptious hand woven fabric for a possible hanging.  A l Continue Reading Top tier Interior Design Firms buy at high end art and antique auctions,  They travel the world and scout unique pieces.  They  commission great artists and masters to paint or build a piece.  In short, they use original one of a kind art.  Many of us will never have the opportunity to use a top tier firm, but with a bit of careful study and a willingness to wait and search for just the right item, we can add exquisite but affordable pieces to our surroundings.   There are three questions to each art purchase....\"Is the color right?  Is it the proper proportion for my area?  Does it tell my story?\"     If all three answers are \"Yes!\", it is time to ask the price.  Think beyond the usual.  Attend art shows and fairs for a bit.  Look at scrumptious hand woven fabric for a possible hanging.  A l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:39:30.179Z"),
    "question" : "Where do top tier Interior Design Firms find wall decor? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca854b30e99eeabcd5306"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-Clever-interior-design-tricks-to-transform-your-house?-",
    "answer" : "Whether you’ve just moved or are looking for a quick, little home pick-me-up, or perhaps something more significant, there are some well-known interior design tricks that designers employ that you too can easily do with minimal effort and cost. Sometimes the smallest things make the greatest impact. It could be the addition of a mirror, a painting, a lamp or even a plant. Maybe you want to soften your walls, brighten a room, or add some warmth to your living space. Take a look at these clever design tips and see how they can inspire you! 10 Clever Interior Design Tricks to Transform Your Home 1. Paint smaller rooms in softer, lighter colors to help make the room feel larger.  The living room above is a great example of how to maximize a small living space. A room of this size has the tendency  Continue Reading Whether you’ve just moved or are looking for a quick, little home pick-me-up, or perhaps something more significant, there are some well-known interior design tricks that designers employ that you too can easily do with minimal effort and cost. Sometimes the smallest things make the greatest impact. It could be the addition of a mirror, a painting, a lamp or even a plant. Maybe you want to soften your walls, brighten a room, or add some warmth to your living space. Take a look at these clever design tips and see how they can inspire you! 10 Clever Interior Design Tricks to Transform Your Home 1. Paint smaller rooms in softer, lighter colors to help make the room feel larger.  The living room above is a great example of how to maximize a small living space. A room of this size has the tendency  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:39:48.178Z"),
    "question" : "What are Clever interior design tricks to transform your house? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca878b30e99eeabcd5317"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-NATA-necessary-for-an-interior-designing-course-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "no it is not necessary you did not mention from which college you want to do interior designing there are different entrance exams for different colleges. like if you want to appear for cept SID(school of interior designing)you have to clear that exam and get a good rank to get into it but my advice would be that you give NATA .because NATA as a whole covers all of the things including design and architecture Rohan Sharma",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:40:24.091Z"),
    "question" : "Is NATA necessary for an interior designing course in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca898b30e99eeabcd5325"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-drives-trends-in-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "I’d say it’s a tug of war between commercial interest, need to create, nostalgia and desire for novelty. It start from a basic need to create. Somebody creates something. It gets noticed by early adopters, then general public. Original idea becomes widespread. At some stage consumers become bored with the status quo, simultaneously new generation gets buying power, so the need for new things will make society susceptible for new creations (which people with need to create create are constantly producing). Something new gets noticed, cycle repeats. Then active generation becomes older and they become nostalgic. So they will be looking for things and ideas that essentially return them to childhood. However, because for a younger generation creation of something new happens at the same time, idea Continue Reading I’d say it’s a tug of war between commercial interest, need to create, nostalgia and desire for novelty. It start from a basic need to create. Somebody creates something. It gets noticed by early adopters, then general public. Original idea becomes widespread. At some stage consumers become bored with the status quo, simultaneously new generation gets buying power, so the need for new things will make society susceptible for new creations (which people with need to create create are constantly producing). Something new gets noticed, cycle repeats. Then active generation becomes older and they become nostalgic. So they will be looking for things and ideas that essentially return them to childhood. However, because for a younger generation creation of something new happens at the same time, idea Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:40:56.867Z"),
    "question" : "What drives trends in interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca8afb30e99eeabcd5332"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Need-recommendations-for-good-office-interior-designers-for-startups-in-bangalore-on-a-budget?-",
    "answer" : "Here are some pointers to apply in your office interior design hunting: · Don't simply settle for aesthetics While you may think an aesthetically designed workplace can motivate your employees, the fact is it is not the only most important thing in the world of worker efficiency or representative satisfaction. Set aside some effort to ponder the sort of culture, qualities, ability, and procedures that characterizes your association and fuse these variables into the general look of your office. · Go for flexibility in employee and organizational levels With an increasing shift toward flexible working conditions, you could focus on utilizing your office space to serve both the needs of your employees and your company. For your employees, having flexible working areas means they can easily move int Continue Reading Here are some pointers to apply in your office interior design hunting: · Don't simply settle for aesthetics While you may think an aesthetically designed workplace can motivate your employees, the fact is it is not the only most important thing in the world of worker efficiency or representative satisfaction. Set aside some effort to ponder the sort of culture, qualities, ability, and procedures that characterizes your association and fuse these variables into the general look of your office. · Go for flexibility in employee and organizational levels With an increasing shift toward flexible working conditions, you could focus on utilizing your office space to serve both the needs of your employees and your company. For your employees, having flexible working areas means they can easily move int Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:41:19.865Z"),
    "question" : "Need recommendations for good office interior designers for startups in bangalore on a budget? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca8d3b30e99eeabcd533d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-interior-designing-service-providers-in-Perth?-",
    "answer" : "Design the kitchen of your dreams with The Makers Designer Kitchens, Australia’s most awarded interior kitchen designer. Specialising in innovative and modern kitchen designs, the team provides personalised service and custom designs a kitchen to suit your individual needs. You will be guided by our in-house design team as well as a Site Coordinator to make the process of designing and renovating your dream kitchen as smoothly and stress-free as possible. To know more about services click here →Classic Style Kitchen Designs | The Maker Samir Ranjan Tudu",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:41:55.980Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best interior designing service providers in Perth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca8e4b30e99eeabcd5346"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-IITs-offer-interior-designing-courses?-",
    "answer" : "No iit nift or nit offers it they offer architecture and product design and industrial design for interior design you need to go to cept ahemdabad,nids,pearl academy ,mit Pune,ggsipu delhi,and many other institutions offers it. Or you can go for product design and make thesis in furniture design and can pursue interiors in professional field many private universities also offer this course you can go for it also Sachin Kumbhar",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:42:12.022Z"),
    "question" : "Which IITs offer interior designing courses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca8f5b30e99eeabcd534e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-majors-should-I-take-for-having-interior-designing-as-my-career?-",
    "answer" : "A bachelor's in interior design will give you a broad, technical understanding of the field (residential and commercial design). An associate degree is fine if you're more into decorating, but if you want to do a lot of custom remodeling work in other people's homes or pursue commercial design then a bachelors is highly recommended.  Also, if you think you may want to own your own design practice or even a small shop someday (lots of designers branch off onto their own at some point; I did much sooner than I anticipated!), then I would probably recommend some businesses courses, as well, if that's not already included in the design curriculum of the school you choose to attend. (If there's one thing I wish my school's design program had more of, it would be business courses.) What's more, l Continue Reading A bachelor's in interior design will give you a broad, technical understanding of the field (residential and commercial design). An associate degree is fine if you're more into decorating, but if you want to do a lot of custom remodeling work in other people's homes or pursue commercial design then a bachelors is highly recommended.  Also, if you think you may want to own your own design practice or even a small shop someday (lots of designers branch off onto their own at some point; I did much sooner than I anticipated!), then I would probably recommend some businesses courses, as well, if that's not already included in the design curriculum of the school you choose to attend. (If there's one thing I wish my school's design program had more of, it would be business courses.) What's more, l Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:42:29.546Z"),
    "question" : "What majors should I take for having interior designing as my career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca919b30e99eeabcd5359"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-masters-degree-required-for-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Since you have done your 4 years of Architecture program, which has given you a general sense of what architecture design and thought process. Doing a Masters in Interior Design is very beneficial, as it will train you in space allocation and programming which will assist you if you decide to work in architectural design. If you decide to pursue work in an Interiors firm, it will assist in that you have a basic fundamentals of architectural and knowledge set for interior design. A Masters in Interiors is where you can specialise in: Hospitality, Retail, Commercial, and Residential; and the more work experience you have with these specialisation, the more you can transition to other firms. The compensation for Interiors work is much better than architecture work.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:43:05.529Z"),
    "question" : "Is a masters degree required for an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca931b30e99eeabcd5366"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-find-a-good-interior-designer-in-the-Greater-Noida?-",
    "answer" : "Easyhome solutions designed my complete home in Greater Noida Alpha-1. They are true professionals when it comes to designing your interior. Their staff are very helpful and friendly in nature. They also provide free site visit and estimate cost of the project.                         Their 3 step process which makes the process fluent. Our three step interior design process Step 1Understanding clients design idea: In the first step we deeply understand clients design ideas. We take into account the colors, design elements and feel of the idea. Step 2Optimizing clients design: Keeping in mind the recommended color, design elements of the client we optimize it by adding some finishing touches and then make multiple computer programmed demo to show the client. Step 3Start designing: After the client shows the green flag Continue Reading Easyhome solutions designed my complete home in Greater Noida Alpha-1. They are true professionals when it comes to designing your interior. Their staff are very helpful and friendly in nature. They also provide free site visit and estimate cost of the project.                         Their 3 step process which makes the process fluent. Our three step interior design process Step 1Understanding clients design idea: In the first step we deeply understand clients design ideas. We take into account the colors, design elements and feel of the idea. Step 2Optimizing clients design: Keeping in mind the recommended color, design elements of the client we optimize it by adding some finishing touches and then make multiple computer programmed demo to show the client. Step 3Start designing: After the client shows the green flag Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:43:29.833Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I find a good interior designer in the Greater Noida? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca943b30e99eeabcd536c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-are-the-best-architects-and-interior-designers-in-Hyderabad?-",
    "answer" : "In the event that you have been taking a gander at the best inside fashioners to fabricate your home or office space, at that point, the time has come to investigate the entirety of the focuses you should remember before you waitlist one. Finding an inside planner isn't extremely troublesome these days, however finding the correct one for you could require significant investment! With rising thriving, India is host to numerous who are getting increasingly eager about their homes just like office spaces. There are numerous inside architects working in India, and a large number of them have a solid comprehension of the specialized needs of the space. Some of them are growing new styles and alluring structures also. In any case, the best inside architects will build up your space in your direc Continue Reading In the event that you have been taking a gander at the best inside fashioners to fabricate your home or office space, at that point, the time has come to investigate the entirety of the focuses you should remember before you waitlist one. Finding an inside planner isn't extremely troublesome these days, however finding the correct one for you could require significant investment! With rising thriving, India is host to numerous who are getting increasingly eager about their homes just like office spaces. There are numerous inside architects working in India, and a large number of them have a solid comprehension of the specialized needs of the space. Some of them are growing new styles and alluring structures also. In any case, the best inside architects will build up your space in your direc Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:43:47.535Z"),
    "question" : "Who are the best architects and interior designers in Hyderabad? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca952b30e99eeabcd5372"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-I-need-to-start-an-interior-designing-company?-",
    "answer" : "Joydeb Dasgupta You start with the advantage of having enough experience within your family to fall back upon. The success story of your grand parents and not so successful experience of your father. Their experiences should improve your learning curve and you might also have a ready clientele base to approach. Well, interior design is a very creative area and I consider it more as an intellectual property than the real materials that come out of it..So more creative you are, the chances of hitting the market will be more. Fortunately, the number of high income bracket of people in India, who are basically your target group, are increasing by the day. You must be aware that your clients are based out of Metro cities, Capital cities and Tier II cities in India at the moment. So the location of your unit has  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:44:02.483Z"),
    "question" : "What do I need to start an interior designing company? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca97cb30e99eeabcd5382"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-designers-in-Bhubaneswar?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which is the best interior designers in Bhubaneswar?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:44:44.799Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior designers in Bhubaneswar? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca9aeb30e99eeabcd5396"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-a-civil-engineer-become-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, It's the best combo. You are a professional who deals with construction, design and maintenance from civil perspective. Interior Designing covers your creation with space, appropriate lighting, and beautiful designing covering both interior and exterior of any building. You would also get better job opportunities in India, abroad and even online projects. So Go for it! Foresta Ply",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:45:34.129Z"),
    "question" : "Can a civil engineer become an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca9beb30e99eeabcd53a0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-interior-design-company-in-Noida?-",
    "answer" : "Interior Designers:  If you are moving into a new home or remodeling your current one, you could be considering hiring someone to help in building new. A quick search on the internet and some input from family and friends will leave you with more questions. What is the difference between designers and which should you hire. They provide different service as although it is differently mistaken. So the difference between an interior designer and interior decorator is difficult to understand. Interior designers in Delhi usually work closely with architects and decorators. In a way, the team works on the same goal, presentation of the final look for client satisfaction. This means that decorators and designers will involve at the beginning of a project up until the last decorative piece is place Continue Reading Interior Designers:  If you are moving into a new home or remodeling your current one, you could be considering hiring someone to help in building new. A quick search on the internet and some input from family and friends will leave you with more questions. What is the difference between designers and which should you hire. They provide different service as although it is differently mistaken. So the difference between an interior designer and interior decorator is difficult to understand. Interior designers in Delhi usually work closely with architects and decorators. In a way, the team works on the same goal, presentation of the final look for client satisfaction. This means that decorators and designers will involve at the beginning of a project up until the last decorative piece is place Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:45:50.422Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best interior design company in Noida? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca9d2b30e99eeabcd53ac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-main-different-between-a-creative-interior-designer-and-a-commercial-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Creative Interior designer : - Take their job as their passion - They can reduce their fees too .- They try to make new things and unique items in each project .- They don't misguide their clients - They focus on colours and themes . Commercial Interior designer :- Earning is more important then  anything .- They work with limited themes and design - Might not have an education background in interior design field .- They work like a contractor .  Hope you get the differences between two .  Shape Interior , JaipurAmit Sharma ( 8290310808 )A Creative Interior Designer . 2",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:46:10.853Z"),
    "question" : "What is the main different between a creative interior designer and a commercial interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca9e4b30e99eeabcd53b4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-modular-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Modular interior design (also, \"modularity in design\") can be defined as an approach in designing that subdivides a design system into smaller parts. These smaller parts can be created independently as well as used in different systems in order to drive multiple functionalities. Modularity in designing offers several advantages to interior designers. It is greatly helpful to designers in working out the solutions to the common problems that are independent of all projects. This kind of independent work enables the designers to consistently improve their solutions. It helps in leading to an efficient development through reuse.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:46:28.127Z"),
    "question" : "What is modular interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603ca9f4b30e99eeabcd53b8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-most-creative-office-space-interior-designers-in-Bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Dushkriti Chacko Perfect Interior Designs, is one of classic and the best interior designers in Bangalore. We are working actively with our highly qualified interior design team to be established as the best interior design company in Bangalore and one of luxurious . We are dealing and rendering our interior design services on a large scale like home interior designers in Bangalore, commercial and corporate interior design services, office and retail space interior decorating services in order to meet our customer’s requirements etc. For all these good cause, we are named and being listed as top 10 interior designers and decorators in Bangalore, Karnataka. We are sharp intelligent for creating elegant, dynamic interior combined with zeal and creativity. Our hospitality interior designers and decoration team Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:46:44.027Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the most creative office space interior designers in Bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa06b30e99eeabcd53c0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-become-an-interior-decorater-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Decide that you want to be an interior designer.Get a degree/diploma from a renowned college/institute.Learn AutoCAD, 3DsMax/Sketchup + Vray.Complete an internship of at least 6months.Get a job experience of at least 2 years.And you’re done. Ramesh Patel",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:47:02.204Z"),
    "question" : "How can I become an interior decorater in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa18b30e99eeabcd53cc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-home-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Riya Das, Interior DesignerAnswered 6 months agoHow is home interior design? Riya Das According to my knowledge and opinion, home interior designs are a technique to make your home appeal attractive and organized in the eye of consumers. A home is your personal space, and, in that space, you need to feel the warmth and comfort. Interior designing helps consumers give home a luxurious look along with cozy feels. Another advantage of designing interiors of your home is that you get a chance of having the latest and trendy designs for your home. Gone are the days when the walls of your house were painted pale white colors, home interior designers encourage you to explore various contrast options to have a smart home!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:47:20.562Z"),
    "question" : "How is home interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa29b30e99eeabcd53d1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-interesting-topics-for-interior-design-theisis?-",
    "answer" : "Subathra Vijaykumar Space Planning, Colour Scheme, Modular Furnitures, Design Theme, Artifacts, Modern Design, Services, Use of natural materials and many more. You must have surely thaught of all these and might have already rejected them in your mind. The above mentioned topics would get selected by many others so what special would you do? I will not confuse you anymore with n number of topics but I will give you one such topic which is so common now a days but nobody talks about it. Maybe I never thaught of any such thing during my college days. It is a very big problem which is faced by alot of Architects and Designers. I understood it only when I started working and taking designing jobs. As for now the market for Interior Designers is at peak. The standard of living of Indians is growing day by day and maj Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:47:37.822Z"),
    "question" : "What are some interesting topics for interior design theisis? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa3cb30e99eeabcd53d8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-an-interior-designing-course-good-for-women?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Is an interior designing course good for women? Hello Quora User, Why did you asked this question even? I’m not a feminist but I’ll tell you onething. A women has the power to do anything in this world.She can even conquer the world. And coming to your question, Now a days there is hardly in any difference between a boy and a girl. Girls can do things that boys cannot. ( No offense to boys though) Also, Many of the famous interior designers are women. 1- Twinkle Khanna - The white window 2- Gauri Khan - The design cell 3- Suzanne Khan - The Charcoal Project 4- Mana Shetty - R house 5-Parmeshwar Godrej I myself being an architecture student would suggest that interiors is one of the best career to pursue with lots income and Obviously creativity and hardwork is required. Thank you",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:47:56.094Z"),
    "question" : "Is an interior designing course good for women? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa4eb30e99eeabcd53e2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Where-can-I-get-reliable-information-about-a-commercial-interior-designer-in-Delhi?-",
    "answer" : "Sapna Aggarwal Google: It’s very easy to manipulate rankings on Google but there’s still a way to just search on Google and find out about a great interior designing firm in Delhi. Don’t just go with the first result. Check at least 1st 3 pages. Make a list of designers you see on these pages.Go to their website and see their portfolio. See the designs they’ve already made.See their customer testimonials, if available.Visit their facebook page and read reviews there.See what other people are talking about about the names you have narrowed down.Go and talk to actual friends and family who might have hired interior designers in past.Doing all this will help you narrow down to a small list of 5–6 interiors designers in Delhi. Now, go and meet these people. Call them and schedule a meeting. Talk to them. Talki Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:48:14.865Z"),
    "question" : "Where can I get reliable information about a commercial interior designer in Delhi? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa61b30e99eeabcd53ea"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-cept-good-for-interior-designing?-",
    "answer" : "Yes its a very good institute for all courses but getting addmision in cept is to competitive becoz the entrance exam is very difficult if u have good knowledge of basic design concept colours and perspective then apply for it . Fees is about 4 lack per year for BSC ID Web Solutionz",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:48:33.230Z"),
    "question" : "Is cept good for interior designing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa75b30e99eeabcd53f0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-do-interior-designing-after-btech-with-civil-branch?-",
    "answer" : "Yes you can. Example: Myself I completed my B.E (Civil Engineering) and planning M.E (Structural). But I do more interior design (Views. 2D and contract) than civil drawing or other works. Software knowledge and Creativity is only requirement.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:48:53.360Z"),
    "question" : "Can I do interior designing after btech with civil branch? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caa92b30e99eeabcd5400"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-struggle-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "What is the hardest part of becoming an interior designer? Finding a job squarely within your field, at a reputable firm. You have little control over the market, so that’s the soul-crushing part of preparing to become an interior designer. After that, the NCIDQ is your biggest hill to climb, but don’t worry; you’ve got a couple of years in the field before you can even register for the exam. Spend that time building your skills as quickly as you can. When you feel like it’s time to get certified, give yourself four to six months to study intensely, purchase the textbook, make flash cards in a stack 8″ thick, quiz yourself with study buddies, and most importantly: Buy at least two different years of sample practicums. Don’t look over them ahead of time; just pull out the instructions and make Continue Reading What is the hardest part of becoming an interior designer? Finding a job squarely within your field, at a reputable firm. You have little control over the market, so that’s the soul-crushing part of preparing to become an interior designer. After that, the NCIDQ is your biggest hill to climb, but don’t worry; you’ve got a couple of years in the field before you can even register for the exam. Spend that time building your skills as quickly as you can. When you feel like it’s time to get certified, give yourself four to six months to study intensely, purchase the textbook, make flash cards in a stack 8″ thick, quiz yourself with study buddies, and most importantly: Buy at least two different years of sample practicums. Don’t look over them ahead of time; just pull out the instructions and make Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:49:22.180Z"),
    "question" : "What is the struggle for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caac8b30e99eeabcd5414"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-companies-handle-interior-design-of-their-office-space?-",
    "answer" : "Aamrapali Bhogle Infrastructure Managers of companies, also known as Facility Managers, engage a Design Team most suited to their culture, aesthetic sensibilities and budget to have their spaces executed professionally. The Design Team thereafter, takes over responsibility for requested provisions. Any experienced Designer should be able to include general office requirements in the project. However, the company needs to guide their Designer regarding the company's hierarchy, functional grouping, IT and other requirements as applicable to various Departments in their specific industry. Almost as a rule, Office Interior Projects run on shoestring budgets. Least budget is spent on decor items that will remain permanently affixed to the place, such as wallpapers. An optimum balance is achieved between the compa Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:50:16.752Z"),
    "question" : "How do companies handle interior design of their office space? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caadfb30e99eeabcd541b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-do-interior-designing-after-civil-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Shiyas Veliyath 4",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:50:39.178Z"),
    "question" : "How can I do interior designing after civil engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cab08b30e99eeabcd5431"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-tips-would-you-ask-an-interior-designer-to-help-you-with?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What tips would you ask an interior designer to help you with?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:51:20.309Z"),
    "question" : "What tips would you ask an interior designer to help you with? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cab4bb30e99eeabcd5449"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-most-disgusting-interior-designs-ever?-",
    "answer" : "Good design is about putting the user first. If the customer can’t make sense of it and if their every single move is impeded by the bad decisions that the designers and builders made, we’ve got a serious problem. Sometimes these problems all come down to bad craftsmanship, shoddy design, and unaesthetic, hurried, and impractical shortcuts that some builders take without a care in this world. 1 - The tunnel.   2 - Next to the kitchen and wardrobe.   3 - If it fits I shits.   4 - Just sit.   5 - Ohhh.   6 - Just as well there's a toilet paper shortage.   7 - Well.. do what you gotta do.   8 - This sink.   9 - Imagine having to clean it.   10 - There are so many wrong things in this picture.   11 - Imagine trying to negotiate this after a few beers.   12 - You can't even sit on it.  Continue Reading Good design is about putting the user first. If the customer can’t make sense of it and if their every single move is impeded by the bad decisions that the designers and builders made, we’ve got a serious problem. Sometimes these problems all come down to bad craftsmanship, shoddy design, and unaesthetic, hurried, and impractical shortcuts that some builders take without a care in this world. 1 - The tunnel.   2 - Next to the kitchen and wardrobe.   3 - If it fits I shits.   4 - Just sit.   5 - Ohhh.   6 - Just as well there's a toilet paper shortage.   7 - Well.. do what you gotta do.   8 - This sink.   9 - Imagine having to clean it.   10 - There are so many wrong things in this picture.   11 - Imagine trying to negotiate this after a few beers.   12 - You can't even sit on it.  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:52:27.741Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the most disgusting interior designs ever? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cab5bb30e99eeabcd544e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-interior-decorator-in-Patna?-",
    "answer" : "There are many good interior designers in Patna. You should always choose experienced interior designers to design your home. Lets take a look at some of the best interior designers in Patna. Before choosing an interior designer, do a good research about their costing, previous work etc. You can find all this information in review websites like the one below. Top 10 Interior Designers in Patna with Cost and Images Ashoka Interiors One of the best interior designers in Patna. They work on residential as well as commercial projects. The designs are elaborate, functional and comfortable. Services Interior designModular kitchenWoodwork furniture  Eyeconic interiors Eyeconic Interiors gives a unique touch for the residential design where you feel more satisfied. They have over t Continue Reading There are many good interior designers in Patna. You should always choose experienced interior designers to design your home. Lets take a look at some of the best interior designers in Patna. Before choosing an interior designer, do a good research about their costing, previous work etc. You can find all this information in review websites like the one below. Top 10 Interior Designers in Patna with Cost and Images Ashoka Interiors One of the best interior designers in Patna. They work on residential as well as commercial projects. The designs are elaborate, functional and comfortable. Services Interior designModular kitchenWoodwork furniture  Eyeconic interiors Eyeconic Interiors gives a unique touch for the residential design where you feel more satisfied. They have over t Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:52:43.149Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best interior decorator in Patna? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cab6cb30e99eeabcd5455"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-hire-an-interior-designer-or-just-go-straight-to-the-contractor?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Should I hire an interior designer or just go straight to the contractor?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:53:00.040Z"),
    "question" : "Should I hire an interior designer or just go straight to the contractor? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cab90b30e99eeabcd5464"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-interesting-interior-design-detailing-that-one-has-come-across?-",
    "answer" : "David Whitaker  this isn't unique to interior design, but any design genre That you do a concept and plan and all the technical drawings and renderings. its often just your guess and you need to believe in your idea ~ justify that the planning is the best function and everything's working… then you are there when its being built and still when its only structure you're comparing your ideas for the proportions of features ~ heights, relationships of shapes with how it's looking as it progresses finally built its hopefully confirmation that the idea was right and you had the ability to imagine a space and bet that idea on actually specifying dimensions; and built it lives up to the concept and your innovations proved to be “good thinking” EDIT Quora merged this question with the question I answered which asked ~ Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:53:36.019Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most interesting interior design detailing that one has come across? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caba1b30e99eeabcd5469"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-Japanese-interior-design-ideas?-",
    "answer" : "Japanese Interior Design Ideas:  Image Source: Workinjapan Japan consistently has a beautiful and rich culture, which sets them as the best from the rest for notoriety and uniqueness. In this big competition to improve the norms of life, we neglect to carry on with life. Is it accurate to say that you are ready to identify with this pressure and horrible assumption cycle? For what reason don't we make a tranquil sanctuary in the solace of our own home with the Japanese interior design? Think about the accompanying plans to make your sanctum your own Zen. If you wish to add the class of Japan to your home, follow the accompanying Japanese interior design ideas to make your Zen: Introduce Elements of Nature  Image Source: luxelivingasia Japanese have faith in keeping earth most importantly, and the ideal approach to keep warm relations with nature is by bringing nature inside, thinking about how to do it? Bring Japanese plants like Bonsai, bamboo, umbrella tree, and maple to bring a little touch. While picking any green plant, try to pick straightforward, green, and natural, as frequently, you won't see vivid decorative designs in a commonplace home. Another approach to do it is by extensive and enormous windows to bring numerous points of nature inside. Special Japanese Doors  Image Source: Pinterest Regarding the entryway, you have a lot of choices to browse to bring the Japanese feel inside the house. The customary entryway is called shoji, which is a legitimate sliding entryway. Because of the significant expense of living, for the most part, Japanese homes are small, so they use sliders to save cost and space. Stylish Entryway  Image Source: Resources. Real estate The Japanese call the entrance genkan; this is where you can welcome the guests, so make a point to hold a space where you can promptly request that they keep shoes (as per Japanese, it isn't reasonable to stroll inside with shoes). You can find in the picture; there is a rack to store shoes in a primary and rich bureau. You can go for stone tile flooring at the passage as it is clear to clean and profoundly sturdy contrasted with different sorts of the ground surface. Beautiful Color Choice  Image Source: Pufikhomes As a whole, we have perceived that the Japanese love basic things, and a similar principle applies in the shading decision. Like the style, their decision for the tone is additionally enlivened naturally, as wooden components and green plants. They lean toward light tones for dividers with the room's standard components like wood racks, deck, and characteristic houseplants. Conclusion With little effort, you can create a cozy and Japanese interior design. These were some of the few tips and ideas to create your comfort zone. What do you think about these ideas? I hope you apply these ideas to your house and give a luxurious look to your house. Thank You, Have A Great Day!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:53:53.337Z"),
    "question" : "What are some Japanese interior design ideas? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cabb5b30e99eeabcd5475"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-determine-commercial-interior-design-fees?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:54:13.662Z"),
    "question" : "How do I determine commercial interior design fees? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cabc6b30e99eeabcd547d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-interior-design-practical?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is interior design practical?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:54:30.970Z"),
    "question" : "Is interior design practical? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cabdcb30e99eeabcd5483"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-freelance-interior-design-sites?-",
    "answer" : "Bennin Wilfred Sound Absorption Operable Partition Wall for Room Dividing The HuiAcoustics company is ready to provide service for you from our headquarters in Guangzhou, China. Additional support, where necessary or desired, is available from reliable overseas subsidiaries that perform to the same high standards. This powerful combination is our guarantee of innovative, operable partition, acoustic wall and ceiling products, stable pricing and timely delivery on a global basis. Sound Absorbing Operable Partitions Walls for Rooms Dividing Products HUI ACOUSTICS Sound Insulation Mass Loaded Vinyl Manufacturer In ChinaAcoustic Sliding Partition Wall for Hall Room DividersSoundproofing and Fireproof Fabric Panel With Glass WoolHUI ACOUSTICS Customized Office Furniture Soundproofing Desk ScreenGypsum Wooden  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:54:52.377Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best freelance interior design sites? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cabeeb30e99eeabcd548f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-average-salary-for-an-interior-designer-in-bangalore?-",
    "answer" : "Interior designing is a practice that involves planning, furnishing and optimally utilizing the space in a room in a residential or commercial building. In a world where space is getting smaller and making it functional and visually pleasing is getting difficult, the interior designer plays a very significant role. Interior designers Bangalore is a sought-after career option as qualified and creative professionals who can meet with the customer’s budget and preferences are in demand. Therefore, salary for interior designer is dependent on their recognition, years of experience and many other factors.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:55:10.358Z"),
    "question" : "What is the average salary for an interior designer in bangalore? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cac27b30e99eeabcd54a9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-do-interior-designers-charge-for-square-feet-for-interior-design-and-elevation?-",
    "answer" : "Well everyone has their own setbacks and prices.some charge accordingly on material contract basis,some charge only for Design execution and some charge according to consultantion. Everyone has their own style of work and they charge accordingly to that basis.If u really want to know about the prices then do a survey on your area and get to know how everyone is working or you can also work under any designer for experience purpose,then you will get to know how to work and charge accordingly in this competitive field.I hope this might help you and have a great Life .Good luck for future ✌️",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:56:07.246Z"),
    "question" : "How much do interior designers charge for square feet for interior design and elevation? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cac48b30e99eeabcd54b3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-market-size-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "The business of interior design has been quite good over the last twelve months, and we can expect that to continue. Last year’s State of the Industry report showed that interior designing had fully recovered to pre-recession levels, and the momentum carried through this year, with only slight moderation. FACTORS IMPACTING INTERIOR DESIGN: GLOBAL ISSUES The Economy Environmental Protection Security CULTURE/VALUES Generational Differences Well-being Community Design Excellence BUSINESS OF DESIGN Value Proposition Firm Structure Time Data & Knowledge The following statistics shows the rapid growth of interior design industry…  With all indicators showing robust growth, this is a good time to be in the interior design business. Continue Reading The business of interior design has been quite good over the last twelve months, and we can expect that to continue. Last year’s State of the Industry report showed that interior designing had fully recovered to pre-recession levels, and the momentum carried through this year, with only slight moderation. FACTORS IMPACTING INTERIOR DESIGN: GLOBAL ISSUES The Economy Environmental Protection Security CULTURE/VALUES Generational Differences Well-being Community Design Excellence BUSINESS OF DESIGN Value Proposition Firm Structure Time Data & Knowledge The following statistics shows the rapid growth of interior design industry…  With all indicators showing robust growth, this is a good time to be in the interior design business. Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:56:40.394Z"),
    "question" : "What is the market size for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cac6eb30e99eeabcd54c5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-interior-design-part-of-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is interior design part of engineering?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:57:18.645Z"),
    "question" : "Is interior design part of engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cac7eb30e99eeabcd54c9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Who-is-the-best-interior-designer-in-the-world?-",
    "answer" : "Some of the most famous Interior Designers are:-  Source: **Sanjyt Syngh** Sanjyt Syngh: Sanjyt runs his studio in New Delhi with the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio. He is known for his bespoke designs and the incredible space management designs that are a treat for the eyes. She and her mother manage the firm and he is known as the face of the modern age Indian Interior Designers. Lipika Sud: When it comes to the designing of residential spaces, corporate offices and hotels the first name that comes in our mind is Lipika Sud. She runs a big firm known as Lipika Sud Interiors Pvt. Ltd. She is the founder of one other interior designing company which is Art n Aura. Apart from these achievements, she is also the former chairperson of the IIID which is a milestone in itself. Sussanne Khan: For those who Continue Reading Some of the most famous Interior Designers are:-  Source: **Sanjyt Syngh** Sanjyt Syngh: Sanjyt runs his studio in New Delhi with the name of Sanjyt Syngh studio. He is known for his bespoke designs and the incredible space management designs that are a treat for the eyes. She and her mother manage the firm and he is known as the face of the modern age Indian Interior Designers. Lipika Sud: When it comes to the designing of residential spaces, corporate offices and hotels the first name that comes in our mind is Lipika Sud. She runs a big firm known as Lipika Sud Interiors Pvt. Ltd. She is the founder of one other interior designing company which is Art n Aura. Apart from these achievements, she is also the former chairperson of the IIID which is a milestone in itself. Sussanne Khan: For those who Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:57:34.686Z"),
    "question" : "Who is the best interior designer in the world? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cac8fb30e99eeabcd54cf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-should-be-the-first-priority-for-interior-design?-",
    "answer" : "Your Client is always your first priority. In order to conceive and execute a successful design program LISTEN to and understand your clients’ needs and goals. They are the ones who will pay for it and live there.  Interior design is much more than ‘another beautiful space’. It is about creating an environment that is functional, comfortable and aesthetically pleasing where your clients will want to spend time. Good business sense (too many times overlooked) as important as your skill as a designer . Establish a professional, trusting and ethical relationship or your work will never be truly successful, no matter how ‘good’. Perform to the best of all your abilities. Consult professionals in areas you are weak. It is their money; respect their budget. Establish what can reasonably be achieved w Continue Reading Your Client is always your first priority. In order to conceive and execute a successful design program LISTEN to and understand your clients’ needs and goals. They are the ones who will pay for it and live there.  Interior design is much more than ‘another beautiful space’. It is about creating an environment that is functional, comfortable and aesthetically pleasing where your clients will want to spend time. Good business sense (too many times overlooked) as important as your skill as a designer . Establish a professional, trusting and ethical relationship or your work will never be truly successful, no matter how ‘good’. Perform to the best of all your abilities. Consult professionals in areas you are weak. It is their money; respect their budget. Establish what can reasonably be achieved w Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:57:51.065Z"),
    "question" : "What should be the first priority for interior design? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603caca1b30e99eeabcd54db"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-innovative-name-can-I-use-for-an-interior-designing-firm?-",
    "answer" : "Andrey Gavrilov, Interior architect and designer for 16+ years, owner of design firmAnswered 5 years ago · Author has 333 answers and 393.7K answer viewsWhat innovative name can I use for an interior designing firm? Andrey Gavrilov",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:58:09.004Z"),
    "question" : "What innovative name can I use for an interior designing firm? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cacb2b30e99eeabcd54e1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-calculate-the-GST-for-an-interior-design-work-contract?-",
    "answer" : "GST (Goods and service tax), has been kept at 18% for any works contracts service in India. Hence even for an interior design work contract has been kept at the rate of 18%. All such contracts are deemed to be service contracts by treating transactions under such contracts as the offer of services. Though the goods supplied below a works contract, such as mixed contracts currently thought of to be service contracts. Consequently, tax is going to be owed as per the purpose of taxation and place of offer specified for services and not as per an equivalent prescribed for goods. Mukund Abhyankar CA, Prop. M.B.Abhyankar and Co.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:58:26.579Z"),
    "question" : "How do I calculate the GST for an interior design work contract? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cacc7b30e99eeabcd54e8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Interior-designs-study-art-or-science?-",
    "answer" : "To my understanding Interior design can be categorised as science subject. In my country’s universities though it still grouped with art and can only be found in art faculty. What makes me say it’s science is because decision in interior design should be able to be explained rationally and there should be some valid reason as to why you are designing the design. Not only that, even choosing what colour a room should be (ideally) based on some scientific research such as psychology of colour. It’s quite different with arts that tend to priorities “muse” alone or “instinct”. Though both is used in interior design, there still need to be a valid and explainable reason why the muse or instinct can be used in the design",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:58:47.470Z"),
    "question" : "Interior designs study art or science? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cacf5b30e99eeabcd54fb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-commercial-interior-designers-in-pune?-",
    "answer" : "Interior Design is a wide and vivid term, it ranges from the selection of furniture design to colour palette and hold the power to change the feel of the space. The key to a successful business is Location but even with greatest location in the world, a business can easily fail if its interior is not well executed. Commercial design seeks to increase functionality and elevate your style. The scope of work is much larger than the residential projections as commercial interior designers take more responsibility. I know a firm who is into Commercial and Residential interiors named Arrivae. They have a well experienced and skilled designers to fulfil all your interior designing requirements. Their designs aim to maximise aesthetics as well as functionality of your property and also believe in  Continue Reading Interior Design is a wide and vivid term, it ranges from the selection of furniture design to colour palette and hold the power to change the feel of the space. The key to a successful business is Location but even with greatest location in the world, a business can easily fail if its interior is not well executed. Commercial design seeks to increase functionality and elevate your style. The scope of work is much larger than the residential projections as commercial interior designers take more responsibility. I know a firm who is into Commercial and Residential interiors named Arrivae. They have a well experienced and skilled designers to fulfil all your interior designing requirements. Their designs aim to maximise aesthetics as well as functionality of your property and also believe in  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:59:33.658Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the commercial interior designers in pune? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cad07b30e99eeabcd5501"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-there-schools-for-interior-design-when-most-interior-designers-are-self-taught?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Why are there schools for interior design when most interior designers are self-taught?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T08:59:51.325Z"),
    "question" : "Why are there schools for interior design when most interior designers are self-taught? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cad18b30e99eeabcd550c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-salary-of-n-interior-designer-in-USA?-",
    "answer" : "There is no such thing as an ID salary. There is a world out there for you to conquer, with skill, taste, imagination, and the desire to help others. Start wherever you can start (first get your degree), then, like your garden, nourish and feed your career with great work, satisfied clients, and in time you'll be making all the bucks you are so concerned about now. But perhaps your biggest reward may be the satisfaction of having met and worked for, and satisfied, legions of clients who trusted you, respected you, and whom you were honored to know and even call \"friend\". Bon chance!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T09:00:08.475Z"),
    "question" : "What is the salary of n interior designer in USA? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cad2cb30e99eeabcd5514"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-should-you-hire-an-interior-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Why should you hire an interior designer?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T09:00:28.288Z"),
    "question" : "Why should you hire an interior designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603cad5db30e99eeabcd552b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-interior-designers-in-Thane?-",
    "answer" : "Ankit Kapoor Let’s choose good interior designers in Thane, If you search this query on the google you will find lots of companies with the beautiful images that can make you say WOW. But, are they real images? are these designs done by them? The answer is no, not every time. these interior design images are downloaded from other websites and these guys just upload them on their website to attract more customers and make more money. You may say, I am criticising others, No, I am not here to criticise somebody but this is the truth. So, how you should find? I am telling you the exact process to find the top interior designers in your location. First, don’t just see the images but ask for the portfolio, it will you give some idea to see their past projects and work experiences which are very important to do. And Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-03-01T09:01:17.056Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good interior designers in Thane? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}